<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nicotiana Benthamiana on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/nicotiana-benthamiana/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nicotiana Benthamiana on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/nicotiana-benthamiana/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NbALD1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/niben101scf04547g02001.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/niben101scf04547g02001.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Niben101Scf04547g02001.1 Gene Symbol: NbALD1 Gene Name: AGD2-LIKE DEFENCE RESPONSE PROTEIN 1 Genome: Nicotiana benthamiana Genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbALY916</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbaly916/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbaly916/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbALY916 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: NbALY916 is involved in potato virus X P25-triggered cell death in Nicotiana benthamiana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbBAG5</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbbag5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbbag5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbBAG5 Gene Name: B-cell lymphoma2-associated athanogenes5 Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: Through overexpression and down-regulation of NbBAG5, results showed that NbBAG5 could negatively regulate ToCV infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbBGAL1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_benthamiana/nbbgal1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_benthamiana/nbbgal1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;NbS00024332g0007.1 Gene Symbol: NbBGAL1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Description: our data demonstrate that NbBGAL1 acts on galactosylated complex N-glycans of plant-produced glycoproteins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbBTF3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbbtf3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbbtf3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbBTF3 Gene Name: basic transcription factor 3 Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: Silencing of NbBTF3 results in developmental defects and disturbed gene expression in chloroplasts and mitochondria of higher plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbCdc27B</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbcdc27b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbcdc27b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbCdc27B Gene Name: cell division cycle 27 Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: Suppression of Cdc27B expression induces plant defence responses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbCML30</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/niben101scf07608g00007/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/niben101scf07608g00007/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Niben101Scf07608g00007 Gene Symbol: NbCML30 Gene Name: calmodulin-like protein 30 Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: Tobacco mosaic virus hijacks its coat protein-interacting protein IP-L to inhibit NbCML30, a calmodulin-like protein, to enhance its infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbCMT3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbcmt3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbcmt3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbCMT3 Gene Name: chromomethylase protein 3 Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: Virus-induced gene silencing of NbCMT3/3-2 in N.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbCMT3-2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbcmt3-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbcmt3-2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbCMT3-2 Gene Name: chromomethylase3-2 Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: Developmental- and Tissue-Specific Expression of NbCMT3-2 Encoding a Chromomethylase in Nicotiana benthamiana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbEXPA1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbs00007680g0013.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbs00007680g0013.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: NbS00007680g0013.1 Gene Symbol: NbEXPA1 Gene Name: α-expansin protein Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: NbEXPA1, an α-expansin, is plasmodesmata-specific and a novel host factor for potyviral infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbGSTU4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbgstu4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbgstu4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbGSTU4 Gene Name: glutathione transferase4 Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: The glutathione transferase of Nicotiana benthamiana NbGSTU4 plays a role in regulating the early replication of Bamboo mosaic virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbMYB4L</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/niben101scf03570ctg037/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/niben101scf03570ctg037/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Niben101Scf03570Ctg037 Gene Symbol: NbMYB4L Gene Name: Genome: Sol Genomics Network(https://solgenomics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbNOG1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/niben101scf02909g02010.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/niben101scf02909g02010.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Niben101Scf02909g02010.1 Gene Symbol: NbNOG1 Gene Name: Nucleolar GTP-binding protein 1 Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: We characterized NbNOG1, a Nicotiana benthamiana NOG1 ortholog sharing more than 45% amino acid identity with Trypanosoma, yeast, and human NOG1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbPIP2;4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_benthamiana/nbpip24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_benthamiana/nbpip24/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: NbPIP2;4 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Description: this study elucidates a conserved and novel pathway caused by GP1pro to initiate host cellular defences by targeting the plant aquaporin protein NbPIP2;4 and transporting apoplast-to-cytoplast H2O2 to regulate plant immunity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbRabE1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbrabe1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbrabe1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbRabE1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: We characterized the gene expression, subcellular localization, and in vivo functions of a Nicotiana benthamiana small GTPase belonging to the RabE family, designated NbRabE1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbRABG3f</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbrabg3f/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbrabg3f/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbRABG3f Gene Name: Rab small GTPase Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: NbRABG3f, a member of Rab GTPase, is involved in Bamboo mosaic virus infection in Nicotiana benthamiana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbRae1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbrae1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbrae1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbRae1 Gene Name: RNA export 1 Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: Virus-induced gene silencing of Nicotiana benthamiana Rae1, NbRae1, which encodes a protein with four WD40 repeats, resulted in growth arrest and abnormal leaf development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbRAF2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbraf2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-benthamiana/nbraf2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NbRAF2 Gene Name: Rubisco assembly factor 2 Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Descriptions: Rubisco assembly factor 2 (NbRAF2), which localizes in the nucleus, cell periphery, chloroplasts, and stromules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NbWRKY1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_benthamiana/nbwrky1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_benthamiana/nbwrky1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: NbWRKY1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Nicotiana benthamiana Functional Description: Our recent study has shown that NbWRKY1, a Group I WRKY transcription factor, positively regulates the incompatible interaction between a mulcrilevirus, mulberry mosaic dwarf associated virus (MMDaV) and N.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
