<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Citrus Sinensis on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/citrus-sinensis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Citrus Sinensis on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/citrus-sinensis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ABF2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/abf2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/abf2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs3g23480 Gene Symbol: ABF2 Gene Name: Genome: Reference genome of sweet orange Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: A model was proposed to illustrate how ABF2 mediates the ABA signalling involved in sucrose transport, chlorophyll degradation, auxin homoeostasis, carotenoid and ABA biosynthesis, and cell wall metabolism during citrus fruit development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CitACS4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cla011230/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cla011230/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cla011230 Gene Symbol: CitACS4 Gene Name: 1-aminocyclopropane-1-carboxylate synthase 4 Genome: watermelon genome() Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: Mutation in the gene encoding 1-aminocyclopropane-1-carboxylate synthase 4 (CitACS4) led to andromonoecy in watermelon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CitERF71</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrus-sinensis/orange1.1g047100m/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrus-sinensis/orange1.1g047100m/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: orange1.1g047100m Gene Symbol: CitERF71 Gene Name: AP2/ERF transcription factor 71 Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: Among cloned members of the AP2/ERF transcription factor gene family, CitERF71 showed a similar expression pattern to CitTPS16.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CitTPS16</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrus-sinensis/cs7g17670.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrus-sinensis/cs7g17670.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cs7g17670.1 Gene Symbol: CitTPS16 Gene Name: terpene synthase16 Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: Transcription factor CitERF71 activates the terpene synthase gene CitTPS16 involved in the synthesis of E-geraniol in sweet orange fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsACD2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csacd2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csacd2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs1g22670 Gene Symbol: CsACD2 Gene Name: Genome: Citrus sinensis Valencia genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsAP2-09</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/csap2-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/csap2-09/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsAP2-09 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: Demonstrated that overexpression of an Xcc-inducible apetala 2/ethylene response factor encoded by Citrus sinensis, CsAP2-09, enhances CBC resistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsATG8c</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csatg8c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csatg8c/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs4g10210 Gene Symbol: CsATG8c Gene Name: Genome: Citrus sinensis Valencia genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsbHLH18</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/orange1.1g024930m/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/orange1.1g024930m/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: orange1.1g024930m Gene Symbol: CsbHLH18 Gene Name: basic helix–loop–helix transcription factor 18 Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: The transcription factor CsbHLH18 of sweet orange functions in modulation of cold tolerance and homeostasis of reactive oxygen species by regulating the antioxidant gene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsBZIP40</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs8g15030/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs8g15030/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cs8g15030 Gene Symbol: CsBZIP40 Gene Name: Genome: CPBD platform (http://citrus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsbZIP44</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csbzip44/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csbzip44/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs3g25230 Gene Symbol: CsbZIP44 Gene Name: Genome: Reference genome of sweet orange Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsbZIP44 is essential for ABA-mediated carotenoid biosynthesis in citrus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsCAD</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/cscad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/cscad/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs1g20590 Gene Symbol: CsCAD Gene Name: Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: The transcript levels of lignin biosynthetic genes, namely, hydroxycinnamoyl transferase (CsHCT, CAP ID: Cs1g14450), cinnamyl alcohol dehydrogenase (CsCAD, CAP ID: Cs1g20590) and caffeoyl-CoA O-methyltransferase (CsCCoAOMT, CAP ID: Cs4g13430), were elevated in the leaves of the transgenic lines after mock inoculation and Xcc infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsCAF1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cscaf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cscaf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsCAF1 Gene Name: carbon catabolite repressor 4 (CCR4)-associated factor 1 Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: Role of the Citrus sinensis RNA deadenylase CsCAF1 in citrus canker resistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsCBF1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/cscbf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/cscbf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs5g10240 Gene Symbol: CsCBF1 Gene Name: Genome: Citrus sinensis Valencia genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsCCoAOMT</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csccoaomt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csccoaomt/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs4g13430 Gene Symbol: CsCCoAOMT Gene Name: Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: The transcript levels of lignin biosynthetic genes, namely, hydroxycinnamoyl transferase (CsHCT, CAP ID: Cs1g14450), cinnamyl alcohol dehydrogenase (CsCAD, CAP ID: Cs1g20590) and caffeoyl-CoA O-methyltransferase (CsCCoAOMT, CAP ID: Cs4g13430), were elevated in the leaves of the transgenic lines after mock inoculation and Xcc infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsCCoAOMT1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrus-sinensis/cs8g05410/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrus-sinensis/cs8g05410/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cs8g05410 Gene Symbol: CsCCoAOMT1 Gene Name: caffeoyl-CoA O-methyltransferase 1 Genome: Citrus sinensis reference genome Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: A multifunctional true caffeoyl coenzyme A O-methyltransferase (CsCCoAOMT1) enzyme participates in the biosynthesis of polymethoxylated flavones in citrus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsDUO1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrus-sinensis/cs1g03470/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrus-sinensis/cs1g03470/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cs1g03470 Gene Symbol: CsDUO1 Gene Name: DUO POLLEN 1 Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: The miR159a-DUO1 module regulates pollen development by modulating auxin biosynthesis and starch metabolism in citrus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsELT1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/cselt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/cselt1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs3g11690 Gene Symbol: CsELT1 Gene Name: Esterase/lipase/thioesterase 1 Genome: sweet orange (Citrus sinensis) reference genome Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsELT1 promotes the accumulation of β-chain carotenoids in plastid globules by forming a fat-soluble environment rich in triacylglycerol (TGA).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsERF061</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cserf061/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cserf061/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsERF061 Gene Name: group I ethylene response factor 61 Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: Ethylene activation of carotenoid biosynthesis by a novel transcription factor CsERF061.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsHB5</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/cshb5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/cshb5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs3g17870 Gene Symbol: CsHB5 Gene Name: Genome: Reference genome of sweet orange Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsHB5, a positive regulator of ABA and carotenoid-driven processes, activates the expression of CsbZIP44 by binding to its promoter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsHCT</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/cshct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/cshct/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs1g14450 Gene Symbol: CsHCT Gene Name: Genome: Reference genome of sweet orange Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsHCT,lignin biosynthetic genes, namely, hydroxycinnamoyl transferase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsiLAC17</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs8g17630.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs8g17630.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cs8g17630.1 Gene Symbol: CsiLAC17 Gene Name: Citrus LACCASE-17 Genome: Orange Genomic Database Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsiLAC4 and CsiLAC17 are predominantly localized in the apoplast of tobacco epidermal cells.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsiLAC4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs6g07800.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs6g07800.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cs6g07800.1 Gene Symbol: CsiLAC4 Gene Name: Citrus LACCASE-4 Genome: Orange Genomic Database Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsiLAC4’s role in xylem lignification was determined by mRNA hybridization and cytochemistry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsKCS20</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/cskcs20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/cskcs20/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs9g07970.1 Gene Symbol: CsKCS20 Gene Name: Genome: Reference genome of sweet orange Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: Function and transcriptional regulation of CsKCS20 in the elongation of very-long-chain fatty acids and wax biosynthesis in Citrus sinensis flavedo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsLOB1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs7g27640/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs7g27640/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cs7g27640 Gene Symbol: CsLOB1 Gene Name: Citrus sinensis lateral organ boundary 1 Genome: C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsMADS3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csmads3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csmads3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs7g10980.3 Gene Symbol: CsMADS3 Gene Name: MADS-box transcription factor 3 Genome: Citrus sinensis Valencia genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsMADS5</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/csmads5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/csmads5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsMADS5 Gene Name: FRUITFULL sub-clade MADS 5 Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: A fruit ripening-associated transcription factor CsMADS5 positively regulates carotenoid biosynthesis in citrus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsMADS6</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csmads6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csmads6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: CsMADS6 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: The Citrus Transcription Factor CsMADS6 Modulates Carotenoid Metabolism by Directly Regulating Carotenogenic Genes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsMPK6</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csmpk6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csmpk6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: CsMPK6 Gene Name: Genome: Citrus sinensis cv.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsMYB3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/csmyb3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/csmyb3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsMYB3 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsMYB3 and CsRuby1 form an ‘Activator-and-Repressor’ Loop for the Regulation of Anthocyanin Biosynthesis in Citrus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsMYB77</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csmyb77/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csmyb77/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs3g23950 Gene Symbol: CsMYB77 Gene Name: MYB77 transcription factor Genome: Citrus Pan-genome to Breeding Database Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: The expression of PIN5 was activated by CsMYB77, which promoted free indole-3-acetic acid decline and modulated auxin signaling in the fruits of transgenic Hongkong kumquat lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsMYB96</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs5g10670.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs5g10670.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cs5g10670.1 Gene Symbol: CsMYB96 Gene Name: R2R3 MYB transcription factor 96 Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsMYB96 confers resistance to water loss in citrus fruit by simultaneous regulation of water transport and wax biosynthesis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsMYC2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csmyc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csmyc2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Ciclev10019730m Gene Symbol: CsMYC2 Gene Name: Genome: Citrus sinensis cv.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsPH4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csph4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csph4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs9g03070 Gene Symbol: CsPH4 Gene Name: Proanthocyanidin4 Genome: Citrus sinensis Valencia genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsPHL3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs2g01480.1-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs2g01480.1-/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cs2g01480.1 Gene Symbol: CsPHL3 Gene Name: Citrus Phosphate Starvation Response Factor 3 Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsPHL3 could directly represses the expression of PSY, thus resulting in a reduction of carotenoid contents, which may release less amounts of SLs and ultimately suppress Pi signaling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsPHT4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs6g07670/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs6g07670/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cs6g07670 Gene Symbol: CsPHT4|2 Gene Name: plastid-type phosphate transporter 4|2 Genome: citrus genome database (http://citrus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsPLDα1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cspld%CE%B11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cspld%CE%B11/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsPLDα1 Gene Name: phospholipase D alpha Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsPLDα1 and CsPLDγ1 are differentially induced during leaf and fruit abscission and diurnally regulated in Citrus sinensis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsPLDγ1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cspld%CE%B31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cspld%CE%B31/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsPLDγ1 Gene Name: phospholipase D gamma Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsPLDα1 and CsPLDγ1 are differentially induced during leaf and fruit abscission and diurnally regulated in Citrus sinensis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsPrx25</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csprx25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csprx25/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: CsPrx25 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsPrx25, a class III peroxidase in Citrus sinensis, confers resistance to citrus bacterial canker through the maintenance of ROS homeostasis and cell wall lignification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsPrx53</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs7g_pb023540/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs7g_pb023540/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cs7g_pb023540 Gene Symbol: CsPrx53 Gene Name: Genome: CPBD platform (http://citrus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsRBOH2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/csrboh2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/csrboh2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsRBOH2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: Plants overexpressing CsWRKY25 were more resistant to CBC and showed higher expression of the respiratory burst oxidase homolog (RBOH) CsRBOH2, in addition to exhibiting increased RBOH activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsRuby1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csruby1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csruby1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: CsRuby1 Gene Name: Citrus sinensis Ruby1 Genome: Citrus sinensis Valencia genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSCL2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/ciclev10019083m/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/ciclev10019083m/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ciclev10019083m , CsUn_pb052510 Gene Symbol: CsSCL2 Gene Name: SCARECROW-LIKE 2 Genome: database Orange Genome annotation project Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: Identified 2 csi-miR171c–targeted SCARECROW-LIKE genes CsSCL2 and CsSCL3 (CsSCL2/3), which exert positive feedback regulation on csi-miR171c expression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSCL3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/ciclev10019094m/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/ciclev10019094m/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ciclev10019094m , CsUn_pb052500 Gene Symbol: CsSCL3 Gene Name: SCARECROW-LIKE 3 Genome: database Orange Genome annotation project Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: Identified 2 csi-miR171c–targeted SCARECROW-LIKE genes CsSCL2 and CsSCL3 (CsSCL2/3), which exert positive feedback regulation on csi-miR171c expression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSGRa</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrus-sinensis/cs5g10040/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrus-sinensis/cs5g10040/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cs5g10040 Gene Symbol: CsSGRa Gene Name: STAY-GREEN Genome: C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSGRb</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrus-sinensis/cs3g20450/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrus-sinensis/cs3g20450/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cs3g20450 Gene Symbol: CsSGRb Gene Name: STAY-GREEN Genome: C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSOD13</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs8g_pb021190/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs8g_pb021190/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cs8g_pb021190 Gene Symbol: CsSOD13 Gene Name: Genome: CPBD platform (http://citrus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsTIP2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/orange1.1g023108/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/orange1.1g023108/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: orange1.1g023108 Gene Symbol: CsTIP2|1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: Expression of the citrus CsTIP2|1|CsTIP2|1 gene improves tobacco plant growth, antioxidant capacity and physiological adaptation under stress conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsTPS1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cstps1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cstps1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsTPS1 Gene Name: terpene synthase1 Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: The role and function of CitAP2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsTT8</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs5g31400/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs5g31400/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cs5g31400 Gene Symbol: CsTT8 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsTT8 regulates anthocyanin accumulation in blood orange through alternative splicing transcription.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsUBC24</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csubc24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csubc24/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs2g06030 Gene Symbol: CsUBC24 Gene Name: Genome: Citrus sinensis Valencia genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsWAKL08</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs9g14540/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs9g14540/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cs9g14540 Gene Symbol: CsWAKL08 Gene Name: Wall-associated receptor-like kinase 8 Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsWAKL08, a pathogen-induced wall-associated receptor-like kinase in sweet orange, confers resistance to citrus bacterial canker via ROS control and JA signaling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsWRKY25</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cswrky25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cswrky25/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsWRKY25 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: Plants overexpressing CsWRKY25 were more resistant to CBC and showed higher expression of the respiratory burst oxidase homolog (RBOH) CsRBOH2, in addition to exhibiting increased RBOH activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsWRKY43</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs9g03310/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs9g03310/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cs9g03310 Gene Symbol: CsWRKY43 Gene Name: Genome: CPBD platform (http://citrus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsWRKY70</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/cswrky70/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/cswrky70/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: CsWRKY70 Gene Name: Genome: C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Csβ-LCY1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs%CE%B2-lcy1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs%CE%B2-lcy1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: Csβ-LCY1 Gene Name: beta-cyclase1 Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: The β-cyclization of lycopene, catalysed by the lycopene β-cyclases (β-LCY), seems to be a key regulatory step of the carotenoid pathway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Csβ-LCY2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs%CE%B2-lcy2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs%CE%B2-lcy2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: Csβ-LCY2 Gene Name: beta-cyclase2 Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: The β-cyclization of lycopene, catalysed by the lycopene β-cyclases (β-LCY), seems to be a key regulatory step of the carotenoid pathway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noemi</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/noemi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/noemi/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs5g31400 Gene Symbol: Noemi Gene Name: bHLH protein Genome: Citrus sinensis Valencia genome v1.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
