<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Petunia Hybrida on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/petunia-hybrida/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Petunia Hybrida on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/petunia-hybrida/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AN2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/an2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/an2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: AN2 Gene Name: ANTHOCYANIN2 Genome: Species: Petunia hybrida Functional Descriptions: The anthocyanin biosynthesis pathway was strongly downregulated in star petals, including its major regulator ANTHOCYANIN2 (AN2).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAM1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/pam1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/pam1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PAM1 Gene Name: penetration and arbuscule morphogenesis 1 Genome: Species: Petunia hybrida Functional Descriptions: We have previously identified a mutant in Petunia hybrida, penetration and arbuscule morphogenesis 1 (PAM1), that is defective in the intracellular stages of AM development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhACO1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/phaco1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/phaco1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PhACO1 Gene Name: 1-aminocyclopropane-1-carboxylate oxidase1 Genome: Species: Petunia hybrida Functional Descriptions: PhACO1 was subsequently edited using the CRISPR/Cas9 system, and its role in ethylene production was investigated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhBPBT</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/petunia-hybrida/phbpbt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/petunia-hybrida/phbpbt/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PhBPBT Gene Name: benzoyl CoA:benzyl alcohol/phenylethanol benzoyltransferase Genome: Species: Petunia hybrida Functional Descriptions: Tissue-specific PhBPBT expression is differentially regulated in response to endogenous ethylene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhCCoAOMT1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/phccoaomt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/phccoaomt1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PhCCoAOMT1 Gene Name: caffeoyl-coenzyme A O-methyltransferase 1 Genome: Species: Petunia hybrida Functional Descriptions: Cloned and characterized a caffeoyl-coenzyme A O-methyltransferase (PhCCoAOMT1) from the petals of the fragrant petunia ‘Mitchell’.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhDEF</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/phdef/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/phdef/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PhDEF Gene Name: PhDEFICIENS Genome: Species: Petunia hybrida Functional Descriptions: Cell layer–specific expression of the homeotic MADS-box transcription factor PhDEF contributes to modular petal morphogenesis in petunia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhERF2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/pherf2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/pherf2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PhERF2 Gene Name: ethylene-responsive-element-binding factor 2 Genome: Species: Petunia hybrida Functional Descriptions: A petunia ethylene-responsive element binding factor, PhERF2, plays an important role in antiviral RNA silencing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhERS1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/phers1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/phers1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PhERS1 Gene Name: ethylene receptor1 Genome: Species: Petunia hybrida Functional Descriptions: Characterization of two ethylene receptors PhERS1 and PhETR2 from petunia: PhETR2 regulates timing of anther dehiscence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhERS2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/phers2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/phers2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PhERS2 Gene Name: ethylene receptor2 Genome: Species: Petunia hybrida Functional Descriptions: Characterization of two ethylene receptors PhERS1 and PhETR2 from petunia: PhETR2 regulates timing of anther dehiscence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhGRL2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/phgrl2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/phgrl2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PhGRL2 Gene Name: Green-ripe like protein 2 Genome: Species: Petunia hybrida Functional Descriptions: PhGRL2 Protein, Interacting with PhACO1, Is Involved in Flower Senescence in the Petunia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhOBF1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/peaxi162scf00285g00011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/peaxi162scf00285g00011/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Peaxi162Scf00285g00011 Gene Symbol: PhOBF1 Gene Name: Genome: Sol Genomics Network (https://solgenomics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhPT1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/phpt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/petunia-hybrida/phpt1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PhPT1|PhPht1|1 Gene Name: phosphate transporter1 Genome: Species: Petunia hybrida Functional Descriptions: Ethylene regulates phosphorus remobilization and expression of a phosphate transporter (PhPT1|PhPht1|1) during petunia corolla senescence.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
