<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ipomoea Batatas on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/ipomoea-batatas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ipomoea Batatas on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/ipomoea-batatas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IbBBX24</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/ipomoea_batatas/ibbbx24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/ipomoea_batatas/ibbbx24/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: IbBBX24 Gene Name: Genome: http://sweetpotato-garden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbBBX29</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/ipomoea_batatas/ibbbx29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/ipomoea_batatas/ibbbx29/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: IbBBX29 Gene Name: Genome: Taizhong 6 genome Species: Ipomoea batatas Functional Description: IbBBX29 plays a pivotal role in regulating IAA-mediated leaf development and flavonoid biosynthesis in sweet potato and Arabidopsis, providing a candidate gene for flavonoid biofortification in plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbEXP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/ibexp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/ibexp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: IbEXP1 Gene Name: expansin gene Genome: Species: Ipomoea batatas Functional Descriptions: The expressions of IbEXP1, IbEXP2 and IbEXPL1 were significantly correlated with the changes in cell wall component content, and were related to the qualitative structure changes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbLEA14</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/iblea14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/iblea14/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: IbLEA14 Gene Name: Late embryogenesis abundant 14 Genome: Species: Ipomoea batatas Functional Descriptions: Sweetpotato late embryogenesis abundant 14 (IbLEA14) gene influences lignification and increases osmotic- and salt stress-tolerance of transgenic calli.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbMYB1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/ibmyb1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/ibmyb1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: IbMYB1 Gene Name: MYB domain protein 1 Genome: Species: Ipomoea batatas Functional Descriptions: Interaction of small RNA–8105 and the intron of IbMYB1 RNA regulates IbMYB1 family genes through secondary siRNAs and DNA methylation after wounding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbMYB73</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/ipomoea_batatas/ibmyb73/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/ipomoea_batatas/ibmyb73/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;itb01g33150.t1 Gene Symbol: IbMYB73 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Ipomoea batatas Functional Description: IbMYB73 targets abscisic acid-responsive IbGER5 to regulate root growth and stress tolerance in sweet potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbNAC087</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/itr_sc000462.1_g00010.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/itr_sc000462.1_g00010.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Itr_sc000462.1_g00010.1 Gene Symbol: IbNAC087 Gene Name: Genome: Sweetpotato GARDEN (Sweetpotato Genome and Resource Database ENtry) (http://sweetpotato-garden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbNAC1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/ibnac1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/ibnac1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: IbNAC1 Gene Name: NAC transcription factor 1 Genome: Species: Ipomoea batatas Functional Descriptions: IbNAC1 was constitutively expressed in root tissues and was induced earlier than sporamin following the wounding of leaves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbNAC29</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/itf01g25900.t1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/itf01g25900.t1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: itf01g25900.t1 Gene Symbol: IbNAC29 Gene Name: Genome: Sweet Potato Genomics Resource database (http://sweetpotato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbNIEL</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/itr_sc000449.1_g00025.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/itr_sc000449.1_g00025.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Itr_sc000449.1_g00025.1 Gene Symbol: IbNIEL Gene Name: NAC087-INTERACTING E3 LIGASE Genome: Sweetpotato GARDEN (Sweetpotato Genome and Resource Database ENtry) (http://sweetpotato-garden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbPAL1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/ipomoea-batatas/ibpal1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/ipomoea-batatas/ibpal1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: IbPAL1 Gene Name: phenylalanine ammonia lyase Genome: Species: Ipomoea batatas Functional Descriptions: Overexpression of IbPAL1 promotes chlorogenic acid biosynthesis in sweetpotato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbpreproHypSys</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/ibpreprohypsys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/ibpreprohypsys/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: IbpreproHypSys Gene Name: hydroxyproline-rich preprosystemin Genome: Species: Ipomoea batatas Functional Descriptions: The expression of IbpreproHypSys, encoding the precursor of IbHypSys, was induced in sweet potato (Ipomoea batatas cv.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbSnRK1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/ibsnrk1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/ibsnrk1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: IbSnRK1 Gene Name: sucrose non-fermenting-1-related protein kinase-1 Genome: Species: Ipomoea batatas Functional Descriptions: These findings indicate that IbSnRK1 improves starch content and quality through systematical up-regulation of the genes and the increase in key enzyme activities involved in starch biosynthesis pathway in transgenic sweet potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbSnRK1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/ipomoea_batatas/ibsnrk1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/ipomoea_batatas/ibsnrk1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: IbSnRK1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Ipomoea batatas Functional Description: These results show that the IbSnRK1 gene confers salt, drought, and cold tolerance in sweet potato by activating the ROS scavenging system and controlling stomatal closure via the ABA signaling pathway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbVP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/ibvp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/ipomoea-batatas/ibvp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: IbVP1 Gene Name: H+-pyrophosphatase 1 Genome: Species: Ipomoea batatas Functional Descriptions: H+-pyrophosphatase IbVP1 promotes efficient iron use in sweet potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbVP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/ipomoea_batatas/ibvp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/ipomoea_batatas/ibvp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: IbVP1 Gene Name: pyrophosphate-energized vacuolar membrane proteon pump 1 Genome: Taizhong 6 genome Species: Ipomoea batatas Functional Description: Our study shows that the IbVP1 gene plays an important role in regulating starch metabolism in sweet potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IibC3H18</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/ipomoea_batatas/iibc3h18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/ipomoea_batatas/iibc3h18/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: IibC3H18 Gene Name: Genome: Taizhong 6 genome Species: Ipomoea batatas Functional Description: our data indicate that IbC3H18 functions in enhancing abiotic stress tolerance in sweet potato, which may serve as a candidate gene for use in improving abiotic stress resistance in crops.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
