<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Medicago Truncatula on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/medicago-truncatula/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Medicago Truncatula on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/medicago-truncatula/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DIB1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/dib1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/dib1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Medtr2g102570 Gene Symbol: DIB1 Gene Name: dwarf and increased branching 1 Genome: M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EAN1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/ean1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/ean1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Medtr4g094762 Gene Symbol: EAN1 Gene Name: Medicago truncatula empty anther1 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: We characterized the male-sterile mutant empty anther1 (EAN1) and identified EAN1 as a tapetum-specific bHLH transcription factor necessary for tapetum degeneration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EIN2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr7g101410/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr7g101410/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr7g101410 Gene Symbol: EIN2 Gene Name: ETHYLENE INSENSITIVE2 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Consistent with this observation, the EIN2 mutation rescues the previously described effects of ethylene overproduction in mature phytochrome-deficient plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtABCG10</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtabcg10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtabcg10/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtABCG10 Gene Name: ATP-binding cassette G subfamily Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: The experiments described here demonstrated that the level of Medicago truncatula ABCG10 (MtABCG10) mRNA was elevated following application of fungal oligosaccharides to plant roots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtAHL1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr4g098450/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr4g098450/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr4g098450 Gene Symbol: MtAHL1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Whereas mutation of NCR169 arrested bacteroid development at a late stage, the absence of MtAHL1 or MtAHL2 completely blocked bacteroid differentiation indicating that they also regulate other NCR genes required for the development of nitrogen-fixing nodules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtAHL2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr7g080980/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr7g080980/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr7g080980 Gene Symbol: MtAHL2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Whereas mutation of NCR169 arrested bacteroid development at a late stage, the absence of MtAHL1 or MtAHL2 completely blocked bacteroid differentiation indicating that they also regulate other NCR genes required for the development of nitrogen-fixing nodules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtbHLH1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtbhlh1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtbhlh1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtbHLH1 Gene Name: basic helix loop helix 1 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: MtbHLH1, a bHLH transcription factor involved in Medicago truncatula nodule vascular patterning and nodule to plant metabolic exchanges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtCCD1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtccd1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtccd1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtCCD1 Gene Name: carotenoid cleavage dioxygenase 1 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: RNA Interference-Mediated Repression of MtCCD1 in Mycorrhizal Roots of Medicago truncatula Causes Accumulation of C27 Apocarotenoids, Shedding Light on the Functional Role of CCD1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtCcs52A</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17_chr4g0057131/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17_chr4g0057131/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MtrunA17_Chr4g0057131 Gene Symbol: MtCcs52A Gene Name: B-type cell cycle switch protein ccs52A Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: The MtCcs52A and MtCcs52B proteins represent two subgroups of the Cdh1-type activators, which display differences in their cell cycle regulation, structure, and function.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtCcs52B</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17_chr3g0111961/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17_chr3g0111961/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MtrunA17_Chr3g0111961 Gene Symbol: MtCcs52B Gene Name: B-type cell cycle switch protein ccs52B Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: The MtCcs52A and MtCcs52B proteins represent two subgroups of the Cdh1-type activators, which display differences in their cell cycle regulation, structure, and function.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtCEP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17_chr8g0374821/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17_chr8g0374821/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MtrunA17_Chr8g0374821 Gene Symbol: MtCEP1 Gene Name: Medicago truncatula CEP1 Genome: Jemalong A17 Mt5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtCIPK12</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr8g086380/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr8g086380/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr8g086380 Gene Symbol: MtCIPK12 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Protein kinase MtCIPK12 modulates iron reduction in Medicago truncatula by regulating riboflavin biosynthesis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtCLE12</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr4g079630/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr4g079630/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr4g079630 Gene Symbol: MtCLE12 Gene Name: CLAVATA3/ESR (CLE)-related protein 12 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Root growth inhibition was detected when MtCLE12 was ectopically expressed in wild-type roots or synthetic CLE12 peptide was applied exogenously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtCML42</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/mtcml42/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/mtcml42/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MtCML42 Gene Name: Genome: M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtCOPT1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr4g019870/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr4g019870/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr4g019870 Gene Symbol: MtCOPT1 Gene Name: COPT transporter 1 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Medicago truncatula copper transporter 1 (MtCOPT1) delivers copper for symbiotic nitrogen fixation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtCRE1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17chr8g0392301/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17chr8g0392301/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MtrunA17Chr8g0392301 Gene Symbol: MtCRE1 Gene Name: Cytokinin Response Element 1 Genome: M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtDMI2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr5g030920/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr5g030920/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr5g030920 Gene Symbol: MtDMI2 Gene Name: DOES NOT MAKE INFECTION 2 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: The MtDMI2-MtPUB2 Negative Feedback Loop Plays a Role in Nodulation Homeostasis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtEFD</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17_chr4g0002631/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17_chr4g0002631/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MtrunA17_Chr4g0002631 Gene Symbol: MtEFD Gene Name: Ethylene response Factor required for nodule Differentiation Genome: Mt5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtEFD</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17_chr4g0002631mt0064_00055/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17_chr4g0002631mt0064_00055/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MtrunA17_Chr4g0002631;MT0064_00055 Gene Symbol: MtEFD Gene Name: Genome: Mt5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtEFD2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17_chr3g0137174/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17_chr3g0137174/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MtrunA17_Chr3g0137174 Gene Symbol: MtEFD2 Gene Name: ETHYLENE RESPONSE FACTOR REQUIRED FOR NODULE DIFFERENTIATION 2 Genome: Mt5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtERF1-1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mterf1-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mterf1-1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtERF1-1 Gene Name: B-3 Ethylene Response Factor Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: The B-3 Ethylene Response Factor MtERF1-1 Mediates Resistance to a Subset of Root Pathogens in Medicago truncatula without Adversely Affecting Symbiosis with Rhizobia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtERF74</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr2g105380/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr2g105380/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr2g105380 Gene Symbol: MtERF74 Gene Name: Medicago truncatula ERF-VII TF 74 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Group VII ethylene response factors, MtERF74 and MtERF75, sustain nitrogen fixation in Medicago truncatula microoxic nodules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtERF75</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr8g022820/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr8g022820/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr8g022820 Gene Symbol: MtERF75 Gene Name: Medicago truncatula ERF-VII TF 75 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Group VII ethylene response factors, MtERF74 and MtERF75, sustain nitrogen fixation in Medicago truncatula microoxic nodules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtKIX8</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/medicago-truncatula/mtkix8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/medicago-truncatula/mtkix8/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtKIX8 Gene Name: KINASE-INDUCIBLE DOMAIN INTERACTING 8 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: KINASE-INDUCIBLE DOMAIN INTERACTING 8 (MtKIX8) regulates helical pod morphology in Medicago truncatula.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtKNOX2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/medicago-truncatula/medtr2g024390/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/medicago-truncatula/medtr2g024390/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr2g024390 Gene Symbol: MtKNOX2 Gene Name: Class I KNOTTED-like homeobox Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Phylogenetic analysis revealed that the STM-like genes (MtKNOX1 and MtKNOX6), a BP-like gene (MtKNOX2), and a KNAT2/6-like gene (MtKNOX7) are grouped into Class I KNOX genes (MtKNOXI) in M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtKNOX4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtknox4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtknox4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtKNOX4 Gene Name: class II KNOTTED-LIKE HOMEOBOX transcription factor Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: MtKNOX4-regulated MtKCS12 manifests hardseededness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtKNOX6</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/medicago-truncatula/medtr5g085860/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/medicago-truncatula/medtr5g085860/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr5g085860 Gene Symbol: MtKNOX6 Gene Name: Class I KNOTTED-like homeobox Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Phylogenetic analysis revealed that the STM-like genes (MtKNOX1 and MtKNOX6), a BP-like gene (MtKNOX2), and a KNAT2/6-like gene (MtKNOX7) are grouped into Class I KNOX genes (MtKNOXI) in M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtLHY</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/mtlhy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/mtlhy/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MtLHY Gene Name: Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: These data shed new light on the roles of MtLHY in the orchestration of circadian oscillator in nodules and shoots, which provides a mechanistic link between nodulation, nitrogen assimilation, and clock function.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtLMI1a</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/mtlmi1a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/mtlmi1a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Medtr1g061660 Gene Symbol: MtLMI1a Gene Name: Genome: M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtLMI1b</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/mtlmi1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/mtlmi1b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Medtr7g103340 Gene Symbol: MtLMI1b Gene Name: Genome: M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtLUX</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/mtlux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/mtlux/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MtLUX Gene Name: Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: In vivo and in vitro experiments showed that MtLUX directly binds to a cis-element in the promoter of MtTB1/MtTCP1A, suggesting that MtLUX regulates branching by rhythmically suppressing MtTB1/MtTCP1A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtMIF3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtr_4g127360/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtr_4g127360/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MTR_4g127360 Gene Symbol: MtMIF3 Gene Name: Macrophage migration inhibitory factor 3 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Macrophage migration inhibitory factor MtMIF3 prevents the premature aging of Medicago truncatula nodules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtMOT1.2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtmot1.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtmot1.2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtMOT1.2 Gene Name: Molybdate Transporter 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtMOT1.3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtmot1.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtmot1.3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtMOT1.3 Gene Name: Molybdate Transporter type 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtMSBP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtmsbp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtmsbp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtMSBP1 Gene Name: steroid-binding protein 1 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Membrane steroid-binding protein 1 (MtMSBP1) induced by a diffusible fungal signal is critical for mycorrhization in Medicago truncatula Three of them were previously shown to be mycorrhiza induced at later stages of the symbiosis, while MtMSBP1, encoding a membrane-bound steroid-binding protein, is a novel mycorrhizal marker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtNAC80</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/medicago-truncatula/mtnac80/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/medicago-truncatula/mtnac80/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtNAC80 Gene Name: NAC domain-containing protein 80 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: The S-acylation cycle of transcription factor MtNAC80 influences cold stress responses in Medicago truncatula.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtNAC969</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtnac969/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtnac969/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtNAC969 Gene Name: NAC969 transcription factor Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Over-expression of one of these transcription factors, MtNAC969, induced formation of a shorter and less-branched root system, whereas RNAi-mediated MtNAC969 inactivation promoted lateral root formation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtNAM</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtnam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtnam/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtNAM Gene Name: NO APICAL MERISTEM Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: NO APICAL MERISTEM (MtNAM) regulates floral organ identity and lateral organ separation in Medicago truncatula.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtNFH1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr4g116990.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr4g116990.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr4g116990.1 Gene Symbol: MtNFH1|MtChit5 Gene Name: NOD FACTOR HYDROLASE1 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Role of the Nod Factor Hydrolase MtNFH1|MtChit5 in Regulating Nod Factor Levels during Rhizobial Infection and in Mature Nodules of Medicago truncatula.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtNOOT1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr7g090020.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr7g090020.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr7g090020.1 Gene Symbol: MtNOOT1 Gene Name: NODULE ROOT1 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: The Medicago truncatula nodule identity gene MtNOOT1 is required for coordinated apical-basal development of the root.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtNOOT1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr7g090020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr7g090020/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr7g090020 Gene Symbol: MtNOOT1 Gene Name: NODULE ROOT1 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: The Medicago truncatula nodule identity gene MtNOOT1 is required for coordinated apical-basal development of the root.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtNRT1.3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr5g093170.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr5g093170.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr5g093170.1 Gene Symbol: MtNRT1.3 Gene Name: nitrate transporter NRT1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtNRT2.1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/mtnrt2.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/mtnrt2.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MtrunA17_Chr4g0028551.1 Gene Symbol: MtNRT2.1 Gene Name: Genome: M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtPI</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtpi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtpi/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtPI Gene Name: PISTILLATA Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: The B-class gene PISTILLATA (PI) codes for a MADS-box transcription factor required for floral organ identity in angiosperms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtPLP</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtplp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtplp/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtPLP Gene Name: PETIOLULE-LIKE PULVINUS Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Identification and characterization of petiolule- like pulvinus (MsPLP) mutants with abolished nyctinastic leaf movement in the model legume Medicago truncatula.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtPUB2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtpub2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtpub2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtPUB2 Gene Name: U-box (PUB)–type E3 ligase 2 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: The MtDMI2-MtPUB2 Negative Feedback Loop Plays a Role in Nodulation Homeostasis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtRac1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr6g087980/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr6g087980/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr6g087980 Gene Symbol: MtRac1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Here, we found that small GTPases (MtRac1/MtROP9 and its homologs) are required for root hair development and rhizobial infection in Medicago truncatula.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtRbohE</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr8g095520.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr8g095520.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr8g095520.1 Gene Symbol: MtRbohE Gene Name: respiratory burst oxidase homolog protein E Genome: Mt4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtREV1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr2g094520/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr2g094520/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr2g094520 Gene Symbol: MtREV1|PPF1 Gene Name: REVOLUTA1 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Detailed characterization revealed that a lesion in a HD-ZIPIII gene, REVOLUTA (MtREV1|PPF1), resulted in the defects of the mutant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtROP9</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtrop9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtrop9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtROP9 Gene Name: small G-protein ROP9 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Silencing of the Rac1 GTPase MtROP9 in Medicago truncatula Stimulates Early Mycorrhizal and Oomycete Root Colonizations But Negatively Affects Rhizobial Infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtRopGEF2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr8g030850/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr8g030850/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr8g030850 Gene Symbol: MtRopGEF2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Phosphorylation of MtRopGEF2 by LYK3 mediates MtROP activity to regulate rhizobial infection in Medicago truncatula.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtSERF1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/medicago-truncatula/mtserf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/medicago-truncatula/mtserf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtSERF1 Gene Name: SOMATIC EMBRYO RELATED FACTOR1 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: The transcription factor MtSERF1 of the ERF subfamily identified by transcriptional profiling is required for somatic embryogenesis induced by auxin plus cytokinin in Medicago truncatula.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtST1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr4g069810/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr4g069810/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr4g069810 Gene Symbol: MtST1 Gene Name: Specific Tissue 1 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Three members of Medicago truncatula ST family are ubiquitous during development and modulated by nutritional status (MtST1) and dehydration (MtST2 and MtST3).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtST2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr3g116440/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr3g116440/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr3g116440 Gene Symbol: MtST2 Gene Name: Specific Tissue 2 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Three members of Medicago truncatula ST family are ubiquitous during development and modulated by nutritional status (MtST1) and dehydration (MtST2 and MtST3).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtST3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr3g116430/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr3g116430/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr3g116430 Gene Symbol: MtST3 Gene Name: Specific Tissue 3 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Three members of Medicago truncatula ST family are ubiquitous during development and modulated by nutritional status (MtST1) and dehydration (MtST2 and MtST3).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtSWEET1b</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr3g089125/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr3g089125/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr3g089125 Gene Symbol: MtSWEET1b Gene Name: Sugars Will Eventually be Exported Transporter 1b Genome: M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtTdp1α</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mttdp1%CE%B1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mttdp1%CE%B1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtTdp1α Gene Name: tyrosyl-DNA phosphodiesterase 1 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: An intron-spliced hairpin RNA approach was used for the targeted silencing of the MtTdp1α gene encoding the αisoform of tyrosyl-DNA phosphodiesterase 1 in Medicago truncatula Gaertn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtYSL3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr3g092090/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr3g092090/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr3g092090 Gene Symbol: MtYSL3 Gene Name: Medicago truncatula Yellow Stripe1-Like3 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: MtYSL3 is a plasma membrane protein expressed by vascular cells in roots and nodules and by cortical nodule cells.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtYSL7</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr3g063490/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr3g063490/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr3g063490 Gene Symbol: MtYSL7 Gene Name: Genome: M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtZIP14</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr6g007687/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr6g007687/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr6g007687 Gene Symbol: MtZIP14 Gene Name: Zn-regulated iron-regulated transporter-like protein 14 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Suggesting that increased colonization by the AM fungus is associated with increased expression of MtZIP14 The putative Zn transporter gene MtZIP14 was markedly up-regulated in M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtZPT2-2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtr_1g106730/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtr_1g106730/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MTR_1g106730 Gene Symbol: MtZPT2-2 Gene Name: C2H2 type ZFP Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: The objectives of this study were to investigate the role of MtZPT2-2 from R108 in regulating salt tolerance using overexpressing lines and gene-edited mutants and the underlying mechanisms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtZR1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtzr1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtzr1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtZR1 Gene Name: PRAF family Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: MtZR1, a PRAF protein, is involved in the development of roots and symbiotic root nodules in Medicago truncatula.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NCR169</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr7g029760/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr7g029760/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr7g029760 Gene Symbol: NCR169 Gene Name: nodule-specific cysteine-rich 169 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Widely conserved AHL transcription factors are essential for NCR gene (NCR169) expression and nodule development in Medicago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NPF7.6</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/npf7.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/npf7.6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Mtr.27727.1 Gene Symbol: NPF7.6 Gene Name: Genome: JCVI Mt 4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RH1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/rh1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/rh1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: RH1 Gene Name: RED HEART1 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Our findings reveal the molecular mechanism of the antagonistic gene paralogs RH1 and RH2 in determining anthocyanin leaf markings in M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RH2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/rh2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/rh2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: RH2 Gene Name: RED HEART2 Genome: Medicago genome sequences MtrunA17r5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ST6</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr3g107810/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr3g107810/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr3g107810 Gene Symbol: ST6 Gene Name: Specific tissue protein 6 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Specific tissue proteins 1 and 6 are involved in root biology during normal development and under symbiotic and pathogenic interactions in Medicago truncatula.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
