<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Flavonol on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/tags/flavonol/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Flavonol on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/tags/flavonol/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AaYABBY5</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aayabby5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aayabby5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: AaYABBY5 Gene Name: YABBY family transcription factor 5 Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: Transcriptional regulation of flavonoid biosynthesis in Artemisia annua by AaYABBY5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaMYB39</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cicer-arietinum/camyb39/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cicer-arietinum/camyb39/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CaMYB39 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB-SG7 transcription factor Genome: Species: Cicer arietinum Functional Descriptions: The R2R3-MYB-SG7 transcription factor CaMYB39 orchestrates surface phenylpropanoid metabolism and pathogen resistance in chickpea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsbZIP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/csbzip1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/csbzip1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsbZIP1 Gene Name: bZIP transcription factor 1 Genome: Species: Camellia sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsbZIP1-CsMYB12 mediates the production of bitter-tasting flavonols in tea plants (Camellia sinensis) through a coordinated activator-repressor network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsGT45</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/crocus-sativus/csgt45/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/crocus-sativus/csgt45/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsGT45 Gene Name: flavonoid glucosyltransferase Genome: Species: Crocus sativus Functional Descriptions: Using degenerate primers designed to match the plant secondary product glucosyltransferase (PSPG) box we cloned a full length cDNA encoding CsGT45 from C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsMYB12</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/csmyb12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/csmyb12/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsMYB12 Gene Name: MYB12 protein Genome: Species: Camellia sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsbZIP1-CsMYB12 mediates the production of bitter-tasting flavonols in tea plants (Camellia sinensis) through a coordinated activator-repressor network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsUGT84J2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/tea000239/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/tea000239/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TEA000239 Gene Symbol: CsUGT84J2 Gene Name: Al-induced glycosyltransferase Genome: Species: Camellia sinensis Functional Descriptions: Found that flavonol glycoside levels in tea roots increased following Al treatment, and the Al-induced UDP glycosyltransferase CsUGT84J2 was involved in this mechanism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CtCHI1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/carthamus-tinctorius/ctchi1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/carthamus-tinctorius/ctchi1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CtCHI1 Gene Name: chalcone isomerase1 Genome: Species: Carthamus tinctorius Functional Descriptions: Overexpression of CtCHS1 Increases Accumulation of Quinochalcone in Safflower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DTX35</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/capana03g002183/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/capsicum-annuum/capana03g002183/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Capana03g002183 Gene Symbol: DTX35 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Capsicum annuum Functional Descriptions: The CabHLH1-DTX35/DFR module regulates pollen fertility by promoting flavonoid biosynthesis in Capsicum annuum L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FabHLH3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fabhlh3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fabhlh3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FabHLH3 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: FaMYB123 interacts with FabHLH3 to regulate the late steps of anthocyanin and flavonol biosynthesis during ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaMYB123</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fvh4_5g32460/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fvh4_5g32460/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: FvH4_5g32460 Gene Symbol: FaMYB123 Gene Name: R2R3 MYB transcription factor 123 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: FaMYB123 interacts with FabHLH3 to regulate the late steps of anthocyanin and flavonol biosynthesis during ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtMATE21</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntmate21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntmate21/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtMATE21 Gene Name: multidrug and toxic compound extrusion21 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: NtMATE21 and NtMATE22, and demonstrate their role in flavonol transport and in plant growth and development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtMATE22</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntmate22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntmate22/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtMATE22 Gene Name: multidrug and toxic compound extrusion22 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: NtMATE21 and NtMATE22, and demonstrate their role in flavonol transport and in plant growth and development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PbMYB10b</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-bretschneideri/pbmyb10b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-bretschneideri/pbmyb10b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PbMYB10b Gene Name: MYB10b transcription factor Genome: Species: Pyrus bretschneideri Functional Descriptions: Among these MYB-like genes, the specific functions of two novel MYB TFs, designated as PbMYB10b and PbMYB9, were further verified by both overexpression and RNAi transient assays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PbMYB9</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-bretschneideri/pbmyb9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-bretschneideri/pbmyb9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PbMYB9 Gene Name: MYB9 transcription factor Genome: Species: Pyrus bretschneideri Functional Descriptions: Among these MYB-like genes, the specific functions of two novel MYB TFs, designated as PbMYB10b and PbMYB9, were further verified by both overexpression and RNAi transient assays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmSIZ1a</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/zea-mays/zm00001eb355110/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/zea-mays/zm00001eb355110/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Zm00001eb355110 Gene Symbol: ZmSIZ1a|phd17 Gene Name: PHD-transcription factor 17 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmSIZ1b</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/zea-mays/zm00001eb265410/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/zea-mays/zm00001eb265410/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Zm00001eb265410 Gene Symbol: ZmSIZ1b|phd12 Gene Name: PHD-transcription factor 12 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
