<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PAMP-Triggered Immunity on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/tags/pamp-triggered-immunity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PAMP-Triggered Immunity on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/tags/pamp-triggered-immunity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HvCEBiP</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvcebip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvcebip/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TA30910_4513 Gene Symbol: HvCEBiP Gene Name: CEBiP chitin receptor Genome: barley EST database Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Our findings suggest that HvWRKY2 represses barley basal immunity by directly targeting pathogen-associated molecular pattern (PAMP) recognition receptor genes, suggesting that HvCEBiP and likely chitin signaling function in barley PAMP-triggered immune responses to Bgh infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvSTP13</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvstp13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvstp13/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvSTP13 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: The expression of HvSTP13 increased on bacterial and fungal pathogen-associated molecular pattern (PAMP) application, suggesting a PAMP-triggered signalling that converged on the transcriptional induction of the gene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvWRKY2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvwrky2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvwrky2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: HvWRKY2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Our findings suggest that HvWRKY2 represses barley basal immunity by directly targeting pathogen-associated molecular pattern (PAMP) recognition receptor genes, suggesting that HvCEBiP and likely chitin signaling function in barley PAMP-triggered immune responses to Bgh infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MFAP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os06g22850/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os06g22850/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os06g22850 RAPdb gene ID: Os06g0335101 Gene Symbol: MFAP1 Gene Name: Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlSAP3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/slsap3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/slsap3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SlSAP3 Gene Name: stress-associated protein 3 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Tomato SlSAP3, a member of the stress-associated protein family, is a positive regulator of immunity against Pseudomonas syringae pv.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
