<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cucumis Sativus on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/cucumis-sativus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cucumis Sativus on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/cucumis-sativus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ACS1G</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csav3_6g044410/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csav3_6g044410/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_6G044410 Gene Symbol: ACS1G Gene Name: 1-aminocyclopropane-1-carboxylate synthase Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Gain-of-function of the 1-aminocyclopropane-1-carboxylate synthase gene ACS1G induces female flower development in cucumber gynoecy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Csa6G046210</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csa6g046210/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csa6g046210/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa6G046210 Gene Symbol: Csa6G046210 Gene Name: Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Two candidate genes (Csa6G046210 and Csa6G046240) were identified by fine-mapping gsb-s6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Csa6G046240</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csa6g046240/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csa6g046240/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa6G046240 Gene Symbol: Csa6G046240 Gene Name: Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Two candidate genes (Csa6G046210 and Csa6G046240) were identified by fine-mapping gsb-s6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsAAP2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csav3_4g030920csa4g470690/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csav3_4g030920csa4g470690/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_4G030920;Csa4G470690 Gene Symbol: CsAAP2 Gene Name: Amino Acid Permease 2 Genome: Cucurbit Genomics Database Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Disruption of the amino acid transporter CsAAP2 inhibits auxin-mediated root development in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsAAP2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csaap2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csaap2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa4G470690 Gene Symbol: CsAAP2 Gene Name: Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v3 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsAAP2 knockout lines exhibited arrested development of root meristem, which then caused the delayed initiation of lateral root and the inhibition of root elongation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsAAP2A</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa4m573860/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa4m573860/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa4M573860 Gene Symbol: CsAAP2A Gene Name: Amino Acid Permease 2A Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: DM resistance in cucumber due to CsAAP2A mutations is caused by perturbing pathogen-induced amino acid loading of infected leaves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsaARC5</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa7g051430/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa7g051430/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa7G051430 Gene Symbol: CsaARC5 Gene Name: ACCUMULATION AND REPLICATION OF CHLOROPLASTS 5 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: By re-sequencing of bulked segregants, we identified the candidate gene Csa7G051430 encoding ACCUMULATION AND REPLICATION OF CHLOROPLASTS 5 (ARC5) that plays a vital role in chloroplast division in Arabidopsis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsAGA2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csa4g167980/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csa4g167980/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa4G167980 Gene Symbol: CsAGA2 Gene Name: Alkaline α-galactosidase 2 Genome: Cucurbit Genomics Database Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Alkaline α-galactosidase 2 (CsAGA2) plays a pivotal role in mediating source–sink communication in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsAGL16</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csav3_3g048150/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csav3_3g048150/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_3G048150 Gene Symbol: CsAGL16 Gene Name: AGAMOUS-LIKE 16 Genome: Cucurbitaceae genome database Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: The AGAMOUS-LIKE 16–GENERAL REGULATORY FACTOR 1 module regulates axillary bud outgrowth via catabolism of abscisic acid in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsAKT1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csakt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csakt1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;CsaV3_1G029650 Gene Symbol: CsAKT1 Gene Name: Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v3 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsAKT1 is a key gene for the CeO2 nanoparticle&amp;rsquo;s improved cucumber salt tolerance: a validation from CRISPR-Cas9 lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsALC</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csalc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csalc/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa2G356640 Gene Symbol: CsALC Gene Name: ALCATRAZ Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: SPATULA and ALCATRAZ confer female sterility and fruit cavity via mediating pistil development in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsaMLO1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa1m085890/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa1m085890/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa1M085890 Gene Symbol: CsaMLO1 Gene Name: Mildew Locus O1 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsaMLO1 and CsaMLO11 were cloned from cucumber and overexpressed in a tomato mlo mutant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsaMLO11</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa6m292430/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa6m292430/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa6M292430 Gene Symbol: CsaMLO11 Gene Name: Mildew Locus O11 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsaMLO1 and CsaMLO11 were cloned from cucumber and overexpressed in a tomato mlo mutant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsaMLO8</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa5m623470.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa5m623470.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa5M623470.1 Gene Symbol: CsaMLO8 Gene Name: MLO-like susceptibility gene8 Genome: Cucurbit Genomics Database Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsaMLO8 alleles from susceptible and resistant cucumber were cloned and transformed to mlo-mutant tomato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsARN6.1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa6g504460/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa6g504460/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa6G504460 Gene Symbol: CsARN6.1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: The major-effect quantitative trait locus CsARN6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsATAF1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa4m361820.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa4m361820.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa4M361820.1 Gene Symbol: CsATAF1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsATAF1 Positively Regulates Drought Stress Tolerance by an ABA-Dependent Pathway and by Promoting ROS Scavenging in Cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsbHLH1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csa7g071650/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csa7g071650/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa7G071650 Gene Symbol: CsbHLH1 Gene Name: Transcription factor BHLH1 Genome: Cucurbit Genomics Database Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Virus-induced gene silencing analysis revealed that CsHOMEOBOX3 (CsHOX3) and CsbHLH1 are involved in nonglandular trichome elongation and glandular trichome formation, respectively, which corresponds with the transcriptome data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsBPC2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csbpc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csbpc2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsBPC2 Gene Name: BASIC PENTACYSTEINE 2 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsBPC2 knockout reduced cucumber cold tolerance by increasing the chilling injury index, relative electrical conductivity and malondialdehyde (MDA) content and decreasing antioxidant enzyme activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsBRC1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csbrc1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csbrc1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa1G020890 Gene Symbol: CsBRC1 Gene Name: cucumber BRANCHED1 Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsBRC1 inhibits axillary bud outgrowth by directly repressing the auxin efflux carrier CsPIN3 in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsbZIP63</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csbzip63/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csbzip63/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;CsGy2G003130 Gene Symbol: CsbZIP63 Gene Name: Genome: Cucumber (Gy14) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsbZIP63 and CsLRR1 play a role in the response of cucumber to PM infection and in the signaling pathways mediated by SA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsChi23</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csa6g507520/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csa6g507520/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa6G507520 Gene Symbol: CsChi23 Gene Name: Chitin-binding type-1 domain-containing protein Genome: Chinese Long Genome v.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsCOR413PM2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cscor413pm2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cscor413pm2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa_2G238250.1 Gene Symbol: CsCOR413PM2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Suppression of CsCOR413PM2 decreased cold tolerance of cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsCRC</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cscrc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cscrc/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;CsGy5G023910 Gene Symbol: CsCRC Gene Name: CRABS CLAW Genome: Cucumber (Gy14) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CRABS CLAW (CsCRC) as underlying the major-effect fruit size/shape QTL FS5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsCRK2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/csav3_2g024820/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/csav3_2g024820/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_2G024820 Gene Symbol: CsCRK2 Gene Name: cysteine-rich receptor-like kinase 2 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsMLO8 and CsCRK2 competitively interact with the C-terminus of CsRbohD to affect CsCRK2-CsRbohD module-mediated ROS production during PM defense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsCuRX</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cscurx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cscurx/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa3G215590 Gene Symbol: CsCuRX Gene Name: Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: miRNA_157-CsCuRX, miRNA_411-CsGH3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsCWIN3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa3g777580/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa3g777580/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa3G777580 Gene Symbol: CsCWIN3 Gene Name: Cell wall invertase 3 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Cell wall invertase 3 (CsCWIN3) plays critical roles in providing sugars during pollination and fertilization in cucumber CsCWIN3-RNA interference plants also showed affected seed development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsDFB1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csdfb1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csdfb1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa7G067350 Gene Symbol: CsDFB1 Gene Name: DEFORMED FLORAL BUD1 Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: We propose that the CsDFB1-CsPHB module represents a regulatory pathway for local auxin distribution that governs floral organogenesis and vascular differentiation in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsDMP</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csdmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csdmp/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;CsaV3_1G028660 Gene Symbol: CsDMP Gene Name: DOMAIN OF UNKNOWN FUNCTION 679 MEMBRANE PROTEIN Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v3 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Mutating the maternal haploid inducer gene CsDMP in cucumber produces haploids in planta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsEIL3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_6g004610/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_6g004610/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_6G004610 Gene Symbol: CsEIL3 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: A CsEIL3-CsARN6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsERF31</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa3g135120/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa3g135120/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa3G135120 Gene Symbol: CsERF31 Gene Name: ETHYLENE RESPONSE FACTOR31 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: A positive feedback loop mediated by CsERF31 initiates female cucumber flower development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsExo70B</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csexo70b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csexo70b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;CsaV3_1G036490.1 Gene Symbol: CsExo70B Gene Name: exocytosis subunit Exo70B Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v3 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Our work reveals a regulatory mechanism that CsExo70B promotes both fruit elongation and disease resistance by maintaining appropriate RK levels at the PM.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsFnl7.1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csfnl7.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csfnl7.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;CsGy7G014720 Gene Symbol: CsFnl7.1 Gene Name: Genome: Cucumber (Gy14) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: The major-effect quantitative trait locus Fnl7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsFT</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csft/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa1G651710 Gene Symbol: CsFT Gene Name: FLOWERING LOCUS T Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: FLOWERING LOCUS T (CsFT) is presumably an important genetic determinant of flowering time variation in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsFUL1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csful1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csful1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa1G039910 Gene Symbol: CsFUL1 Gene Name: FRUITFULL Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: A Functional Allele of CsFUL1 Regulates Fruit Length through Repressing CsSUP and Inhibiting Auxin Transport in Cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsGH3.6</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csgh3.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csgh3.6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa3G088930 Gene Symbol: CsGH3.6 Gene Name: Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: miRNA_157-CsCuRX, miRNA_411-CsGH3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsGL1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa3g748220/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa3g748220/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa3G748220 Gene Symbol: CsGL1 Gene Name: Glabrous 1 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsGL1 controls the formation of cucumber trichomes, including foliar trichomes, fruit spines, and bloom trichomes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsGPA1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csgpa1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csgpa1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa_4G648550.1 Gene Symbol: CsGPA1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Mechanism of CsGPA1 in regulating cold tolerance of cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsGRP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csgrp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csgrp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsGRP1 Gene Name: cell wall glycine-rich protein 1 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Differential accumulation of the mRNA of the auxin-repressed gene CsGRP1 and the auxin-induced peg formation during gravimorphogenesis of cucumber seedlings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsHD-Zip</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cshd-zip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cshd-zip/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa6G525430 Gene Symbol: CsHD-Zip Gene Name: Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: miRNA_157-CsCuRX, miRNA_411-CsGH3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsHEC1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cshec1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cshec1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa4G639900 Gene Symbol: CsHEC1 Gene Name: HECATE1 Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: We found that cucumber CsHEC1 is highly expressed in the fruit neck region and plays a positive role in fruit neck elongation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsHEC2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cshec2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cshec2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa2G285890 Gene Symbol: CsHEC2 Gene Name: HECATE2 Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: The basic Helix-Loop-Helix (bHLH) gene HECATE2 (CsHEC2) was highly expressed in cucumber fruit peels including spines and tubercules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsHLS1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_1g036420/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_1g036420/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_1G036420 Gene Symbol: CsHLS1 Gene Name: HOOKLESS 1 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsHLS1-CsSCL28 module regulates compact plant architecture in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsHMA3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/achr01008892.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/achr01008892.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: ACHR01008892.1 Gene Symbol: CsHMA3 Gene Name: heavy metal ATPase3 Genome: The genome of cucumber (ACHR0100000)(https://www.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsHMA4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/achr01010422.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/achr01010422.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: ACHR01010422.1 Gene Symbol: CsHMA4 Gene Name: heavy metal ATPase4 Genome: The genome of cucumber (ACHR0100000)(https://www.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsHOX3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csa1g031750/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csa1g031750/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa1G031750 Gene Symbol: CsHOX3 Gene Name: CsHOMEOBOX3 Genome: Cucurbit Genomics Database Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Virus-induced gene silencing analysis revealed that CsHOMEOBOX3 (CsHOX3) and CsbHLH1 are involved in nonglandular trichome elongation and glandular trichome formation, respectively, which corresponds with the transcriptome data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsHSFA1d</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa3g008920/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa3g008920/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa3G008920 Gene Symbol: CsHSFA1d Gene Name: heat-shock transcription factor HSFA1d Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Report that heat shock induces cold acclimation in cucumber seedlings, via a process involving the heat-shock transcription factor HSFA1d.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsIVP</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cucsa_101020.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cucsa_101020.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cucsa_101020.1 Gene Symbol: CsIVP Gene Name: Irregular Vasculature Patterning Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsIVP Modulates Low Nitrogen and High-Temperature Resistance in Cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsKF1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa7m446860/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa7m446860/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa7M446860 Gene Symbol: CsKF1 Gene Name: Kinesin protein1 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Characterization and expression profiling of cucumber kinesin genes during early fruit development: revealing the roles of kinesins in exponential cell production and enlargement in cucumber fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsKF2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa3m062600/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa3m062600/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa3M062600 Gene Symbol: CsKF2 Gene Name: Kinesin protein2 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Characterization and expression profiling of cucumber kinesin genes during early fruit development: revealing the roles of kinesins in exponential cell production and enlargement in cucumber fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsKF3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa4m002000/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa4m002000/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa4M002000 Gene Symbol: CsKF3 Gene Name: Kinesin protein3 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Characterization and expression profiling of cucumber kinesin genes during early fruit development: revealing the roles of kinesins in exponential cell production and enlargement in cucumber fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsLFY</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa1g000050.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa1g000050.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa1G000050.1 Gene Symbol: CsLFY Gene Name: LEAFY Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsLFY is required for shoot meristem maintenance via interaction with WUSCHEL in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsLOB1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cslob1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cslob1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsLOB1 Gene Name: Lateral organ boundaries 1 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: PthA, a transcriptional activator-like (TAL) effector, directs the expression of the canker susceptibility gene CsLOB1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsLRR1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cslrr1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cslrr1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;CsGy5G016190 Gene Symbol: CsLRR1 Gene Name: Genome: Cucumber (Gy14) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: A single-nucleotide substitution in the Leucine-Rich-Repeat-only gene CsLRR1 confers powdery mildew resistance in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsMLO11</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_6g021740/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_6g021740/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_6G021740 Gene Symbol: CsMLO11 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Knockout mutants of CsMLO8 and CsMLO11 generated by CRISPR/Cas9 both showed improved PM resistance in the stem, hypocotyl, and leaves, and the double mutant mlo8mlo11 displayed even stronger resistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsMLO8</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_5g036400/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_5g036400/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_5G036400 Gene Symbol: CsMLO8 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: The reverse mutation of CsMLO8 results in susceptibility to powdery mildew via inhibiting cell wall apposition formation and cell death in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsMTP7</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csmtp7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csmtp7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsMTP7 Gene Name: metal tolerance protein 7 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Cucumber metal tolerance protein 7 (CsMTP7) is involved in the accumulation of Fe in mitochondria under Fe excess.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsMYB36</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa2g352940/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa2g352940/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa2G352940 Gene Symbol: CsMYB36 Gene Name: MYB DOMAIN PROTEIN 36 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Transcription factor CsMYB36 regulates fruit neck length via mediating cell expansion in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsMYB6</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa3m824850.1-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa3m824850.1-/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa3M824850.1 Gene Symbol: CsMYB6 Gene Name: MIXTA-like MYB transcription factor 6 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: A CsMYB6-CsTRY module regulates fruit trichome initiation in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsMYB60</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_4g001130.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_4g001130.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_4G001130.1 Gene Symbol: CsMYB60 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsMYB60 directly and indirectly activates structural genes to promote the biosynthesis of flavonols and proanthocyanidins in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsNIP2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa017389/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa017389/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa017389 Gene Symbol: CsNIP2|1 Gene Name: nodulin-26 like intrinsic protein2 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsNIP2|1|CsNIP2|1 is a Plasma Membrane Transporter from Cucumis sativus that Facilitates Urea Uptake When Expressed in Saccharomyces cerevisiae and Arabidopsis thaliana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsPIN1b</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cspin1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cspin1b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa1G025070 Gene Symbol: CsPIN1b Gene Name: PIN-FORMED 1 Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: The auxin efflux carrier genes, CsPIN1b (Csa1G025070) and CsPIN3 (Csa5G576590).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsPIN3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cspin3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cspin3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa5G576590 Gene Symbol: CsPIN3 Gene Name: PIN-FORMED 3 Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: The auxin efflux carrier genes, CsPIN1b (Csa1G025070) and CsPIN3 (Csa5G576590).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsPLDα</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cspld%CE%B1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cspld%CE%B1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsPLDα Gene Name: Phospholipase D alpha Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Cucumber Phospholipase D alpha (CsPLDα) gene overexpression in tobacco enhanced drought stress tolerance by regulating stomatal closure and lipid peroxidation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsPM5.2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa5m471600/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa5m471600/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa5M471600 Gene Symbol: CsPM5.2 Gene Name: Powdery mildew 5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsPPSR1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa3g009550/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa3g009550/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa3G009550 Gene Symbol: CsPPSR1 Gene Name: Phloem Phosphate Stress-Repressed 1 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: A cucumber protein, Phloem Phosphate Stress-Repressed 1(CsPPSR1), rapidly degrades in response to a phosphate stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsRAX1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_6g014240/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_6g014240/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_6G014240 Gene Symbol: CsRAX1 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor 1 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsRAXs negatively regulate leaf size and fruiting ability through auxin glycosylation in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsRAX2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_3g036040/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_3g036040/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_3G036040 Gene Symbol: CsRAX2 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor 2 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsRAXs negatively regulate leaf size and fruiting ability through auxin glycosylation in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsRAX3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_2g025830/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_2g025830/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_2G025830 Gene Symbol: CsRAX3 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor 3 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsRAXs negatively regulate leaf size and fruiting ability through auxin glycosylation in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsRAX4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_6g044410/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_6g044410/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_6G044410 Gene Symbol: CsRAX4 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor 4 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsRAXs negatively regulate leaf size and fruiting ability through auxin glycosylation in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsRAX5</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_ung046320/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_ung046320/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_UNG046320 Gene Symbol: CsRAX5 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor 5 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsRAXs negatively regulate leaf size and fruiting ability through auxin glycosylation in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsRbohD</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_3g043480/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_3g043480/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_3G043480 Gene Symbol: CsRbohD Gene Name: respiratory burst oxidase homolog D Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsMLO8 and CsCRK2 competitively interact with the C-terminus of CsRbohD to affect CsCRK2-CsRbohD module-mediated ROS production during PM defense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsRDR1a</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csrdr1a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csrdr1a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsRDR1a Gene Name: RNA-dependent RNA polymerase 1a Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: The expression of all four CsRDR1 genes was induced by virus infection, after which the expression level of CsRDR1b increased 10–20-fold in several virus-resistant cucumber cultivars and in a broad virus-resistant transgenic cucumber line expressing a high level of transgene small RNAs, all without alteration in salicylic acid (SA) levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsRDR1b</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csrdr1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csrdr1b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsRDR1b Gene Name: RNA-dependent RNA polymerase 1b Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: The expression of all four CsRDR1 genes was induced by virus infection, after which the expression level of CsRDR1b increased 10–20-fold in several virus-resistant cucumber cultivars and in a broad virus-resistant transgenic cucumber line expressing a high level of transgene small RNAs, all without alteration in salicylic acid (SA) levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsRDR1c1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csrdr1c1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csrdr1c1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsRDR1c1 Gene Name: RNA-dependent RNA polymerase 1c Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: The expression of all four CsRDR1 genes was induced by virus infection, after which the expression level of CsRDR1b increased 10–20-fold in several virus-resistant cucumber cultivars and in a broad virus-resistant transgenic cucumber line expressing a high level of transgene small RNAs, all without alteration in salicylic acid (SA) levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsRDR1c2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csrdr1c2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csrdr1c2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsRDR1c2 Gene Name: RNA-dependent RNA polymerase 1c2 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: The expression of all four CsRDR1 genes was induced by virus infection, after which the expression level of CsRDR1b increased 10–20-fold in several virus-resistant cucumber cultivars and in a broad virus-resistant transgenic cucumber line expressing a high level of transgene small RNAs, all without alteration in salicylic acid (SA) levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSCL28</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csscl28/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csscl28/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_3G003740 Gene Symbol: CsSCL28 Gene Name: SCRARERROW-LIKE 28 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsHLS1-CsSCL28 module regulates compact plant architecture in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSEC23</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa5g585430/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa5g585430/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa5G585430 Gene Symbol: CsSEC23 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: MutMap, genotyping, and gene editing results demonstrated that CsSEC23, which is the core component of COPII vesicles, mediates the glossiness of cucumber fruit peel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSEF1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssef1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssef1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsSEF1 Gene Name: putative CCCH-type zinc finger protein Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Expression of CsSEF1 gene encoding putative CCCH zinc finger protein is induced by defoliation and prolonged darkness in cucumber fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSh5.1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cssh5.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cssh5.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa5G171710 Gene Symbol: CsSh5.1 Gene Name: Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Mapping and identification of CsSh5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSPL</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa3m850670/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa3m850670/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa3M850670 Gene Symbol: CsSPL Gene Name: SPOROCYTELESS Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsSPL functions as an adaptor between HD-ZIP III and CsWUS transcription factors regulating anther and ovule development in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSPT</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csspt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csspt/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa6G491000 Gene Symbol: CsSPT Gene Name: SPATULA Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsSPT and CsALC act in homodimers and heterodimers to confer fruit cavity and female sterility by mediating genes involved in TT development, auxin-mediated signaling, and cell wall organization in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSTS1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssts1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssts1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsSTS1 Gene Name: STACHYOSE SYNTHASE 1 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Cucumber STACHYOSE SYNTHASE is regulated by its cis-antisense RNA asCsSTS to balance source–sink carbon partitioning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSTS2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssts2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssts2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsSTS2 Gene Name: STACHYOSE SYNTHASE 2 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Cucumber STACHYOSE SYNTHASE is regulated by its cis-antisense RNA asCsSTS to balance source–sink carbon partitioning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSTS3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssts3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssts3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsSTS3 Gene Name: STACHYOSE SYNTHASE 3 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Cucumber STACHYOSE SYNTHASE is regulated by its cis-antisense RNA asCsSTS to balance source–sink carbon partitioning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSUP</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cssup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cssup/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa3G012410 Gene Symbol: CsSUP Gene Name: Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: A Functional Allele of CsFUL1 Regulates Fruit Length through Repressing CsSUP and Inhibiting Auxin Transport in Cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSUS3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssus3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssus3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsSUS3 Gene Name: Sucrose Synthase 3 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Antisense expression of CsSUS3 clearly reduced cucumber tolerance to hypoxic stress induced by flooding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSUS4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa5g322500/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa5g322500/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa5G322500 Gene Symbol: CsSUS4 Gene Name: Sucrose Synthase 4 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Down-Regulating Cucumber Sucrose Synthase 4 (CsSUS4) Suppresses the Growth and Development of Flowers and Fruits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSUT1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssut1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/cssut1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsSUT1 Gene Name: Sucrose Transporter 1 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Down-regulation of the Sucrose Transporter CsSUT1 Causes Male Sterility by Altering Carbohydrate Supply.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsTBH</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cstbh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cstbh/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa3G748220 Gene Symbol: CsTBH Gene Name: TINY BRANCHED HAIR Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: We provide evidence that CsTBH can directly bind to the promoters of cucumber 1-Aminocyclopropane-1-Carboxylate Synthase (CsACS) genes and regulate their expression, which affects multicellular trichome development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsTEN</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csav3_5g039160/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csav3_5g039160/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_5G039160 Gene Symbol: CsTEN Gene Name: Tendril Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Although expression of two cucumber genes regulating tendril formation, Tendril (CsTEN) and Unusual Floral Organs (CsUFO), was significantly decreased in CsTL knockout lines, these two genes were not direct downstream targets of CsTL.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsTFL1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cstfl1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cstfl1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa6G452100 Gene Symbol: CsTFL1 Gene Name: TERMINAL FLOWER1 Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsTFL1 inhibits determinate growth and terminal flower formation through interaction with CsNOT2a in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsTIC21</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cstic21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cstic21/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa7G071680 Gene Symbol: CsTIC21 Gene Name: Cucumber TIC21 homologous Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Gene silencing and CRISPR/Cas9-mediated knock-out assays verified that the cucumber TIC21 homologous gene (CsTIC21) was associated with the albino phenotype.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsTL</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csav3_3g003590/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csav3_3g003590/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_3G003590 Gene Symbol: CsTL Gene Name: tendril-less Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Map-based cloning identified the mutated gene, CsaV3_3G003590, which we designated as CsTL, which is homologous to Arabidopsis thaliana LATERAL SUPPRESSOR (AtLAS).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsTM</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csa1g056960/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csa1g056960/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa1G056960 Gene Symbol: CsTM Gene Name: trichome morphology Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: The CsTM alters multicellular trichome morphology and enhances resistance against aphid by interacting with CsTIP1;1 in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsTOE3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_6g043390/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_6g043390/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_6G043390 Gene Symbol: CsTOE3 Gene Name: TARGET OF EAT3 homolog Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Suggesting that CsTOE3 may be involved in the regulatory network of cucumber fruit spine partly depending on ethylene pathway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsTRM5</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cstrm5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cstrm5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;CsaV3_2G013800 Gene Symbol: CsTRM5 Gene Name: TONNEAU1 recruiting motif protein 5 Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v3 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsTRM5 regulates fruit shape via mediating cell division direction and cell expansion in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsTRY</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa5m139610.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa5m139610.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa5M139610.1 Gene Symbol: CsTRY Gene Name: transcription factor TRY Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: A CsMYB6-CsTRY module regulates fruit trichome initiation in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsTS1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa5g523090/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa5g523090/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa5G523090 Gene Symbol: CsTS1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: A CsTu-TS1 regulatory module promotes fruit tubercule formation in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsTu</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa016861/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa016861/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa016861 Gene Symbol: CsTu Gene Name: Tuberculate fruit Genome: cucumber genome sequence (http://cuke.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsWAX2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa020530/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa020530/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa020530 Gene Symbol: CsWAX2 Gene Name: Genome: Cucumber Genome Database (http://cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsWOX1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa1g042780/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa1g042780/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa1G042780 Gene Symbol: CsWOX1 Gene Name: WUSCHEL-related homeobox1 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: WUSCHEL-related homeobox1 (CsWOX1) regulates vein patterning and leaf size in Cucumis sativus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsWUS</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa6m505860/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa6m505860/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa6M505860 Gene Symbol: CsWUS Gene Name: WUSCHEL Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsSPL functions as an adaptor between HD-ZIP III and CsWUS transcription factors regulating anther and ovule development in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Csyf2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csyf2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csyf2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;CsaV3_4G007140 Gene Symbol: Csyf2 Gene Name: C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsYUC10b</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csyuc10b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/csyuc10b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa3G190380 Gene Symbol: CsYUC10b Gene Name: Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: CsYUC10b promotes the formation of straight cucumber fruits, with possible applications in the production and breeding of cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsZFP6</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_5g028870/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csav3_5g028870/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_5g028870 Gene Symbol: CsZFP6 Gene Name: Genome: CuGenDB Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Cucumber glossy fruit 1 (CsGLF1) encodes the zinc finger protein 6 (CsZFP6) that regulates fruit glossiness by enhancing cuticular wax biosynthesis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mict</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/mict/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/mict/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: Mict Gene Name: Micro-trichome Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Mict regulates flavonoid metabolism in trichome development Mict regulates trichome development at early stages via its function in cell division or elongation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NRP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csa5g606550/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csa5g606550/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa5G606550 Gene Symbol: NRP1 Gene Name: nodulin-related protein 1 Genome: Cucurbit Genomics Database Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Comparative gene expression analysis revealed that nodulin-related protein 1 (NRP1) may be a good candidate for PM resistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NS</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/ns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/ns/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Csa2G264590 Gene Symbol: NS Gene Name: Genome: Cucumber (Chinese Long) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: NS encodes an auxin traNSporter that regulates the ‘numerous spines’ trait in cucumber fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SH3.1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csav3_3g015190/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csav3_3g015190/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_3G015190 Gene Symbol: SH3.1|PhyB Gene Name: Phytochrome B Genome: Cucurbit Genomics Database Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Two QTLs of hypocotyl elongation under low light, SH3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SH6.1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csav3_6g050300/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/cucumis-sativus/csav3_6g050300/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: CsaV3_6G050300 Gene Symbol: SH6.1|FEL Gene Name: FRIGIDA-ESSENTIAL LIKE Genome: Cucurbit Genomics Database Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Two QTLs of hypocotyl elongation under low light, SH3.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
