<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Solanum Tuberosum on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/solanum-tuberosum/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Solanum Tuberosum on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/solanum-tuberosum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BRC1b</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/solanum_tuberosum/brc1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/solanum_tuberosum/brc1b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;PGSC0003DMG400004054 Gene Symbol: BRC1b Gene Name: BRANCHED1b Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Description: We show that BRANCHED1b (BRC1b) acts as a tuberization repressor in aerial axillary buds, which prevents buds from competing in sink strength with stolons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScAREB4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.11g016910/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.11g016910/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.11G016910 Gene Symbol: ScAREB4 Gene Name: ABA-responsive element binding protein 4 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: ScAREB4 promotes potato constitutive and acclimated freezing tolerance associated with enhancing trehalose synthesis and oxidative stress tolerance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SN1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/sn1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/sn1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SN1 Gene Name: Snakin-1 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Snakin-1 (SN1), a cysteine-rich peptide with broad-spectrum antimicrobial activity in vitro, was evaluated for its ability to confer resistance to pathogens in transgenic potatoes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StABF1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stabf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stabf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StABF1 Gene Name: ABRE binding factor1 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Characterization of StABF1, a stress-responsive bZIP transcription factor from Solanum tuberosum L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StABL1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.10g025990.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.10g025990.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.10G025990.1 Gene Symbol: StABL1 Gene Name: bZIP transcription factors StABI5-like 1 Genome: Spud DB (http://spuddb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StAmy23</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg400009891/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg400009891/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: PGSC0003DMG400009891 Gene Symbol: StAmy23 Gene Name: alpha-amylase 23 Genome: potato genome sequence consortium database (http://solanaceae.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StAN11</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stan11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stan11/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StAN11 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: StAN11, a WD40-repeat gene, was cloned from potato cultivar Chieftain (Solanum tuberosum L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StAST1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.06g026030.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.06g026030.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.06G026030.1 Gene Symbol: StAST1 Gene Name: TCP protein 1 Genome: Spud DB (http://spuddb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StBAM1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg400001549/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg400001549/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: PGSC0003DMG400001549 Gene Symbol: StBAM1 Gene Name: Genome: potato genome sequence consortium database (http://solanaceae.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StBAM9</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg400010664/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg400010664/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: PGSC0003DMG400010664 Gene Symbol: StBAM9 Gene Name: Genome: potato genome sequence consortium database (http://solanaceae.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StBEL5</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stbel5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stbel5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StBEL5 Gene Name: BEL1-related homeotic protein 5 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: The level of StBEL5 mRNA increased in response to a short-day photoperiod in both leaves and stolons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StbHLH93</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stbhlh93/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stbhlh93/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StbHLH93 Gene Name: transcription factor bHLH93-like Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: We identified a novel tuber-specific basic helix–loop–helix (bHLH) transcription factor, StbHLH93, based on the high-resolution transcriptome of potato tuber development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StBIN2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.03g001350.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.03g001350.2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.03G001350.2 Gene Symbol: StBIN2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: StSN2 interacts with the brassinosteroid signaling suppressor StBIN2 to maintain tuber dormancy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StBRI1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmt400050728/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmt400050728/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: PGSC0003DMT400050728 Gene Symbol: StBRI1 Gene Name: BRASSINOSTEROID-INSENSITIVE 1 Genome: Spud DB Potato Genomics Resource data libraries Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: The brassinosteroid receptor StBRI1 promotes tuber development by enhancing plasma membrane H+-ATPase activity in potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StbZIP61</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stbzip61/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stbzip61/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StbZIP61 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: The potato transcription factor StbZIP61 regulates dynamic biosynthesis of salicylic acid in defense against Phytophthora infestans infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StCBL3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.06g013800.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.06g013800.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.06G013800.1 Gene Symbol: StCBL3 Gene Name: Calcineurin B-Like protein 3 Genome: Spud DB (http://spuddb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StCDPK3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stcdpk3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stcdpk3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StCDPK3 Gene Name: calcium dependent protein kinase3 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: The novel Solanum tuberosum calcium dependent protein kinase, StCDPK3, is expressed in actively growing organs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StERF3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/sterf3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/sterf3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StERF3 Gene Name: ERF-associated amphiphilic repression Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: The Potato ERF Transcription Factor StERF3 Negatively Regulates Resistance to Phytophthora infestans and Salt Tolerance in Potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StEXA1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.04g035210/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.04g035210/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.04G035210 Gene Symbol: StEXA1 Gene Name: Essential for potexvirus Accumulation 1 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Susceptibility factor StEXA1 interacts with StnCBP to facilitate potato virus Y accumulation through the stress granule-dependent RNA regulatory pathway in potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StGA20ox1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.03g016400.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.03g016400.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.03G016400.1 Gene Symbol: StGA20ox1 Gene Name: Genome: Spud DB (http://spuddb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StGA2ox1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stga2ox1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stga2ox1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StGA2ox1 Gene Name: Gibberellin 2-oxidase 1 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: StGA2ox1 is induced prior to stolon swelling and controls GA levels during potato tuber development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StInvInh2A</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stinvinh2a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stinvinh2a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StInvInh2A Gene Name: Shepody putative invertase inhibitor Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: StInvInh2 as an inhibitor of StvacINV1 regulates the cold-induced sweetening of potato tubers by specifically capping vacuolar invertase activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StInvInh2B</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stinvinh2b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stinvinh2b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StInvInh2B Gene Name: ND860-2 putative invertase inhibitor Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: StInvInh2 as an inhibitor of StvacINV1 regulates the cold-induced sweetening of potato tubers by specifically capping vacuolar invertase activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StIPP</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/solanum_tuberosum/stipp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/solanum_tuberosum/stipp/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;PGSC0003DMG400016891 Gene Symbol: StIPP Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Description: In Arabidopsis protoplasts, expression of StIPP resulted in the stabilization of the PAMP receptor, FLAGELLIN-SENSITIVE 2, indicating that StIPP may act as a PAMP-induced and localized antagonist of PtdIns(4,5)P2-dependent processes during plant immunity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StJAZ1-like</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.07g012950.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.07g012950.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.07G012950.1 Gene Symbol: StJAZ1-like Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Overexpression of StJAZ1-like affects tuber initiation and yield in potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StKCS6</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stkcs6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stkcs6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StKCS6 Gene Name: 3-ketoacyl-CoA synthase 6 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Silencing of StKCS6 in potato periderm leads to reduced chain lengths of suberin and wax compounds and increased peridermal transpiration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StLRPK1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stlrpk1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stlrpk1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StLRPK1 Gene Name: LRR receptor-like kinase 1 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: A potato STRUBBELIG-RECEPTOR FAMILY member, StLRPK1, associates with StSERK3A/BAK1 and activates immunity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StLTP10</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stltp10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stltp10/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StLTP10 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Silencing of StLTP10 results in reduced resistance to P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StLTP6</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stltp6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stltp6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StLTP6 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Potato (Solanum tuberosum L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StMKK1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/sotub12g010200.1.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/sotub12g010200.1.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Sotub12g010200.1.1 Gene Symbol: StMKK1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Found that StMKK1 negatively regulated potato resistance to the hemibiotrophic/biotrophic pathogens P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StMKK5</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/sotub03g022560/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/sotub03g022560/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Sotub03g022560 Gene Symbol: StMKK5 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: The potato StMKK5-StSIPK module enhances resistance to Phytophthora pathogens through activating the salicylic acid and ethylene signalling pathways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StMLP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.06g027430.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.06g027430.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.06G027430.1 Gene Symbol: StMLP1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: StMLP1, as a Kunitz trypsin inhibitor, enhances potato resistance and specifically expresses in vascular bundles during Ralstonia solanacearum infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StMPK7</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/solanum_tuberosum/stmpk7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/solanum_tuberosum/stmpk7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;PGSC0003DMP400021542 Gene Symbol: StMPK7 Gene Name: Soltu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StMYB144</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.atl_v3.07_1g012240.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.atl_v3.07_1g012240.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.Atl_v3.07_1G012240.1 Gene Symbol: StMYB144 Gene Name: myeloblastosis transcription factor 144 Genome: Annotation (v3) for the Phased Assembly of Atlantic Tetraploid Potato Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: StMYB24, StMYB144, and StMYB168 positively regulate suberin biosynthesis at potato tuber wounds during healing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StMYB168</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.atl_v3.09_2g018520.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.atl_v3.09_2g018520.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.Atl_v3.09_2G018520.1 Gene Symbol: StMYB168 Gene Name: myeloblastosis transcription factor 168 Genome: Annotation (v3) for the Phased Assembly of Atlantic Tetraploid Potato Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: StMYB24, StMYB144, and StMYB168 positively regulate suberin biosynthesis at potato tuber wounds during healing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StMYB24</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.atl_v3.02_4g016430.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.atl_v3.02_4g016430.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.Atl_v3.02_4G016430.1 Gene Symbol: StMYB24 Gene Name: myeloblastosis transcription factor 24 Genome: Annotation (v3) for the Phased Assembly of Atlantic Tetraploid Potato Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: StMYB24, StMYB144, and StMYB168 positively regulate suberin biosynthesis at potato tuber wounds during healing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StMYB44-1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg400003316/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg400003316/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: PGSC0003DMG400003316 Gene Symbol: StMYB44-1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: StMYB44 negatively regulates anthocyanin biosynthesis at high temperatures in tuber flesh of potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StMYB44-2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg400007994/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg400007994/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: PGSC0003DMG400007994 Gene Symbol: StMYB44-2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: StMYB44 negatively regulates anthocyanin biosynthesis at high temperatures in tuber flesh of potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StNAC103</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stnac103/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stnac103/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StNAC103 Gene Name: NAC transcription factor 103 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Silencing of the potato StNAC103 gene enhances the accumulation of suberin polyester and associated wax in tuber skin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StNPR3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg401000923/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg401000923/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: PGSC0003DMG401000923 Gene Symbol: StNPR3 Gene Name: non-expressor of pathogenesis-related protein 3 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: genome editing of StNPR3 confers potato resistance to CLso by activating SA-mediated defences and JA catabolism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StPBS1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stpbs1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stpbs1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StPBS1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Decoy engineering of the receptor-like cytoplasmic kinase StPBS1 to defend against virus infection in potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StPIP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg400014879/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmg400014879/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: PGSC0003DMG400014879 Gene Symbol: StPIP1 Gene Name: Genome: Spud DB (http://solanaceae.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StPP2Ac2b</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stpp2ac2b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stpp2ac2b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StPP2Ac2b Gene Name: protein phosphatase 2A catalytic subunit Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: The protein phosphatase 2A catalytic subunit StPP2Ac2b is involved in the control of potato tuber sprouting and source–sink balance in tubers and sprouts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StPPI1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stppi1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stppi1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StPPI1 Gene Name: proton pump interactor 1 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Characterization of StPPI1, a proton pump interactor from Solanum tuberosum L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StPTP1a</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/solanum_tuberosum/stptp1a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/solanum_tuberosum/stptp1a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;PGSC0003DMC400045325 Gene Symbol: StPTP1a Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Description: StPTP1a negatively regulates potato immunity and represses SA-related gene expression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StSN2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.01g050660.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.01g050660.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.01G050660.1 Gene Symbol: StSN2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: StSN2 interacts with the brassinosteroid signaling suppressor StBIN2 to maintain tuber dormancy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StSP6A</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmt400060057/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/pgsc0003dmt400060057/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: PGSC0003DMT400060057 Gene Symbol: StSP6A Gene Name: SELF-PRUNING 6A Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: The tuberization signal StSP6A represses flower bud development in potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StSP6A</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.05g026370.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.05g026370.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.05G026370.1 Gene Symbol: StSP6A Gene Name: Genome: Spud DB (http://spuddb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StSP6A</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/solanum_tuberosum/stsp6a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/solanum_tuberosum/stsp6a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: StSP6A Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Description: The direct physical interaction between StSWEET11 and StSP6A proteins represents a link between the sugar and photoperiodic pathways for the regulation of potato tuber formation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StSWEET11</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/solanum_tuberosum/stsweet11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/solanum_tuberosum/stsweet11/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: StSWEET11 Gene Name: Genome: Potato Genome Sequencing Consortium website (http://www.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StTINY3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.03g035540.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.03g035540.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.03G035540.1 Gene Symbol: StTINY3 Gene Name: CBF/DREB transcription factor3 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: The transcription factor StTINY3 enhances cold-induced sweetening resistance by coordinating starch resynthesis and sucrose hydrolysis in potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StTOPP6</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.05g025610.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.05g025610.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.05G025610.1 Gene Symbol: StTOPP6 Gene Name: type one protein phosphatase 6 Genome: Group Phureja DM 1-3 516 R44 (v.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StTST3.1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.02g022370.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.02g022370.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.02G022370.1 Gene Symbol: StTST3.1 Gene Name: TST3-type isoform Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Suppression of the tonoplast sugar transporter, StTST3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StTST3.2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.03g003220.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.03g003220.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.03G003220.1 Gene Symbol: StTST3.2 Gene Name: TST3-type isoform Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Suppression of the tonoplast sugar transporter StTST3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StUBA2a/b</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.01g005860.9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.01g005860.9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.01G005860.9 Gene Symbol: StUBA2a/b Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: StMPK7 phosphorylates and stabilizes a potato RNA-binding protein StUBA2a/b to enhance plant defence responses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StWRKY1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stwrky1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/stwrky1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: StWRKY1 Gene Name: WRKY DNA binding protein 1 Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: Transcription factor StWRKY1 regulates phenylpropanoid metabolites conferring late blight resistance in potato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StWUS</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.02g023940.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-tuberosum/soltu.dm.02g023940.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Soltu.DM.02G023940.1 Gene Symbol: StWUS Gene Name: WUSCHEL Genome: Species: Solanum tuberosum Functional Descriptions: WUSCHEL (StWUS) controls genotype-dependent shoot regeneration capacity in potato.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
