<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nodulation on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/tags/nodulation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nodulation on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/tags/nodulation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GmEXPB2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmexpb2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmexpb2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GmEXPB2 Gene Name: β-expansin gene Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: GmEXPB2, a Cell Wall β-Expansin, Affects Soybean Nodulation through Modifying Root Architecture and Promoting Nodule Formation and Development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmFWL1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.09g187000/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.09g187000/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.09G187000 Gene Symbol: GmFWL1 Gene Name: FW2-2-like1 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: The GmFWL1 (FW2-2-like) nodulation gene encodes a plasma membrane microdomain-associated protein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmMaT2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.18g258000/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.18g258000/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.18G258000 Gene Symbol: GmMaT2 Gene Name: malonyl-CoA acyltransferase 2 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Isoflavone malonyl-CoA acyltransferase GmMaT2 is involved in nodulation of soybean by modifying synthesis and secretion of isoflavones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmMAX2a</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmmax2a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmmax2a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GmMAX2a Gene Name: Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: GmMAX2a restored atmax2 root hair defects and soybean root hairs were changed in GmMAX2a overexpression (GmMAX2a-OE) or knockdown (GmMAX2a-KD) mutants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmNINa</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmnina/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmnina/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GmNINa Gene Name: NODULE INCEPTION 1a Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: A GmNINa-miR172c-NNC1 Regulatory Network Coordinates the Nodulation and Autoregulation of Nodulation Pathways in Soybean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmPT7</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmpt7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmpt7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GmPT7 Gene Name: phosphate transporter 7 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: A nodule-localized phosphate transporter GmPT7 plays an important role in enhancing symbiotic N2 fixation and yield in soybean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmRIC1|GmCLE1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/glycine_max/gmric1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/glycine_max/gmric1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.13g292300 Gene Symbol: GmRIC1GmCLE1 Gene Name: Rhizobia-Induced CLE1 Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a4_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Here, we report that microRNA172c (miR172c) activates soybean (Glycine max) Rhizobia-Induced CLE1 (GmRIC1) and GmRIC2 by removing the transcriptional repression of these genes by Nodule Number Control 1 (NNC1), leading to the activation of the AON pathway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmRIC2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/glycine_max/gmric2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/glycine_max/gmric2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.06g284100 Gene Symbol: GmRIC2 Gene Name: Rhizobia-Induced CLE2 Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a4_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Here, we report that microRNA172c (miR172c) activates soybean (Glycine max) Rhizobia-Induced CLE1 (GmRIC1) and GmRIC2 by removing the transcriptional repression of these genes by Nodule Number Control 1 (NNC1), leading to the activation of the AON pathway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmSTF3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glyma.16g092700/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glyma.16g092700/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.16G092700 Gene Symbol: GmSTF3 Gene Name: HYPOCOTYL5 orthologs TGACG-motif binding factors 3 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Shoot-to-root communication via GmUVR8-GmSTF3 photosignaling and flavonoid biosynthesis fine-tunes soybean nodulation under UV-B light.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmUGT4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmugt4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/gmugt4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GmUGT4 Gene Name: isoflavone 7-O-glucosyltransferase UGT4 Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: GmUGT4 was expressed in the roots (mainly in lateral roots) of the 7-day-old seedlings and seeds, both of which contained abundant amounts of isoflavone conjugates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmYUC2a</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.08g038600/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-max/glyma.08g038600/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.08g038600 Gene Symbol: GmYUC2a Gene Name: Genome: Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: GmYUC2a mediates auxin biosynthesis during root development and nodulation in soybean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GsSnRK1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-soja/gssnrk1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-soja/gssnrk1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GsSnRK1 Gene Name: sucrose nonfermenting kinase 1 Genome: wild soybean genome database (https://www.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LjCCD7</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/ljsga_131670.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/ljsga_131670.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: LjSGA_131670.1 Gene Symbol: LjCCD7 Gene Name: CAROTENOID CLEAVAGE DIOXYGENASE 7 Genome: Species: Lotus japonicus Functional Descriptions: CAROTENOID CLEAVAGE DIOXYGENASE 7 modulates plant growth, reproduction, senescence, and determinate nodulation in the model legume Lotus japonicus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LjENOD40–1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/ljenod401/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/ljenod401/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: LjENOD40–1 Gene Name: early nodulin-1 protein Genome: Species: Lotus japonicus Functional Descriptions: Two ENOD40 genes of L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LjENOD40–2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/ljenod402/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/ljenod402/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: LjENOD40–2 Gene Name: early nodulin-2 protein Genome: Species: Lotus japonicus Functional Descriptions: Two ENOD40 genes of L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LjERF1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/ljerf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/lotus-japonicus/ljerf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: LjERF1 Gene Name: transcription factor AP2-EREBP Genome: Species: Lotus japonicus Functional Descriptions: A Positive Regulatory Role for LjERF1 in the Nodulation Process Is Revealed by Systematic Analysis of Nodule-Associated Transcription Factors of Lotus japonicus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtCRE1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17chr8g0392301/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17chr8g0392301/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MtrunA17Chr8g0392301 Gene Symbol: MtCRE1 Gene Name: Cytokinin Response Element 1 Genome: M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtDMI2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr5g030920/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr5g030920/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr5g030920 Gene Symbol: MtDMI2 Gene Name: DOES NOT MAKE INFECTION 2 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: The MtDMI2-MtPUB2 Negative Feedback Loop Plays a Role in Nodulation Homeostasis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtEFD</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17_chr4g0002631/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17_chr4g0002631/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MtrunA17_Chr4g0002631 Gene Symbol: MtEFD Gene Name: Ethylene response Factor required for nodule Differentiation Genome: Mt5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtEFD2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17_chr3g0137174/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtruna17_chr3g0137174/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MtrunA17_Chr3g0137174 Gene Symbol: MtEFD2 Gene Name: ETHYLENE RESPONSE FACTOR REQUIRED FOR NODULE DIFFERENTIATION 2 Genome: Mt5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtERF1-1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mterf1-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mterf1-1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtERF1-1 Gene Name: B-3 Ethylene Response Factor Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: The B-3 Ethylene Response Factor MtERF1-1 Mediates Resistance to a Subset of Root Pathogens in Medicago truncatula without Adversely Affecting Symbiosis with Rhizobia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtERF74</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr2g105380/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr2g105380/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr2g105380 Gene Symbol: MtERF74 Gene Name: Medicago truncatula ERF-VII TF 74 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Group VII ethylene response factors, MtERF74 and MtERF75, sustain nitrogen fixation in Medicago truncatula microoxic nodules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtERF75</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr8g022820/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr8g022820/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr8g022820 Gene Symbol: MtERF75 Gene Name: Medicago truncatula ERF-VII TF 75 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Group VII ethylene response factors, MtERF74 and MtERF75, sustain nitrogen fixation in Medicago truncatula microoxic nodules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtLHY</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/mtlhy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/mtlhy/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MtLHY Gene Name: Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: These data shed new light on the roles of MtLHY in the orchestration of circadian oscillator in nodules and shoots, which provides a mechanistic link between nodulation, nitrogen assimilation, and clock function.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtNRT2.1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/mtnrt2.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/mtnrt2.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MtrunA17_Chr4g0028551.1 Gene Symbol: MtNRT2.1 Gene Name: Genome: M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtPUB2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtpub2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtpub2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtPUB2 Gene Name: U-box (PUB)–type E3 ligase 2 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: The MtDMI2-MtPUB2 Negative Feedback Loop Plays a Role in Nodulation Homeostasis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtROP9</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtrop9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/mtrop9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MtROP9 Gene Name: small G-protein ROP9 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Silencing of the Rac1 GTPase MtROP9 in Medicago truncatula Stimulates Early Mycorrhizal and Oomycete Root Colonizations But Negatively Affects Rhizobial Infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NPF7.6</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/npf7.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_truncatula/npf7.6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Mtr.27727.1 Gene Symbol: NPF7.6 Gene Name: Genome: JCVI Mt 4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rj4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-soja/glyma.01g165800-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/glycine-soja/glyma.01g165800-d/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Glyma.01g165800-D Gene Symbol: Rj4 Gene Name: Glycine soja thaumatin-like protein Genome: Species: Glycine soja Functional Descriptions: Rj4, a Gene Controlling Nodulation Specificity in Soybeans, Encodes a Thaumatin-Like Protein But Not the One Previously Reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ST6</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr3g107810/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr3g107810/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr3g107810 Gene Symbol: ST6 Gene Name: Specific tissue protein 6 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Specific tissue proteins 1 and 6 are involved in root biology during normal development and under symbiotic and pathogenic interactions in Medicago truncatula.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
