<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artemisia Annua on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/artemisia-annua/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Artemisia Annua on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/artemisia-annua/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AabHLH112</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/artemisia_annua/aabhlh112/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/artemisia_annua/aabhlh112/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: AabHLH112 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaDBR2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/artemisia_annua/aadbr2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/artemisia_annua/aadbr2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: AaDBR2 Gene Name: double-bond reductase 2 Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: We found that a trichome-specific transcription factor, AaWRKY9, positively regulates artemisinin biosynthesis by directly binding to the promoters of the artemisinin biosynthesis genes AaDBR2 and AaGSW1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaGSW1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/artemisia_annua/aagsw1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/artemisia_annua/aagsw1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: AaGSW1 Gene Name: glandular trichome–specific WRKY1 Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: We found that a trichome-specific transcription factor, AaWRKY9, positively regulates artemisinin biosynthesis by directly binding to the promoters of the artemisinin biosynthesis genes AaDBR2 and AaGSW1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaGSW2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aagsw2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aagsw2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: AaGSW2 Gene Name: Glandular secreting trichome 2 Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: The WRKY transcription factor AaGSW2 promotes glandular trichome initiation in Artemisia annua.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaHD1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aahd1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aahd1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: AaHD1 Gene Name: HOMEODOMAIN PROTEIN 1 Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: HOMEODOMAIN PROTEIN 1 (AaHD1) is required for jasmonate-mediated glandular trichome initiation in Artemisia annua.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaHD8</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aahd8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aahd8/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: AaHD8 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: Identify a homeodomain-leucine zipper (HD-ZIP) IV transcription factor, AaHD8, directly promoting the expression of AaHD1 for glandular trichome initiation in Artemisia annua.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaLTP3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aaltp3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aaltp3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: AaLTP3 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: Lipid Transfer Proteins (AaLTP3 and AaLTP4) Are Involved in Sesquiterpene Lactone Secretion from Glandular Trichomes in Artemisia annua.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaLTP4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aaltp4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aaltp4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: AaLTP4 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: Lipid Transfer Proteins (AaLTP3 and AaLTP4) Are Involved in Sesquiterpene Lactone Secretion from Glandular Trichomes in Artemisia annua.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaMIXTA1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aamixta1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aamixta1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: AaMIXTA1 Gene Name: MIXTA1 transcription factor Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: The roles of AaMIXTA1 in regulating the initiation of glandular trichomes and cuticle biosynthesis in Artemisia annua.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaMYC2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aamyc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aamyc2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: AaMYC2 Gene Name: MYC2 transcription factor 2 Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: The jasmonate-responsive AaMYC2 transcription factor positively regulates artemisinin biosynthesis in Artemisia annua.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaORA</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/artemisia_annua/aaora/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/artemisia_annua/aaora/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: AaORA Gene Name: octadecanoid-derivative responsive AP2-domain Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: AaTCP15, a JA and ABA dual-responsive teosinte branched1/cycloidea/proliferating (TCP) TF, which is essential for JA and ABA-induced artemisinin biosynthesis by directly binding to and activating the promoters of DBR2 and ALDH1, two genes encoding enzymes for artemisinin biosynthesis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaSEP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aannua10729s694100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aannua10729s694100/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Aannua10729S694100 Gene Symbol: AaSEP1 Gene Name: AaSEPALLATA1 Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: Identified a MADS-box transcription factor, AaSEPALLATA1 (AaSEP1), that positively regulates GST initiation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaSPL9</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aannua01109s179380/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aannua01109s179380/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Aannua01109S179380 Gene Symbol: AaSPL9 Gene Name: SQUAMOSA promoter-binding protein-like 9 Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: AaSPL9 could positively regulate the initiation of glandular trichome and artemisinin content in A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaTCP15</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/artemisia_annua/aatcp15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/artemisia_annua/aatcp15/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: AaTCP15 Gene Name: aldehyde dehydrogenase 1 Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: AaTCP15, a JA and ABA dual-responsive teosinte branched1/cycloidea/proliferating (TCP) TF, which is essential for JA and ABA-induced artemisinin biosynthesis by directly binding to and activating the promoters of DBR2 and ALDH1, two genes encoding enzymes for artemisinin biosynthesis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaWRKY1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aawrky1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aawrky1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: AaWRKY1 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor 1 Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: Isolation and Characterization of AaWRKY1, an Artemisia annua Transcription Factor that Regulates the Amorpha-4,11-diene Synthase Gene, a Key Gene of Artemisinin Biosynthesis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaWRKY17</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aannua01956s266050/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aannua01956s266050/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Aannua01956S266050 Gene Symbol: AaWRKY17 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: AaWRKY17, a positive regulator of artemisinin biosynthesis, is involved in resistance to Pseudomonas syringae in Artemisia annua.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaWRKY9</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/artemisia_annua/aawrky9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/artemisia_annua/aawrky9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: AaWRKY9 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor 9 Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: Our data suggested that the AaWRKY9 protein positively regulates artemisinin biosynthesis by directly binding to the W-boxes in the promoters of DBR2 and AaGSW1 and activating their expression AaWRKY9 contributes to light- and jasmonate-mediated to regulate the biosynthesis of artemisinin in Artemisia annua.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AaYABBY5</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aayabby5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/artemisia-annua/aayabby5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: AaYABBY5 Gene Name: YABBY family transcription factor 5 Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: Transcriptional regulation of flavonoid biosynthesis in Artemisia annua by AaYABBY5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALDH1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/artemisia_annua/aldh1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/artemisia_annua/aldh1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: ALDH1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Artemisia annua Functional Descriptions: AaTCP15, a JA and ABA dual-responsive teosinte branched1/cycloidea/proliferating (TCP) TF, which is essential for JA and ABA-induced artemisinin biosynthesis by directly binding to and activating the promoters of DBR2 and ALDH1, two genes encoding enzymes for artemisinin biosynthesis.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
