<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rosa Hybridaaa on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/rosa-hybridaaa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rosa Hybridaaa on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/rosa-hybridaaa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RcMYB1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rcmyb1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rcmyb1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RcMYB1 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor 1 Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaaa Functional Descriptions: The MYB transcription factor RcMYB1 plays a central role in rose anthocyanin biosynthesis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhARF7</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rharf7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rharf7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhARF7 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaaa Functional Descriptions: We established that the auxin signaling protein RhARF7 binds to the promoter of RhSUC2, and that silencing of RhARF7 reduces petal Suc contents and promotes petal abscission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhbZIP17</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rchiobhm_chr3g0480361/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rchiobhm_chr3g0480361/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: RchiOBHm_Chr3g0480361 Gene Symbol: RhbZIP17 Gene Name: Genome: RchiOBHm-V2(https://lipm-browsers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhCCCH12</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhccch12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhccch12/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhCCCH12 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaaa Functional Descriptions: Two transcription factors, RhERF005 and RhCCCH12, regulate rose resistance to Botrytis cinerea by modulating cytokinin levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhERF005</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rherf005/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rherf005/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhERF005 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaaa Functional Descriptions: Two transcription factors, RhERF005 and RhCCCH12, regulate rose resistance to Botrytis cinerea by modulating cytokinin levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhGID1B</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhgid1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhgid1b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhGID1B Gene Name: GIBBERELLIN INSENSITIVE DWARF1 Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaaa Functional Descriptions: The F-box protein RhSAF destabilizes the gibberellic acid receptor RhGID1 to mediate ethylene-induced petal senescence in rose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhGID1C</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhgid1c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhgid1c/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhGID1C Gene Name: GIBBERELLIN INSENSITIVE DWARF1 Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaaa Functional Descriptions: The F-box protein RhSAF destabilizes the gibberellic acid receptor RhGID1 to mediate ethylene-induced petal senescence in rose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhHB1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhhb1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhhb1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhHB1 Gene Name: homeobox-leucine zipper protein 1 Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaaa Functional Descriptions: Silencing RhHB1 decreased petal dehydration tolerance and resulted in a persistent increase in JA-Ile content and reduced dehydration tolerance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhPAASa1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhpaasa1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhpaasa1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhPAASa1 Gene Name: PHENYLACETALDEHYDE SYNTHASE Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaaa Functional Descriptions: Biosynthesis of 2-Phenylethanol in Rose Petals Is Linked to the Expression of One Allele of RhPAAS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhPAASa2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhpaasa2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhpaasa2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhPAASa2 Gene Name: PHENYLACETALDEHYDE SYNTHASE Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaaa Functional Descriptions: Biosynthesis of 2-Phenylethanol in Rose Petals Is Linked to the Expression of One Allele of RhPAAS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhPAASa3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhpaasa3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhpaasa3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhPAASa3 Gene Name: PHENYLACETALDEHYDE SYNTHASE Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaaa Functional Descriptions: Biosynthesis of 2-Phenylethanol in Rose Petals Is Linked to the Expression of One Allele of RhPAAS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhPLATZ9</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhplatz9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhplatz9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhPLATZ9 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaaa Functional Descriptions: The RhWRKY33a-RhPLATZ9 regulatory module delays petal senescence by suppressing rapid reactive oxygen species accumulation in rose flowers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhSAF</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhsaf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhsaf/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhSAF Gene Name: SENESCENCE-ASSOCIATED F-BOX Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaaa Functional Descriptions: The F-box protein RhSAF destabilizes the gibberellic acid receptor RhGID1 to mediate ethylene-induced petal senescence in rose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhSUC2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhsuc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhsuc2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhSUC2 Gene Name: sucrose proton symporter 2 Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaaa Functional Descriptions: Regulation of RhSUC2, a sucrose transporter, is correlated with the light control of bud burst in Rosa sp.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhVI1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhvi1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhvi1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhVI1 Gene Name: Rosa hybridaaa Vacuolar Invertase isoform 1 Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaaa Functional Descriptions: RhVI1 is a membrane-anchored vacuolar invertase highly expressed in Rosa hybridaaa L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhWRKY30</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rchiobhm_chr4g0429851/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rchiobhm_chr4g0429851/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: RchiOBHm_Chr4g0429851 Gene Symbol: RhWRKY30 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor 30 Genome: RchiOBHm-V2(https://lipm-browsers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhWRKY33a</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhwrky33a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaaa/rhwrky33a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhWRKY33a Gene Name: Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaaa Functional Descriptions: The RhWRKY33a-RhPLATZ9 regulatory module delays petal senescence by suppressing rapid reactive oxygen species accumulation in rose flowers.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
