<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pisum Sativum on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/pisum-sativum/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pisum Sativum on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/pisum-sativum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HSP22</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/hsp22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/hsp22/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HSP22 Gene Name: heat shock protein 22 Genome: Species: Pisum sativum Functional Descriptions: Variability within a pea core collection of LEAM and HSP22, two mitochondrial seed proteins involved in stress tolerance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEAM</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/leam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/leam/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: LEAM Gene Name: late embryogenesis abundant protein Genome: Species: Pisum sativum Functional Descriptions: Variability within a pea core collection of LEAM and HSP22, two mitochondrial seed proteins involved in stress tolerance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsAFB4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/psafb4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/psafb4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PsAFB4 Gene Name: TIR1/AFB 4 Genome: Species: Pisum sativum Functional Descriptions: The pea PsAFB4 mutant ramosus 2 has increased shoot branching, shorter internodes, and reduced shoot and root dry weights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsAFB6</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/psafb6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/psafb6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PsAFB6 Gene Name: TIR1/AFB 6 Genome: Species: Pisum sativum Functional Descriptions: Pericarp PsAFB6 expression was suppressed by seeds and increased in response to deseeding, and exogenous hormone treatments suggest that seed-derived auxin and deseeding-induced ethylene are involved in these responses, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsBRC1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/psbrc1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/psbrc1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PsBRC1 Gene Name: BRANCHED1 Genome: Species: Pisum sativum Functional Descriptions: The effectiveness of SL at affecting bud and branch growth correlated with the ability of SL to regulate expression of PsBRC1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsGRP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/psgrp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/psgrp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PsGRP1 Gene Name: putative glycine rich protein precursor Genome: Species: Pisum sativum Functional Descriptions: Expression of PsGRP1, a novel glycine rich protein gene of Pisum sativum, is induced in developing fruit and seed and by ABA in pistil and root.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsIAA7</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/psiaa7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/psiaa7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PsIAA7 Gene Name: Aux/IAA Genome: Species: Pisum sativum Functional Descriptions: Found that all five pea TIR1/AFB receptor proteins interacted with the pea AUX/IAAs PsIAA6 and/or PsIAA7 in an auxin-dependent manner, a requirement for functional auxin receptors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsIAA8</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/psiaa8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/psiaa8/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PsIAA8 Gene Name: Aux/IAA Genome: Species: Pisum sativum Functional Descriptions: The interaction of the pea TIR1/AFB proteins with PsIAA8 and PsIAA9a proteins in the presence of auxin was quite variable in this Y2H assay system and requires testing using another Y2H system that may be more sensitive to protein–protein interactions promoted by auxin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsIAA9a</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/psiaa9a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/psiaa9a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PsIAA9a Gene Name: Aux/IAA Genome: Species: Pisum sativum Functional Descriptions: The interaction of the pea TIR1/AFB proteins with PsIAA8 and PsIAA9a proteins in the presence of auxin was quite variable in this Y2H assay system and requires testing using another Y2H system that may be more sensitive to protein–protein interactions promoted by auxin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsMLO1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/pisum-sativum/psmlo1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/pisum-sativum/psmlo1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PsMLO1 Gene Name: mildew resistance locus O gene 1 Genome: Species: Pisum sativum Functional Descriptions: The observed resistance in Yunwan 8 plants resulted from a point mutation (C → G) at position 680 of PsMLO1 that introduced a stop codon, leading to premature termination of protein synthesis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsMPK2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/psmpk2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/psmpk2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PsMPK2 Gene Name: C1 subgroup MAP kinase Genome: Species: Pisum sativum Functional Descriptions: PsMPK2, was isolated from Pisum sativum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsPIN1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/pspin1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/pspin1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PsPIN1 Gene Name: auxin efflux carrier protein PIN1 Genome: Species: Pisum sativum Functional Descriptions: PsPK2 (the gene for a pea homolog of Arabidopsis PID , a regulator of PIN1 targeting), PsPIN1 (the major gene for a putative auxin efflux carrier) and LE (a gibberellin biosynthesis gene, GA3ox ), and also examined mutual hormonal regulation of these genes, in pea shoot tips, including a number of mutants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsPK2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/pspk2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/pspk2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PsPK2 Gene Name: Pisum sativum serine/threonine protein kinase2 Genome: Species: Pisum sativum Functional Descriptions: PsPK2 (the gene for a pea homolog of Arabidopsis PID , a regulator of PIN1 targeting), PsPIN1 (the major gene for a putative auxin efflux carrier) and LE (a gibberellin biosynthesis gene, GA3ox ), and also examined mutual hormonal regulation of these genes, in pea shoot tips, including a number of mutants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsTrxo1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/pstrxo1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pisum-sativum/pstrxo1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PsTrxo1 Gene Name: mitochondrial thioredoxin1 Genome: Species: Pisum sativum Functional Descriptions: Response of mitochondrial thioredoxin PsTrxo1, antioxidant enzymes, and respiration to salinity in pea leaves.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
