<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Root Growth on COTTON</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/root-growth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Root Growth on COTTON</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/root-growth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GaJAZ1</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/gajaz1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/gajaz1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cotton_A_11862 Gene Symbol: GaJAZ1 Gene Name: Genome: Gossypium hirsutum L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhAPX</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghapx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghapx/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: GhAPX Gene Name: Genome: Cotton Genome Database Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Root growth of GhAPX-overexpressing Arabidopsis subjected to abiotic stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhCERP</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghcerp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghcerp/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gh_D02G2021 Gene Symbol: GhCERP Gene Name: Genome: cotton genome (Gossypium hirsutum, NAU) Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Inter-species functional analysis of the BR-mediated BES1-CERP-EXPA3 signaling cascade also promotes Arabidopsis root and hypocotyl growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhEXPA3-1</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghexpa3-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/genes/gossypium_hirsutum/ghexpa3-1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gh_D04G1924 Gene Symbol: GhEXPA3-1 Gene Name: Genome: cotton genome (Gossypium hirsutum, NAU) Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: GhBES1 directly binds to E-box of GhCERP and regulates the transcription of GhCERP, which further binds to E-box of GhEXPA3-1 to enhance its transcription to promote plant cell elongation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhMKK3</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghmkk3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghmkk3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GhMKK3 Gene Name: Mitogen-Activated Protein Kinase Kinase 3 Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: The Cotton Mitogen-Activated Protein Kinase Kinase 3 (GhMKK3) Functions in Drought Tolerance by Regulating Stomatal Responses and Root Growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhWRKY17</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghwrky17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/genes/2024.6.9/gossypium-hirsutum/ghwrky17/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: GhWRKY17 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor 17 Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: The Cotton WRKY Transcription Factor GhWRKY17 Functions in Drought and Salt Stress in Transgenic Nicotiana benthamiana Through ABA Signaling and the Modulation of Reactive Oxygen Species Production.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
