<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Salvia Miltiorrhiza on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/salvia-miltiorrhiza/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Salvia Miltiorrhiza on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/salvia-miltiorrhiza/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SmCPS1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smcps1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smcps1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SmCPS1 Gene Name: copalyl diphosphate synthase1 Genome: Species: Salvia miltiorrhiza Functional Descriptions: The ethylene response factor SmERF6 co-regulates the transcription of SmCPS1 and SmKSL1 and is involved in tanshinone biosynthesis in Salvia miltiorrhiza hairy roots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmERF115</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smil_00025335/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smil_00025335/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: SMil_00025335 Gene Symbol: SmERF115 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Salvia miltiorrhiza Functional Descriptions: The SmMYB36-SmERF6/SmERF115 module regulates the biosynthesis of tanshinones and phenolic acids in salvia miltiorrhiza hairy roots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmERF6</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smil_00020272/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smil_00020272/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: SMil_00020272 Gene Symbol: SmERF6 Gene Name: ethylene responsive factor 6 Genome: miltiorrhiza online information resource (http://bi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmERF73</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smerf73/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smerf73/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SmERF73 Gene Name: ethylene response factor 73 Genome: Species: Salvia miltiorrhiza Functional Descriptions: The ERF-VII transcription factor SmERF73 coordinately regulates tanshinone biosynthesis in response to stress elicitors in Salvia miltiorrhiza.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmJAZ8</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smjaz8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smjaz8/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SmJAZ8 Gene Name: jasmonate ZIM-domain protein 8 Genome: Species: Salvia miltiorrhiza Functional Descriptions: SmJAZ8 acts as a core repressor regulating JA-induced biosynthesis of salvianolic acids and tanshinones in Salvia miltiorrhiza hairy roots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmKFB5</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smkfb5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smkfb5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SmKFB5 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Salvia miltiorrhiza Functional Descriptions: SmKFB5 protein regulates phenolic acid biosynthesis by controlling the degradation of phenylalanine ammonia-lyase in Salvia miltiorrhiza.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmKSL1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smksl1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smksl1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SmKSL1 Gene Name: kaurene synthase1 Genome: Species: Salvia miltiorrhiza Functional Descriptions: The ethylene response factor SmERF6 co-regulates the transcription of SmCPS1 and SmKSL1 and is involved in tanshinone biosynthesis in Salvia miltiorrhiza hairy roots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmMYB1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/salvia_miltiorrhiza/smmyb1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/salvia_miltiorrhiza/smmyb1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;SmiContig1043 Gene Symbol: SmMYB1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Salvia miltiorrhiza Functional Description: In the current study, we identified the MeJA-responsive R2R3-MYB transcription factor-encoding gene SmMYB1 from an S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmMYB2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smicontig1859/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smicontig1859/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: SmiContig1859 Gene Symbol: SmMYB2 Gene Name: Genome: S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmMYB36</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smmyb36/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smmyb36/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SmMYB36 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Salvia miltiorrhiza Functional Descriptions: SmMYB36, a Novel R2R3-MYB Transcription Factor, Enhances Tanshinone Accumulation and Decreases Phenolic Acid Content in Salvia miltiorrhiza Hairy Roots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmNPR4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/c16843.graph_c0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/c16843.graph_c0/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: c16843.graph_c0 Gene Symbol: SmNPR4 Gene Name: NPR protein 4 Genome: Species: Salvia miltiorrhiza Functional Descriptions: The SmNPR4-SmTGA5 module regulates SA-mediated phenolic acid biosynthesis in Salvia miltiorrhiza hairy roots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmTGA5</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smil_00004488/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/salvia-miltiorrhiza/smil_00004488/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: SMil_00004488 Gene Symbol: SmTGA5 Gene Name: leucine zipper family transcription factor 5 Genome: Species: Salvia miltiorrhiza Functional Descriptions: The SmNPR4-SmTGA5 module regulates SA-mediated phenolic acid biosynthesis in Salvia miltiorrhiza hairy roots.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
