<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fragaria Ananassa on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/fragaria-ananassa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fragaria Ananassa on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/fragaria-ananassa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>F3H</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/fragaria-ananassa/fvh4_1g11810/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/fragaria-ananassa/fvh4_1g11810/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: FvH4_1g11810 Gene Symbol: F3H Gene Name: flavanone-3-hydroxylase Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: Bulked-segregant analysis sequencing analysis and gene function verification confirmed that the responsible mutation resides in a gene encoding flavanone-3-hydroxylase (F3H) in the anthocyanin synthesis pathway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaAAT2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/faaat2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/faaat2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaAAT2 Gene Name: alcohol acyltransferase2 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: The fruit ripening-related gene FaAAT2 encodes an acyl transferase involved in strawberry aroma biogenesis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaABAR</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/faabar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/faabar/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaABAR Gene Name: ABA receptor Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: Strawberry FaABAR is an ABA receptor that serves an inducer of fruit ripening, and identification of FaABAR-interacting proteins can therefore provide insights into the action of ABA in ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaARF4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/fragaria_ananassa/faarf4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/fragaria_ananassa/faarf4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: FaARF4 Gene Name: auxin response factor4 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Description: Auxin-induced AUXIN RESPONSE FACTOR4 activates APETALA1 and FRUITFULL to promote flowering in woodland strawberry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FabHLH3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fabhlh3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fabhlh3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FabHLH3 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: FaMYB123 interacts with FabHLH3 to regulate the late steps of anthocyanin and flavonol biosynthesis during ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaBRIZ</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/maker-fvb6-2-augustus-gene-66.20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/maker-fvb6-2-augustus-gene-66.20/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: maker-Fvb6-2-augustus-gene-66.20 Gene Symbol: FaBRIZ Gene Name: RING-type E3 ligase Genome: Camarosa Genome Assembly v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaDOF2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fadof2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fadof2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaDOF2 Gene Name: ZnF-Dof-type transcription factor 1 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: The fruit-specific transcription factor FaDOF2 regulates the production of eugenol in ripe fruit receptacles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaGAPC2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/fragaria_ananassa/fagapc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/fragaria_ananassa/fagapc2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;FxaC_14g13400 Gene Symbol: FaGAPC2 Gene Name: Genome: FAN (F.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaGAST1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fagast1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fagast1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaGAST1 Gene Name: GAST-like gene1 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: FaGAST2, a strawberry ripening-related gene, acts together with FaGAST1 to determine cell size of the fruit receptacle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaGAST2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fagast2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fagast2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaGAST2 Gene Name: GAST-like gene2 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: FaGAST2, a strawberry ripening-related gene, acts together with FaGAST1 to determine cell size of the fruit receptacle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaGT2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fagt2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fagt2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaGT2 Gene Name: UDP-glucose glucosyltransferase 2 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: FaGT2: a multifunctional enzyme from strawberry (Fragaria × ananassa) fruits involved in the metabolism of natural and xenobiotic compounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaGT6</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fagt6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fagt6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaGT6 Gene Name: UDP-glucose glucosyltransferase6 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: Two glucosyltransferases, FaGT6 and FaGT7, were cloned from a strawberry (Fragaria×ananassa) cDNA library and the full-length open reading frames were amplified by rapid amplification of cDNA ends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaGT7</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fagt7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fagt7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaGT7 Gene Name: UDP-glucose glucosyltransferase7 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: Two glucosyltransferases, FaGT6 and FaGT7, were cloned from a strawberry (Fragaria×ananassa) cDNA library and the full-length open reading frames were amplified by rapid amplification of cDNA ends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaMADS9</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/fragaria_ananassa/famads9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/fragaria_ananassa/famads9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;FvH4_6g46420 Gene Symbol: FaMADS9 Gene Name: Genome: FAN (F.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaMYB1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/famyb1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/famyb1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaMYB1 Gene Name: transcription factor MYB1 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: The strawberry transcription factor FaMYB1 inhibits the biosynthesis of proanthocyanidins in Lotus corniculatus leaves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaMYB10</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/famyb10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/famyb10/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaMYB10 Gene Name: MYB transcription factor10 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: This insertion introduced a predicted premature termination codon, which suggested the loss of intact FaMYB10 protein playing a critical role in the loss of red colour in white octoploid strawberry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaMYB123</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fvh4_5g32460/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fvh4_5g32460/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: FvH4_5g32460 Gene Symbol: FaMYB123 Gene Name: R2R3 MYB transcription factor 123 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: FaMYB123 interacts with FabHLH3 to regulate the late steps of anthocyanin and flavonol biosynthesis during ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaMYB63</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/fragaria-ananassa/fvh4_3g15320.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/fragaria-ananassa/fvh4_3g15320.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: FvH4_3g15320.1 Gene Symbol: FaMYB63 Gene Name: 2R3-MYB transcription factor 63 Genome: Fragaria vesca Whole Genome v4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaPE1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fape1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fape1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaPE1 Gene Name: pectinesterase1 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: Concerning hormone regulation, auxin treatment increased FaPE1 mRNA levels in green fruit, whereas exogenous ethylene decreased FaPE1 mRNA levels in ripe and senescing fruits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaPEPCK</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/fragaria_ananassa/fapepck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/fragaria_ananassa/fapepck/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;FxaC_1g21491 Gene Symbol: FaPEPCK Gene Name: Genome: FAN (F.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaPG1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fapg1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fapg1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaPG1 Gene Name: putative endo-polygalacturonase Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: Antisense Down-Regulation of the FaPG1 Gene Reveals an Unexpected Central Role for Polygalacturonase in Strawberry Fruit Softening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaPG2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fapg2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fapg2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaPG2 Gene Name: polygalacturonase-like protein Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: Polygalacturonase (PG) activity is low during this process, but two ripening-related PG genes, FaPG1 and FaPG2, have been cloned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaPIP2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fapip2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fapip2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaPIP2|1 Gene Name: Water channel protein Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: FaPIP2|1|FaPIP2|1, an aquaporin subtype of PIP2 was cloned and its functional characterization in Xenopus oocytes determined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaPKc2.2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/fragaria_ananassa/fapkc2.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/fragaria_ananassa/fapkc2.2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;FxaC_15g00080 Gene Symbol: FaPKc2.2 Gene Name: Genome: FAN (F.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaPYR1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fapyr1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fapyr1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaPYR1 Gene Name: abscisic acid receptor PYR1 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: Down-regulation of the FaPYR1 gene not only significantly delayed fruit ripening, but also markedly altered ABA content, ABA sensitivity, and a set of ABA-responsive gene transcripts, including ABI1 and SnRK2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaQR</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/faqr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/faqr/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaQR Gene Name: 2-methylene-furan-3-one reductase-like Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: FaQR, Required for the Biosynthesis of the Strawberry Flavor Compound 4-Hydroxy-2,5-Dimethyl-3(2H)-Furanone, Encodes an Enone Oxidoreductase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaRAV1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/fragaria_ananassa/farav1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/fragaria_ananassa/farav1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: FaRAV1 Gene Name: Genome: FAN (F.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaRGLyase1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/farglyase1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/farglyase1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaRGLyase1 Gene Name: rhamnogalacturonate lyase 1 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: The strawberry (Fragaria×ananassa) fruit-specific rhamnogalacturonate lyase 1 (FaRGLyase1) gene encodes an enzyme involved in the degradation of cell-wall middle lamellae.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaRIF</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/fragaria-ananassa/fvh4_3g20700/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/fragaria-ananassa/fvh4_3g20700/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: FvH4_3g20700 Gene Symbol: FaRIF|FaNAC035 Gene Name: Ripening Inducing Factor Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: The NAC transcription factor FaRIF|FaNAC035 controls fruit ripening in strawberry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaRIPK1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/faripk1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/faripk1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaRIPK1 Gene Name: red-initial protein kinase1 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: Silencing FaRIPK1 expression by VIGS affects ripening-related processes and corresponding gene expression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaTPK1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/fragaria_ananassa/fatpk1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/fragaria_ananassa/fatpk1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: FaTPK1 Gene Name: two-pore potassium channel 1-like Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Description: FaTPK1 increased rapidly and was maintained at a high level in ripened fruit, which was coupled with the fruit&amp;rsquo;s red colour development, suggesting that FaTPK1 is related to fruit quality formation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaVPT1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/fragaria_ananassa/favpt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/fragaria_ananassa/favpt1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: FaVPT1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Description: Strawberry FaVPT1 transports Pi into vacuoles and promotes fruit ripening by sugar signaling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaβGal4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fa%CE%B2gal4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fa%CE%B2gal4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaβGal4 Gene Name: β-galactosidase 14 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: Antisense down-regulation of the strawberry β-galactosidase gene FaβGal4 increases cell wall galactose levels and reduces fruit softening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FveMYB10</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fvh4_1g22020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fvh4_1g22020/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: FvH4_1g22020 Gene Symbol: FveMYB10 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor 10 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: The R2R3-MYB transcription factor FveMYB10 is a major regulator of anthocyanin pigmentation in the red fruits of strawberry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FveMYB10L</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fvh4_1g22040/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/fvh4_1g22040/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: FvH4_1g22040 Gene Symbol: FveMYB10L Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor 10 Like Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: Using mapping-by-sequencing and transient functional assays, we confirmed that the causative mutation resides in a FveMYB10-Like (FveMYB10L) gene and that FveMYB10 and FveMYB10L function independently in the fruit and petiole, respectively.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
