<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Betula Platyphylla on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/betula-platyphylla/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Betula Platyphylla on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/betula-platyphylla/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BpbHLH9</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/betula-platyphylla/bpbhlh9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/betula-platyphylla/bpbhlh9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: BpbHLH9 Gene Name: bHLH transcription factor 9 Genome: Species: Betula platyphylla Functional Descriptions: Cloning and expression of BpMYC4 and BpbHLH9 genes and the role of BpbHLH9 in triterpenoid synthesis in birch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BpGLK1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/betula_platyphylla/bpglk1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/betula_platyphylla/bpglk1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: BpGLK1 Gene Name: Genome: B.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BpGRF3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/betula-platyphylla/bpchr01g18064/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/betula-platyphylla/bpchr01g18064/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: BPChr01G18064 Gene Symbol: BpGRF3 Gene Name: growth-regulating factor 3 Genome: Species: Betula platyphylla Functional Descriptions: BpGRF3 (growth-regulating factor 3) was identified as a regulatory factor upstream of BpGRP1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BpGRP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/betula-platyphylla/bpchr06g07927/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/betula-platyphylla/bpchr06g07927/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: BPChr06G07927 Gene Symbol: BpGRP1 Gene Name: glycine-rich RNA-binding protein 1 Genome: Species: Betula platyphylla Functional Descriptions: Identified BpGRP1 (glycine-rich RNA-binding protein), a Betula platyphylla gene that is induced under salt stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BpHOX2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/betula_platyphylla/bphox2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/betula_platyphylla/bphox2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: BpHOX2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Betula platyphylla Functional Description: BpHOX2 could induce the expression of pyrroline-5-carboxylate synthase, peroxidase, and superoxide dismutase genes to improve proline levels and the reactive oxygen species scavenging capability Literature: Betula platyphylla BpHOX2 transcription factor binds to different cis-acting elements and confers osmotic tolerance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BplncSIR1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/betula-platyphylla/bplncsir1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/betula-platyphylla/bplncsir1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: BplncSIR1 Gene Name: salt-responsive nuclear lncRNA Genome: Species: Betula platyphylla Functional Descriptions: Birch plants overexpressing and knocking out for BplncSIR1 were generated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BpNAC012</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/betula-platyphylla/bpnac012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/betula-platyphylla/bpnac012/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: BpNAC012 Gene Name: NAC transcription factor Genome: Species: Betula platyphylla Functional Descriptions: Gain- and loss-of-function analyses revealed that the transcript level of BpNAC012 was positively associated with salt and osmotic stress tolerance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BpTCP20</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/betula-platyphylla/bptcp20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/betula-platyphylla/bptcp20/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: BpTCP20 Gene Name: TCP transcription factor 20 Genome: Species: Betula platyphylla Functional Descriptions: Plants overexpressing BpTCP20 displayed increased salt tolerance, and BpTCP20 knockout mutants displayed reduced salt tolerance relative to the wild-type (WT) birch.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
