<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Signaling Pathway Gene on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/tags/signaling-pathway-gene/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Signaling Pathway Gene on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/tags/signaling-pathway-gene/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ClGH3.6</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clgh3.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clgh3.6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla97C05G096220 Gene Symbol: ClGH3.6 Gene Name: Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: Expression of the indole-3-acetic acid-amido synthetase gene ClGH3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClSnRK2.3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clsnrk2.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clsnrk2.3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla97C02G038540 Gene Symbol: ClSnRK2.3 Gene Name: Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: ClSnRK2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CmBBX19</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/chrysanthemum_morifolium/cmbbx19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/chrysanthemum_morifolium/cmbbx19/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;UN68402 Gene Symbol: CmBBX19 Gene Name: BBX19 protein Genome: Chrysanthemum genome v2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNGC</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g41710/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os02g41710/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os02g41710 RAPdb gene ID: Os02g0627700 Gene Symbol: CNGC Gene Name: Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsGSTU45</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/camellia_sinensis/csgstu45/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/camellia_sinensis/csgstu45/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: CsGSTU45 Gene Name: Genome: TeaPGDB V1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsLRR1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cslrr1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cucumis_sativus/cslrr1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;CsGy5G016190 Gene Symbol: CsLRR1 Gene Name: Genome: Cucumber (Gy14) v2 Genome Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: A single-nucleotide substitution in the Leucine-Rich-Repeat-only gene CsLRR1 confers powdery mildew resistance in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsUGT84J2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/tea000239/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/tea000239/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TEA000239 Gene Symbol: CsUGT84J2 Gene Name: Al-induced glycosyltransferase Genome: Species: Camellia sinensis Functional Descriptions: Found that flavonol glycoside levels in tea roots increased following Al treatment, and the Al-induced UDP glycosyltransferase CsUGT84J2 was involved in this mechanism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsWOX1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa1g042780/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa1g042780/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa1G042780 Gene Symbol: CsWOX1 Gene Name: WUSCHEL-related homeobox1 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: WUSCHEL-related homeobox1 (CsWOX1) regulates vein patterning and leaf size in Cucumis sativus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FcWRKY40</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-japonic/fcwrky40/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-japonic/fcwrky40/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FcWRKY40 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor 40 Genome: Species: Citrus japonic Functional Descriptions: The transcription factor FcWRKY40 of Fortunella crassifolia functions positively in salt tolerance through modulation of ion homeostasis and proline biosynthesis by directly regulating SOS2 and P5CS1 homologs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmENOD40-1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/glycine_max/gmenod40-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/glycine_max/gmenod40-1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.01G028500 Gene Symbol: GmENOD40-1 Gene Name: Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a2_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: The downstream nodulation marker gene GmENOD40-1 of the nodulation signaling pathway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GmNFYA-C</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/glycine_max/gmnfya-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/glycine_max/gmnfya-c/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Glyma.10G082800 Gene Symbol: GmNFYA-C Gene Name: Genome: Gmax_Wm82_a4_v1 Species: Glycine max Functional Descriptions: Overexpression of miR169c inhibited nodulation through targeting 3′-UTR of GmNFYA-C, whereas knockout miR169c through CRISPR-cas9 promoted nodulation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IbSnRK1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/ipomoea_batatas/ibsnrk1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/ipomoea_batatas/ibsnrk1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: IbSnRK1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Ipomoea batatas Functional Description: These results show that the IbSnRK1 gene confers salt, drought, and cold tolerance in sweet potato by activating the ROS scavenging system and controlling stomatal closure via the ABA signaling pathway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaTRE1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/lupinus-albus/lalb_chr05g0223881/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/lupinus-albus/lalb_chr05g0223881/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Lalb_Chr05g0223881 Gene Symbol: LaTRE1 Gene Name: TREHALASE1 Genome: Species: Lupinus albus Functional Descriptions: Under P deficiency, validamycin A treatment, which inhibits trehalase, led to the accumulation of trehalose and promoted the formation of CR with enhanced organic acid production, whereas overexpression of the white lupin TREHALASE1 (LaTRE1) led to decreased trehalose levels, lateral rootlet density, and organic acid production.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LrABCF1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/lilium-regale/lrabcf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/lilium-regale/lrabcf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: LrABCF1 Gene Name: ATP-binding cassette transporter1 Genome: Species: Lilium regale Functional Descriptions: LrABCF1, a GCN-type ATP-binding cassette transporter from Lilium regale, is involved in defense responses against viral and fungal pathogens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LsRGL1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/lactuca-sativa/lsat_1_v5_gn_2_69481.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/lactuca-sativa/lsat_1_v5_gn_2_69481.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Lsat_1_v5_gn_2_69481.1 Gene Symbol: LsRGL1 Gene Name: RGA-LIKE1 Genome: Species: Lactuca sativa Functional Descriptions: GA signaling protein LsRGL1 interacts with the abscisic acid signaling-related gene LsWRKY70 to affect the bolting of leaf lettuce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LsWRKY70</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/lactuca-sativa/lswrky70/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/lactuca-sativa/lswrky70/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: LsWRKY70 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Lactuca sativa Functional Descriptions: GA signaling protein LsRGL1 interacts with the abscisic acid signaling-related gene LsWRKY70 to affect the bolting of leaf lettuce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LuWRKY36</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/linum-usitatissimum/lus10026409/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/linum-usitatissimum/lus10026409/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Lus10026409 Gene Symbol: LuWRKY36 Gene Name: Genome: Linum usitatissimum genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdBRC1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdbrc1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdbrc1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MdBRC1 Gene Name: BRANCHED1 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: Strigolactone regulates adventitious root formation via the MdSMXL7-MdWRKY6-MdBRC1 signaling cascade in apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdMYC2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000029168/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000029168/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000029168 Gene Symbol: MdMYC2 Gene Name: Jasmonate-Activated Transcription Factor 2 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: MdMYC2 is a homology of Arabidopsis MYC2 in apple, it has highly similarity in structure and function to the Arabidopsis MYC2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsMADS56;GL10</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os10g39130/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os10g39130/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os10g39130 RAPdb gene ID: Os10g0536100 Gene Symbol: OsMADS56 GL10 Gene Name: Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PtrXB38</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/populus-trichocarpa/potri.010g070800.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/populus-trichocarpa/potri.010g070800.6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Potri.010G070800.6 Gene Symbol: PtrXB38 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Populus trichocarpa Functional Descriptions: Expression quantitative trait loci mapping identified PtrXB38 as a key hub gene in adventitious root development in Populus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PvTIFY10C</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/phaseolus-vulgaris/phvul.002g002000.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/phaseolus-vulgaris/phvul.002g002000.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Phvul.002G002000.1 Gene Symbol: PvTIFY10C Gene Name: TIFY transcription factor Genome: Species: Phaseolus vulgaris Functional Descriptions: Common bean (Phaseolus vulgarisL.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlARF7</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/slarf7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/slarf7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SlARF7 Gene Name: AUXIN RESPONSE FACTOR 7 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: The Solanum lycopersicum auxin response factor 7 (SlARF7) regulates auxin signaling during tomato fruit set and development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlMBF1c</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc07g062400.3.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc07g062400.3.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc07g062400.3.1 Gene Symbol: SlMBF1c Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Comprehensive analysis of multiprotein bridging factor 1 family genes and SlMBF1c negatively regulate the resistance to Botrytis cinerea in tomato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ST6</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr3g107810/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr3g107810/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr3g107810 Gene Symbol: ST6 Gene Name: Specific tissue protein 6 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Specific tissue proteins 1 and 6 are involved in root biology during normal development and under symbiotic and pathogenic interactions in Medicago truncatula.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUN24</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/sun24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/sun24/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SUN24 Gene Name: IQ domain-containing calmodulin-binding protein SUN24 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: The tomato IQD gene SUN24 regulates seed germination through ABA signaling pathway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaCRK3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/triticum-aestivum/traescs7a02g105100.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/triticum-aestivum/traescs7a02g105100.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS7A02G105100.1 Gene Symbol: TaCRK3 Gene Name: cysteine-rich receptor-like kinase 3 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: The cysteine-rich receptor-like kinase TaCRK3 contributes to defense against Rhizoctonia cerealis in wheat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaCRTISO-1B</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/triticum-aestivum/traescs1b02g090300/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/triticum-aestivum/traescs1b02g090300/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS1B02G090300 Gene Symbol: TaCRTISO-1B Gene Name: CAROTENOID ISOMERASE-1B Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaGBF1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/triticum-aestivum/tagbf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/triticum-aestivum/tagbf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaGBF1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: The wheat TaGBF1 gene is involved in the blue-light response and salt tolerance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaMED25-A</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/triticum-aestivum/tamed25-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/triticum-aestivum/tamed25-a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaMED25-A Gene Name: Mediator subunit 25 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: The Wheat Mediator Subunit TaMED25 Interacts with the Transcription Factor TaEIL1 to Negatively Regulate Disease Resistance against Powdery Mildew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaMED25-B</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/triticum-aestivum/tamed25-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/triticum-aestivum/tamed25-b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaMED25-B Gene Name: Mediator subunit 25 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: The Wheat Mediator Subunit TaMED25 Interacts with the Transcription Factor TaEIL1 to Negatively Regulate Disease Resistance against Powdery Mildew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaMED25-D</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/triticum-aestivum/tamed25-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/triticum-aestivum/tamed25-d/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaMED25-D Gene Name: Mediator subunit 25 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: The Wheat Mediator Subunit TaMED25 Interacts with the Transcription Factor TaEIL1 to Negatively Regulate Disease Resistance against Powdery Mildew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaOPR1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/triticum-aestivum/taopr1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/triticum-aestivum/taopr1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: TaOPR1 Gene Name: Oxophytodienoate Reductase 1 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Wheat Oxophytodienoate Reductase Gene TaOPR1 Confers Salinity Tolerance via Enhancement of Abscisic Acid Signaling and Reactive Oxygen Species Scavenging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaSPL8</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/triticum-aestivum/traescs2d01g502900/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/triticum-aestivum/traescs2d01g502900/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TraesCS2D01G502900 Gene Symbol: TaSPL8 Gene Name: SQUAMOSA PROMOTER BINDING-LIKE 8 Genome: Species: Triticum aestivum Functional Descriptions: Wheat TaSPL8 Modulates Leaf Angle Through Auxin and Brassinosteroid Signaling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaSRL1-4A</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/triticum_aestivum/tasrl1-4a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/triticum_aestivum/tasrl1-4a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS4A02G005600 Gene Symbol: TaSRL1-4A Gene Name: SHORT ROOT LENGTH 1 Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaSRL1-4B</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/triticum_aestivum/tasrl1-4b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/triticum_aestivum/tasrl1-4b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS4B02G299400 Gene Symbol: TaSRL1-4B Gene Name: SHORT ROOT LENGTH 1 Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaSRL1-4D</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/triticum_aestivum/tasrl1-4d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/triticum_aestivum/tasrl1-4d/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TraesCS4D02G298400 Gene Symbol: TaSRL1-4D Gene Name: SHORT ROOT LENGTH 1 Genome: Chinese_Spring1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmAPX1;apx3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/zea_mays/zmapx1apx3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/zea_mays/zmapx1apx3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb013080 Gene Symbol: ZmAPX1 apx3 Gene Name: ascorbate peroxidase 1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmAPX1;ZmAPx01</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/zea_mays/zmapx1zmapx01zmapx1.1apx3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/zea_mays/zmapx1zmapx01zmapx1.1apx3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb013080 Gene Symbol: ZmAPX1 ZmAPx01 ZmAPX1.1 apx3 Gene Name: ascorbate peroxidase homolog3 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmGLP1;glp1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/zea_mays/zmglp1glp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/zea_mays/zmglp1glp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb282040 Gene Symbol: ZmGLP1 glp1 Gene Name: germin-like protein1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmGSK2;ZmSK1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/zea_mays/zmgsk2zmsk1gsk2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/zea_mays/zmgsk2zmsk1gsk2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb338190 Gene Symbol: ZmGSK2 ZmSK1 gsk2 Gene Name: glycogen synthase kinase2 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmMYC7;ZmMYC2a</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/zea_mays/zmmyc7zmmyc2abhlh149zmmyc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/zea_mays/zmmyc7zmmyc2abhlh149zmmyc2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb024330 Gene Symbol: ZmMYC7 ZmMYC2a bhlh149 ZmMYC2 Gene Name: myc transcription factor7 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmSTG1;stg1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/zea_mays/zmstg1stg1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/zea_mays/zmstg1stg1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb388110 Gene Symbol: ZmSTG1 stg1 Gene Name: Salt-Tolerant Gene 1 Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZmYODA</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/zea_mays/zmyoda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/zea_mays/zmyoda/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Zm00001eb186910 Gene Symbol: ZmYODA Gene Name: Genome: Zm-B73-REFERENCE-NAM-5.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
