<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Citrullus Lanatus on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/citrullus-lanatus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Citrullus Lanatus on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/citrullus-lanatus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ACS7</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/acs7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/acs7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla97C03G066100 Gene Symbol: ACS7 Gene Name: carboxylate synthase 7 Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: An allelic variant in the ACS7 gene promotes primary root growth in watermelon。 The ACS7 expression and ethylene levels in the primary root tips suggested that ethylene is a negative regulator of root elongation in watermelon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClAGA2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrullus-lanatus/cla97c04g070460/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrullus-lanatus/cla97c04g070460/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cla97C04G070460 Gene Symbol: ClAGA2 Gene Name: alkaline alpha-galactosidase Genome: Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: Through a genome-wide association study, the alkaline alpha-galactosidase ClAGA2 was identified as the key factor controlling stachyose and Raf hydrolysis, and it was determined to be specifically expressed in the vascular bundle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClAGO1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clago1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clago1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla97C04G079510 Gene Symbol: ClAGO1 Gene Name: Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: ClAGO1 and ClAGO5 expression levels were highly induced by CGMMV infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClAGO5</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clago5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clago5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla97C01G012980 Gene Symbol: ClAGO5 Gene Name: Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: ClAGO1 and ClAGO5 expression levels were highly induced by CGMMV infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClATM1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clatm1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clatm1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla010576 Gene Symbol: ClATM1 Gene Name: Citrullus lanatus Abnormal Tapetum 1 Genome: latermelon database 97103 V1 (http://cucurbitgenomics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClBG1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clbg1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clbg1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla97C08G153160 Gene Symbol: ClBG1 Gene Name: Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: CRISPR/Cas9-mediated mutagenesis of ClBG1 decreased seed size and promoted seed germination in watermelon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cldf</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/cldf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/cldf/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla015407 Gene Symbol: Cldf Gene Name: Genome: latermelon database 97103 V1 (http://cucurbitgenomics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClDMP4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/cldmp4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/cldmp4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla97C06G121370 Gene Symbol: ClDMP4 Gene Name: Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: ClDMP4,which is specifically expressed in male flower buds and pollen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClERF4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clerf4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clerf4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: ClERF4 Gene Name: ethylene-responsive transcription factor 4 Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: ClERF4 in regulating watermelon rind hardness and implied that ethylene is a common regulator of fruit firmness in both climacteric and nonclimacteric fruits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClGH3.6</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clgh3.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clgh3.6/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla97C05G096220 Gene Symbol: ClGH3.6 Gene Name: Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: Expression of the indole-3-acetic acid-amido synthetase gene ClGH3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClGIF1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clgif1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clgif1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla97C02G042620 Gene Symbol: ClGIF1 Gene Name: Citrullus lanatus GRF-INTERACTING FACTOR1 Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: By overexpressing a chimeric fusion of ClGRF4 and ClGIF1, we achieved highly efficient transformation in watermelon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClGRF4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clgrf4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clgrf4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla97C02G034420 Gene Symbol: ClGRF4 Gene Name: Citrullus lanatus GROWTH-REGULATING FACTOR4 Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: By overexpressing a chimeric fusion of ClGRF4 and ClGIF1, we achieved highly efficient transformation in watermelon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClINV</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clinv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clinv/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla97C10G201810 Gene Symbol: ClINV Gene Name: Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: Transcriptome analysis showed that the invertase gene ClINV was the only gene involved in sucrose metabolism that was upregulated in mutant flesh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClLCYB</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrullus-lanatus/cla97c04g070940/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrullus-lanatus/cla97c04g070940/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cla97C04G070940 Gene Symbol: ClLCYB Gene Name: lycopene β-cyclase Genome: [watermelon reference v2 genome](http://cucurbitgenomics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClNAC68</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clnac68/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clnac68/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla97C03G059250 Gene Symbol: ClNAC68 Gene Name: Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: The NAC transcription factor ClNAC68 positively regulates sugar content and seed development in watermelon by repressing ClINV and ClGH3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clpsk1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clpsk1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clpsk1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla97C01G016930 Gene Symbol: Clpsk1 Gene Name: Gene_name:Citrullus lanatus Phytosulfokine1 Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: Resistance evaluation indicated that Clpsk1 loss-of-function renderedwatermelon seedlings more resistant to infection by FON.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClPsy1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrullus-lanatus/cla97c01g008760/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrullus-lanatus/cla97c01g008760/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cla97C01G008760 Gene Symbol: ClPsy1 Gene Name: phytoene synthase 1 Genome: Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: Nucleotide variation in the phytoene synthase (ClPsy1) gene contributes to golden flesh in watermelon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClSnRK2.3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clsnrk2.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clsnrk2.3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla97C02G038540 Gene Symbol: ClSnRK2.3 Gene Name: Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (97103) v2) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: ClSnRK2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClSWEET3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrullus-lanatus/cla97c01g000640/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrullus-lanatus/cla97c01g000640/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cla97C01G000640 Gene Symbol: ClSWEET3 Gene Name: Sugars Will Eventually Be Exported Transporter 3 Genome: [watermelon reference v2 genome](http://cucurbitgenomics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClTST2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/cltst2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/cltst2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cla000264 ; Cla97C02G036390 Gene Symbol: ClTST2 Gene Name: Tonoplast Sugar Transporter gene2 Genome: latermelon database 97103 V1 Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: Molecular and biochemical analyses indicated that ClTST2 encodes a vacuolar membrane protein, whose expression is associated with tonoplast uptake and accumulation of sugars in watermelon fruit flesh cells.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClVST1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrullus-lanatus/cla97c02g031010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/citrullus-lanatus/cla97c02g031010/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cla97C02G031010 Gene Symbol: ClVST1 Gene Name: vacuolar sugar transporter Genome: watermelon genome database Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: Report a novel vacuolar sugar transporter (ClVST1) identified through map-based cloning and association study, whose expression in fruit phloem is associated with accumulation of sucrose (Suc) in watermelon fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClWIP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrullus-lanatus/cla008537/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrullus-lanatus/cla008537/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Cla008537 Gene Symbol: ClWIP1 Gene Name: C2H2 zinc finger transcription factor Genome: Cucurbit Genomics Database Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: A putative C2H2 zinc finger transcription factor gene, ClWIP1 (gene ID Cla008537), an orthologue of the melon gynoecy gene CmWIP1, was disrupted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClWPRb</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clwprb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrullus_lanatus/clwprb/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;ClCG04G006480 Gene Symbol: ClWPRb Gene Name: Genome: Citrullus lanatus (Watermelon (Charleston Gray)) Species: Citrullus lanatus Functional Descriptions: Interactions between WPRb and the MP of CGMMV lead to the restriction of viral movement in plants.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
