<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Medicago Sativa on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/medicago-sativa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Medicago Sativa on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/medicago-sativa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MfAOC2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_sativa/mfaoc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_sativa/mfaoc2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MfAOC2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Medicago sativa Functional Descriptions: These results suggest that expression of MfAOC2 or MtAOC2 promotes biosynthesis of JA, which positively regulates expression of CBF genes and antioxidant defense under cold conditions and expression of JA downstream genes after pathogen infection, leading to greater cold tolerance and pathogen resistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MsDHN1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_sativa/msdhn1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_sativa/msdhn1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MsDHN1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Medicago sativa Functional Descriptions: These results indicate that MsDHN1 can increase alfalfa tolerance to Al stress via increasing oxalate secretion from root tips, which may involve in the interaction of MsDHN1 with two AQP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MsDIUP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_sativa/msdiup1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_sativa/msdiup1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MsDIUP1 Gene Name: Medicago sativa DROUGHT-INDUCED UNKNOWN PROTEIN 1 Genome: whole genome sequencing and assembly of Medicago sativa Species: Medicago sativa Functional Descriptions: Taken together, these results reveal a positive role for MsDIUP1 in regulating drought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MsFLS13</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_sativa/msfls13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_sativa/msfls13/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MsFLS13 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Medicago sativa Functional Descriptions: Our findings highlight the crucial role of MsFLS13 in alfalfa in response to saline-alkali stress and provide a novel genetic resource for creating saline-alkali-resistant alfalfa through genetic engineering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MsFTa1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_sativa/msfta1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_sativa/msfta1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MsFTa1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Medicago sativa Functional Descriptions: Improvement of alfalfa forage quality and management through the down-regulation of MsFTa1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MsLEA1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/mslea1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/mslea1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MsLEA1 Gene Name: Late embryogenesis-abundant (LEA) 1 Genome: alfalfa genome(https://sciencedirect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MsLEA1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_sativa/mslea1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_sativa/mslea1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MS.gene058705 Gene Symbol: MsLEA1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Medicago sativa Functional Descriptions: These results indicate that MsLEA1 recruits and protects its target proteins (SOD and Ms1770) and increases alfalfa tolerance against drought and Al stresses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MsNST1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_sativa/msnst1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_sativa/msnst1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MsNST1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Medicago sativa Functional Descriptions: These results suggest that MsNST1 affects lignin synthesis in alfalfa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MsPLP</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_sativa/msplp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/medicago_sativa/msplp/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MsPLP Gene Name: Genome: Species: Medicago sativa Functional Descriptions: Down-regulation of MsPLP results in altered pulvinus structure with increased leaflet breakstrength, thus offering a new approach to decrease leaf loss during alfalfa haymaking process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MsRBR</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-sativa/msrbr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-sativa/msrbr/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MsRBR Gene Name: Retinoblastoma-related protein Genome: Species: Medicago sativa Functional Descriptions: Roscovitine treatment abolished the activity of alfalfa MsCDKA1|1 and MsCDKB2|1, and the phospho-MsRBR protein level was significantly decreased in the treated cells.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MsSPSA</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-sativa/msspsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-sativa/msspsa/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MsSPSA Gene Name: sucrose phosphate synthase Genome: Species: Medicago sativa Functional Descriptions: Nodule-enhanced expression of a sucrose phosphate synthase gene member (MsSPSA) has a role in carbon and nitrogen metabolism in the nodules of alfalfa.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
