<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pyrus Pyrifolia on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/pyrus-pyrifolia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pyrus Pyrifolia on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/pyrus-pyrifolia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PbrARI2.3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/pbrari2.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/pbrari2.3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Pbr020065.1 Gene Symbol: PbrARI2.3 Gene Name: Genome: Pear Genome Project database (http://dx.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PbrBZR1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/pbrbzr1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/pbrbzr1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Pbr020081.1 Gene Symbol: PbrBZR1 Gene Name: Genome: Pear Genome Project database (http://dx.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PbrEXLA3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/pbrexla3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/pbrexla3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Pbr033313.1 Gene Symbol: PbrEXLA3 Gene Name: Genome: Pear Genome Project database (http://dx.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PbrSTONE</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/pbrstone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/pbrstone/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Pbr005042 Gene Symbol: PbrSTONE Gene Name: Genome: Pyrus bretschneideri genome Species: Pyrus pyrifolia Functional Description: One candidate gene, PbrSTONE, identified in GWAS, has been functionally verified to be involved in the regulation of stone cell formation, one of the most important fruit quality traits in pear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PpBBX16</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/ppbbx16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/ppbbx16/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Pbr020473.1 Gene Symbol: PpBBX16 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Pyrus pyrifolia Functional Description: Our work uncovered regulatory modes for PpBBX16 and suggested the potential functions of other pear BBX genes in the regulation of anthocyanin accumulation, thereby providing target genes for further studies on anthocyanin biosynthesis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PpbHLH64</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/ppbhlh64/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/ppbhlh64/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Pbr001646.1 Gene Symbol: PpbHLH64 Gene Name: Genome: pear genome database available online (http://peargenome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PpERF105</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-pyrifolia/pperf105/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-pyrifolia/pperf105/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PpERF105 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Pyrus pyrifolia Functional Descriptions: Ethylene-activated PpERF105 induces the expression of the repressor-type R2R3-MYB gene PpMYB140 to inhibit anthocyanin biosynthesis in red pear fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PpERF9</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/pperf9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/pperf9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Pbr000398.1 Gene Symbol: PpERF9 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Pyrus pyrifolia Functional Description: Collectively, these results indicate that ethylene inhibits anthocyanin biosynthesis by a mechanism that involves PpERF9-PpTPL1 complex-mediated histone deacetylation of PpMYB114 and PpRAP2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PpMYB114</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/ppmyb114/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/ppmyb114/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Pbr042132.1 Gene Symbol: PpMYB114 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Pyrus pyrifolia Functional Description: Collectively, these results indicate that ethylene inhibits anthocyanin biosynthesis by a mechanism that involves PpERF9-PpTPL1 complex-mediated histone deacetylation of PpMYB114 and PpRAP2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PpMYB140</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-pyrifolia/pbr000876.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-pyrifolia/pbr000876.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Pbr000876.1 Gene Symbol: PpMYB140 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Pyrus pyrifolia Functional Descriptions: Ethylene-activated PpERF105 induces the expression of the repressor-type R2R3-MYB gene PpMYB140 to inhibit anthocyanin biosynthesis in red pear fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PpRAP2.4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/pprap2.4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/pprap2.4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Pbr016049.2 Gene Symbol: PpRAP2.4 Gene Name: PpRELATED TO APETALA2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PpTFL1-1a</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-pyrifolia/tcons_00012718/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-pyrifolia/tcons_00012718/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TCONS_00012718 Gene Symbol: PpTFL1-1a Gene Name: TERMINAL FLOWER1 Genome: Species: Pyrus pyrifolia Functional Descriptions: The induction of the productive meristem identity MADS-box gene AP1 after repression of PpTFL1s suggested a primary role for PpTFL1 in floral induction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PpTFL1-2a</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-pyrifolia/tcons_00029789/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-pyrifolia/tcons_00029789/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: TCONS_00029789 Gene Symbol: PpTFL1-2a Gene Name: TERMINAL FLOWER1 Genome: Species: Pyrus pyrifolia Functional Descriptions: The induction of the productive meristem identity MADS-box gene AP1 after repression of PpTFL1s suggested a primary role for PpTFL1 in floral induction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PybZIPa</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/pybzipa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/pybzipa/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: PybZIPa Gene Name: Genome: Species: Pyrus pyrifolia Functional Description: Dual luciferase and Y1H assays further verified that PybZIPa directly activated the expression of PyUFGT by binding to tandem G-box motifs in the promoter, which was key to differential anthocyanin accumulation in debagged pear skin, and the number of G-box motifs affected the transcriptional activation of PyUFGT by PybZIPa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyUFGT</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/pyufgt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/pyrus_pyrifolia/pyufgt/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: PyUFGT Gene Name: Genome: Species: Pyrus pyrifolia Functional Description: Dual luciferase and Y1H assays further verified that PybZIPa directly activated the expression of PyUFGT by binding to tandem G-box motifs in the promoter, which was key to differential anthocyanin accumulation in debagged pear skin, and the number of G-box motifs affected the transcriptional activation of PyUFGT by PybZIPa.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
