<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nicotiana Tabacum on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/nicotiana-tabacum/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nicotiana Tabacum on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/nicotiana-tabacum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nt-RhoGDI2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/nt-rhogdi2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/nt-rhogdi2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: Nt-RhoGDI2 Gene Name: Pollen tube RhoGDI2 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: Nt-RhoGDI2 regulates Rac/Rop signaling and polar cell growth in tobacco pollen tubes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtALS1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/nitab4.5_0001530g0160.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/nitab4.5_0001530g0160.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Nitab4.5_0001530g0160.1 Gene Symbol: NtALS1 Gene Name: acetolactate synthase1 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: The trichome-specific acetolactate synthase NtALS1 gene, is involved in acylsugar biosynthesis in tobacco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ntann12</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-tabacum/ntann12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-tabacum/ntann12/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: Ntann12 Gene Name: Annexin 12 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: The tobacco Ntann12 gene, encoding an annexin, is induced upon Rhodoccocus fascians infection and during leafy gall development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtAQP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-tabacum/ntaqp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-tabacum/ntaqp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtAQP1 Gene Name: Aquaporin 1 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: Tobacco aquaporin NtAQP1 is involved in mesophyll conductance to CO2in vivo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtbHLH1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntbhlh1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntbhlh1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtbHLH1 Gene Name: basic helix-loop-helix 1 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: NtbHLH1, a JAF13-like bHLH, interacts with NtMYB6 to enhance proanthocyanidin accumulation in Chinese Narcissus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtbHLH123</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_tabacum/ntbhlh123/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_tabacum/ntbhlh123/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: NtbHLH123 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Description: Our data show that NtbHLH123 is a positive regulator and acts as a molecular switch to control a Rboh-dependent mechanism in response to salt stress in plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtCdc27B1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntcdc27b1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntcdc27b1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtCdc27B1 Gene Name: cell division cycle 27 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: Suppression of Cdc27B expression induces plant defence responses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtCdc27B2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntcdc27b2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntcdc27b2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtCdc27B2 Gene Name: cell division cycle 27 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: Suppression of Cdc27B expression induces plant defence responses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtCP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-tabacum/ntcp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-tabacum/ntcp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtCP1 Gene Name: cysteine protease 1 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: NtCP1 encoding a C-terminus partial sequence of a putative tobacco cysteine proteinase gene whereas the 1300 bp fragment (NtCP2) is a full-length cysteine proteinase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtCP2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-tabacum/ntcp2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-tabacum/ntcp2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtCP2 Gene Name: cysteine protease 2 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: NtCP2 has a high similarity to KDEL-tailed cysteine proteinases and is expressed in mature green leaves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtERF172</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_tabacum/nterf172/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_tabacum/nterf172/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: NtERF172 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Description: We propose that NtERF172 acts as a positive factor in drought stress tolerance, at least in part through the regulation of CAT-mediated H2O2 homeostasis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtFAD2–2a</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntfad22a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntfad22a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtFAD2–2a Gene Name: Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: We suggested that mutation of the seed-type NtFAD2–2 genes will not affect the fatty acid desaturation in tobacco leaves, because of the function redundancy of NtFAD2–1 genes in vegetative tissues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtFAD2–2b</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntfad22b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntfad22b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtFAD2–2b Gene Name: Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: We suggested that mutation of the seed-type NtFAD2–2 genes will not affect the fatty acid desaturation in tobacco leaves, because of the function redundancy of NtFAD2–1 genes in vegetative tissues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtGA20ox1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-tabacum/ntga20ox1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-tabacum/ntga20ox1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtGA20ox1 Gene Name: gibberellin 20-oxidase Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: The transcription factor RSG regulates negative feedback of NtGA20ox1 encoding GA 20-oxidase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtGNL1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntgnl1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntgnl1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtGNL1 Gene Name: GNOM-like 1 protein Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: NtGNL1 is involved in embryonic cell division patterning, root elongation, and pollen tube growth in tobacco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtGNL1a</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntgnl1a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntgnl1a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtGNL1a Gene Name: GNOM-LIKE protein1a Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: NtGNL1a ARF-GEF acts in endocytosis in tobacco cells.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtGSNOR1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_tabacum/ntgsnor1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_tabacum/ntgsnor1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: NtGSNOR1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Description: our results indicate that NtGSNOR1 functions as both positive and negative regulator of cell death under different conditions and displays distinct effects on resistance against viral and bacterial pathogens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtHD12</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nthd12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nthd12/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtHD12 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: Transcription factors NtHD9 and NtHD12 control long glandular trichome formation via jasmonate signaling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtHD9-1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/nthd9-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/nthd9-1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtHD9-1 Gene Name: homeodomain leucine zipper II member 9 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: Transcription factors NtHD9 and NtHD12 control long glandular trichome formation via jasmonate signaling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtHD9-2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/nthd9-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/nthd9-2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtHD9-2 Gene Name: homeodomain leucine zipper II member 9 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: Transcription factors NtHD9 and NtHD12 control long glandular trichome formation via jasmonate signaling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtKRP</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntkrp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntkrp/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtKRP Gene Name: kinesin-related protein Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: Ribosomal protein NtRPL17 interacts with kinesin-12 family protein NtKRP and functions in the regulation of embryo/seed size and radicle growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtLTP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-tabacum/ntltp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-tabacum/ntltp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtLTP1 Gene Name: Non-specific lipid-transfer protein Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: Tobacco NtLTP1, a glandular-specific lipid transfer protein, is required for lipid secretion from glandular trichomes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtMATE21</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntmate21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntmate21/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtMATE21 Gene Name: multidrug and toxic compound extrusion21 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: NtMATE21 and NtMATE22, and demonstrate their role in flavonol transport and in plant growth and development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtMATE22</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntmate22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntmate22/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtMATE22 Gene Name: multidrug and toxic compound extrusion22 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: NtMATE21 and NtMATE22, and demonstrate their role in flavonol transport and in plant growth and development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtMET1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-tabacum/ntmet1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-tabacum/ntmet1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtMET1 Gene Name: DNA (cytosine-5)-methyltransferase1 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: A Tobacco NtMET1 cDNA Encoding a DNA Methyltransferase: Molecular Characterization and Abnormal Phenotypes of Transgenic Tobacco Plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtMPK4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntmpk4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntmpk4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtMPK4 Gene Name: mitogen-activated protein kinase4 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: Silencing of NtMPK4 impairs CO2-induced stomatal closure, activation of anion channels and cytosolic Ca2+signals in Nicotiana tabacum guard cells.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtMYB305a</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_tabacum/ntmyb305a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_tabacum/ntmyb305a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: NtMYB305a Gene Name: Genome: genome of N.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtMYBJS1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntmybjs1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntmybjs1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtMYBJS1 Gene Name: Methyl jasmonate induced MYB-related Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: A novel R2R3 MYB transcription factor NtMYBJS1 is a methyl jasmonate-dependent regulator of phenylpropanoid-conjugate biosynthesis in tobacco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtMYC2a</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-tabacum/ntmyc2a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-tabacum/ntmyc2a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtMYC2a Gene Name: MYC2a transcription factor Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: Tobacco Transcription Factors NtMYC2a and NtMYC2b Form Nuclear Complexes with the NtJAZ1 Repressor and Regulate Multiple Jasmonate-Inducible Steps in Nicotine Biosynthesis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtMYC2b</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-tabacum/ntmyc2b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-tabacum/ntmyc2b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtMYC2b Gene Name: MYC2b transcription factor Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: Tobacco Transcription Factors NtMYC2a and NtMYC2b Form Nuclear Complexes with the NtJAZ1 Repressor and Regulate Multiple Jasmonate-Inducible Steps in Nicotine Biosynthesis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtNAC028</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntnac028/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntnac028/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtNAC028 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: Transcription factors NtNAC028 and NtNAC080 form heterodimers to regulate jasmonic acid biosynthesis during leaf senescence in Nicotiana tabacum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtNAC080</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntnac080/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntnac080/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtNAC080 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: Transcription factors NtNAC028 and NtNAC080 form heterodimers to regulate jasmonic acid biosynthesis during leaf senescence in Nicotiana tabacum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtPDR3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntpdr3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntpdr3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtPDR3 Gene Name: pleiotropic drug resistance protein 3 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: The Nicotiana tabacum ABC transporter NtPDR3 secretes O-methylated coumarins in response to iron deficiency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtRFP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntrfp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntrfp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtRFP1 Gene Name: RING-finger protein 1 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: Tobacco RING E3 Ligase NtRFP1 Mediates Ubiquitination and Proteasomal Degradation of a Geminivirus-Encoded βC1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtRHO1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntrho1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntrho1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtRHO1 Gene Name: Rho-type GTPase 1 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: The small GTPase NtRHO1 negatively regulates tobacco defense response to tobacco mosaic virus by interacting with NtWRKY50.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtRPL17</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntrpl17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntrpl17/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtRPL17 Gene Name: 60S ribosomal protein L17 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: Ribosomal protein NtRPL17 interacts with kinesin-12 family protein NtKRP and functions in the regulation of embryo/seed size and radicle growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtSCP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntscp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntscp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtSCP1 Gene Name: serine carboxypeptidase III Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: We isolated cDNAs for two extracellular serine carboxypeptidase III genes from tobacco (Nicotiana tabacum), NtSCP1 and NtSCP2, belonging to a phylogenetic clade not yet functionally characterized in plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtsTOM2A</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_tabacum/ntstom2a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_tabacum/ntstom2a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: NtsTOM2A Gene Name: Genome: www.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NttTOM2A</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_tabacum/ntttom2a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_tabacum/ntttom2a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: NttTOM2A Gene Name: Genome: www.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhoGAP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/rhogap1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/rhogap1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhoGAP1 Gene Name: GTPase activating protein1 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: In vivo Rac/Rop localization as well as interaction with RhoGAP and RhoGDI in tobacco pollen tubes: analysis by low-level expression of fluorescent fusion proteins and bimolecular fluorescence complementation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhoGDI2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/rhogdi2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/rhogdi2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhoGDI2 Gene Name: Guanine Nucleotide Dissociation Inhibitor2 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: Bimolecular fluorescence complementation analysis shows in vivo interaction between wild type Nt-Rac5 and Nt-RhoGDI2 fusion proteins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROX1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/rox1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/rox1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: ROX1 Gene Name: Putative ROX1 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: ROX1, a gene induced by rolB, is involved in procambial cell proliferation and xylem differentiation in tobacco stamen.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
