<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Musa Acuminata on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/musa-acuminata/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Musa Acuminata on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/musa-acuminata/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MaACO1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma07_t19730.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma07_t19730.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ma07_t19730.1 Gene Symbol: MaACO1 Gene Name: aminocyclopropane-1-carboxylate oxidase 1 Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: CRISPR/Cas9-mediated genome editing of MaACO1 (aminocyclopropane-1-carboxylate oxidase 1) promotes the shelf life of banana fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaBAH1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma05_g02600/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma05_g02600/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ma05_g02600 Gene Symbol: MaBAH1 Gene Name: benzoic acid hypersensitive 1 Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: Proteasomal degradation of MaMYB60 mediated by the E3 ligase MaBAH1 causes high temperature-induced repression of chlorophyll catabolism and green ripening in banana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaBEL1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma01_g01710/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma01_g01710/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ma01_g01710 Gene Symbol: MaBEL1 Gene Name: BEL1-LIKE HOMEODOMAIN transcription factor 1 Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: MaBEL1 regulates banana fruit ripening by activating cell wall and starch degradation-related genes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaC2H2-IDD</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/mac2h2-idd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/mac2h2-idd/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MaC2H2-IDD Gene Name: Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: MaC2H2-IDD regulates fruit softening and involved in softening disorder induced by cold stress in banana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaDof23</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/gsmua_achr11t03360_001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/gsmua_achr11t03360_001/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: GSMUA_Achr11T03360_001 Gene Symbol: MaDof23 Gene Name: Putative Dof zinc finger protein DOF4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaDREB2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/gsmua_achr5g28050_001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/gsmua_achr5g28050_001/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: GSMUA_Achr5G28050_001 Gene Symbol: MaDREB2 Gene Name: dehydration-responsive element binding 2 Genome: The Banana Genome Hub (http://banana-genome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaERF11</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/maerf11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/maerf11/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MaERF11 Gene Name: ETHYLENE RESPONSE FACTOR11 Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: Banana Transcription Factor MaERF11 Recruits Histone Deacetylase MaHDA1 and Represses the Expression of MaACO1 and Expansins during Fruit Ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaICE1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/maice1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/maice1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MaICE1 Gene Name: transcription factor ICE1 Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: Banana fruit NAC transcription factor MaNAC1 is a direct target of MaICE1 and involved in cold stress through interacting with MaCBF1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaMADS1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/mamads1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/mamads1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MaMADS1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: MaMADS1–MaNAC083 transcriptional regulatory cascade regulates ethylene biosynthesis during banana fruit ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaMADS2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/gsmua_achr4t29150/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/gsmua_achr4t29150/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: GSMUA_Achr4T29150 Gene Symbol: MaMADS2 Gene Name: Genome: banana genome hub website (http://banana-genome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaMADS36</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/musa_acuminata/mamads36/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/musa_acuminata/mamads36/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Ma05_g18560.1 Gene Symbol: MaMADS36 Gene Name: MADS-box transcription factor 36 Genome: banana A genome Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: Our findings revealed that MaMADS36 directly binds to the CA/T(r)G box of the MaBAM9b promoter to increase MaBAM9b transcription and, in turn, enzyme activity and starch degradation during ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaMAPK3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma06_g34790/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma06_g34790/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ma06_g34790 Gene Symbol: MaMAPK3|MaMAPK3a Gene Name: Genome: genome database of Musa (http://banana-genome-hub.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaMPK14</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma04_g03880/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma04_g03880/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ma04_g03880 Gene Symbol: MaMPK14 Gene Name: Mitogen-activated protein kinase 14 Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: MaMPK14 cooperated with MaMYB4 to mediate postharvest banana fruit ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaMYB16L</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/musa_acuminata/mamyb16l/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/musa_acuminata/mamyb16l/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: MaMYB16L Gene Name: Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: The alternative splicing of MaMYB16L might generate a self-controlled regulatory loop to regulate banana fruit ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaMYB3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma06_g11140/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma06_g11140/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ma06_g11140 Gene Symbol: MaMYB3 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor 3 Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: A banana R2R3-MYB transcription factor MaMYB3 is involved in fruit ripening through modulation of starch degradation by repressing starch degradation-related genes and MabHLH6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaMYB4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/musa_acuminata/mamyb4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/musa_acuminata/mamyb4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Ma03_g21920 Gene Symbol: MaMYB4 Gene Name: Genome: banana A genome Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: We demonstrate that MaMYB4 negatively modulates banana fruit ripening, and that MaMYB4 abundance could be regulated by protein ubiquitination, thus providing insights into the role of MaMYB4 in controlling fruit ripening at both transcriptional and post-translational levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaMYB60</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma04_g00460.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma04_g00460.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ma04_g00460.1 Gene Symbol: MaMYB60 Gene Name: Musa acuminata Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: Proteasomal degradation of MaMYB60 mediated by the E3 ligase MaBAH1 causes high temperature-induced repression of chlorophyll catabolism and green ripening in banana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaNAC083</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma10_g12120/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma10_g12120/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ma10_g12120 Gene Symbol: MaNAC083 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: MaMADS1–MaNAC083 transcriptional regulatory cascade regulates ethylene biosynthesis during banana fruit ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaNAC1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/musa_acuminata/manac1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/musa_acuminata/manac1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Ma06_g28730 Gene Symbol: MaNAC1 Gene Name: NAC transcription factor1 Genome: banana A genome Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: Our findings revealed that MaNAC1 performs a vital role as a positive modulator in modulating cell wall cellulose metabolism within banana fruit under chilling stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaNIP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma10_p07000/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma10_p07000/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ma10_p07000 Gene Symbol: MaNIP1 Gene Name: NYC1-interacting protein 1 Genome: banana genome database (https://banana-genome-hub.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaNYC1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma07_p10650/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma07_p10650/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ma07_p10650 Gene Symbol: MaNYC1 Gene Name: NON-YELLOW COLORING 1 Genome: banana genome database (https://banana-genome-hub.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaOFP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma08_t28410.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma08_t28410.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ma08_t28410.1 Gene Symbol: MaOFP1 Gene Name: Genome: banana genome database (https://banana-genome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaPIP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/mapip1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/mapip1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MaPIP1|1 Gene Name: PIP1 subfamily AQP Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: A banana aquaporin gene, MaPIP1|1|MaPIP1|1, is involved in tolerance to drought and salt stresses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaRZF1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma02_p05740/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/ma02_p05740/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ma02_p05740 Gene Symbol: MaRZF1 Gene Name: RING Zinc Finger 1 Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: RING-type ubiquitin E3 ligase MaRZF1 interacts with chlorophyll catabolic enzyme MaSGR1, which promotes the ubiquitination and proteasomal degradation of MaSGR1, causing the green ripening of banana fruit under high temperature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaSBE2.3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/musa_acuminata/masbe2.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/musa_acuminata/masbe2.3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Ma06_t09160.1 Gene Symbol: MaSBE2.3 Gene Name: Genome: banana A-genome databases Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: The suggested functional role of MaSBE2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaSGR1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/masgr1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/masgr1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MaSGR1 Gene Name: STAY-GREEN 1 Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: RING-type ubiquitin E3 ligase MaRZF1 interacts with chlorophyll catabolic enzyme MaSGR1, which promotes the ubiquitination and proteasomal degradation of MaSGR1, causing the green ripening of banana fruit under high temperature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MuMADS1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/mumads1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/mumads1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MuMADS1 Gene Name: MADS-box protein MADS1 Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: Banana Ovate Family Protein MaOFP1 and MADS-Box Protein MuMADS1 Antagonistically Regulated Banana Fruit Ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MusaDHN-1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/musadhn-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/musadhn-1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MusaDHN-1 Gene Name: SK3-type dehydrin Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: MusaDHN-1, a novel multiple stress-inducible SK3-type dehydrin gene, contributes affirmatively to drought- and salt-stress tolerance in banana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MusaENODL3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/musa_acuminata/musaenodl3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/musa_acuminata/musaenodl3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Ma11_g13300.1 Gene Symbol: MusaENODL3 Gene Name: Genome: banana genome A Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: Targeted knockout of early nodulin-like 3 (MusaENODL3) gene in banana reveals its function in resistance to Xanthomonas wilt disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MusaPIP1;2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/musapip12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/musapip12/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MusaPIP1;2 Gene Name: Aquaporin PIP1-2 Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: Transgenic banana plants overexpressing a native plasma membrane aquaporin MusaPIP1;2 display high tolerance levels to different abiotic stresses.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
