<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Actinidia Chinensis on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/actinidia-chinensis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Actinidia Chinensis on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/actinidia-chinensis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AcALMT1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/actinidia_chinensis/acalmt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/actinidia_chinensis/acalmt1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Acc03208 Gene Symbol: AcALMT1 Gene Name: Al-ACTIVATED MALATE TRANSPORTER Genome: Actinidia chinensis (Red5) Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: An Al-ACTIVATED MALATE TRANSPORTER gene (AcALMT1) was identified as a candidate responsible for citrate accumulation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AcBFT2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/actinidia_chinensis/acbft2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/actinidia_chinensis/acbft2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Acc28037 Gene Symbol: AcBFT2 Gene Name: Genome: Actinidia chinensis (Red5) Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: CRISPR-Cas9-mediated mutagenesis of kiwifruit BFT genes results in an evergrowing but not early flowering phenotype.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AceGBF3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/actinidia_chinensis/acegbf3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/actinidia_chinensis/acegbf3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;DTZ79_15g00300/Actinidia27344 Gene Symbol: AceGBF3 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: AceGGP3 was identified as the most highly expressed GGP in Actinidia eriantha fruit, which has high fruit AsA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AceGGP3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/actinidia_chinensis/aceggp3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/actinidia_chinensis/aceggp3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Acc18653.1 Gene Symbol: AceGGP3 Gene Name: GDP-L-galactose phosphorylase 3 Genome: Actinidia chinensis (Red5) Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: AceGGP3 was identified as the most highly expressed GGP in Actinidia eriantha fruit, which has high fruit AsA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AceMYBS1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/actinidia_chinensis/acemybs1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/actinidia_chinensis/acemybs1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;DTZ79_16g09490/Actinidia31027 Gene Symbol: AceMYBS1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: Overexpression and gene-editing show AceMYBS1 effectively increases AsA accumulation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AcERF182</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/actinidia_chinensis/acerf182/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/actinidia_chinensis/acerf182/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Acc04742 Gene Symbol: AcERF182 Gene Name: Genome: Actinidia chinensis (Red5) Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: AcERF182 may play an important role in the accumulation of soluble sugar metabolism via direct regulation of the transcription of AcBAM3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AchnbZIP29</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/achn340751/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/achn340751/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Achn340751 Gene Symbol: AchnbZIP29 Gene Name: basic leucine zipper transcription factor 29 Genome: Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: Through subcellular localization analysis in this work, AchnbZIP29 and AchnMYB70 transcription factors were observed to be localized in the nucleus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AchnFAR</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/achn107181/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/achn107181/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Achn107181 Gene Symbol: AchnFAR Gene Name: Genome: Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: MYB41, MYB107, and MYC2 promote ABA-mediated primary fatty alcohol accumulation via activation of AchnFAR in wound suberization in kiwifruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AchnMYB107</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/achn267491/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/achn267491/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Achn267491 Gene Symbol: AchnMYB107 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: The positive role of TFs, including AchnMYB41, AchnMYB107, and AchnMYC2, in the regulation of AchnFAR was identified.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AchnMYB41</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/achn345001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/achn345001/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Achn345001 Gene Symbol: AchnMYB41 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: The positive role of TFs, including AchnMYB41, AchnMYB107, and AchnMYC2, in the regulation of AchnFAR was identified.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AchnMYB70</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/achn117821/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/achn117821/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Achn117821 Gene Symbol: AchnMYB70 Gene Name: MYB transcription factor 70 Genome: Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: Through subcellular localization analysis in this work, AchnbZIP29 and AchnMYB70 transcription factors were observed to be localized in the nucleus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AchnMYC2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/achn104421/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/achn104421/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Achn104421 Gene Symbol: AchnMYC2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: The positive role of TFs, including AchnMYB41, AchnMYB107, and AchnMYC2, in the regulation of AchnFAR was identified.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AcHZP45</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/achzp45/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/achzp45/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: AcHZP45 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: AcHZP45 is a repressor of chlorophyll biosynthesis and activator of chlorophyll degradation in kiwifruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AcKUP2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/ach02g251101.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/ach02g251101.2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ach02g251101.2 Gene Symbol: AcKUP2 Gene Name: K+ transporter KT/HAK/KUP 2 Genome: Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: Ethylene-induced potassium transporter AcKUP2 gene is involved in kiwifruit postharvest ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AcMADS68</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/acmads68/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/acmads68/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: AcMADS68 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: A new SEP gene, AcMADS68, was identified as a regulatory candidate for anthocyanin biosynthesis in the kiwifruit by transcriptome data and bioinformatic analyses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AcNAC1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/acnac1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/acnac1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: AcNAC1 Gene Name: NAC transcription factor 1 Genome: Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: A dramatic decline in fruit citrate induced by mutagenesis of a NAC transcription factor, AcNAC1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AcNAC4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/actinidia_chinensis/acnac4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/actinidia_chinensis/acnac4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Acc08288 Gene Symbol: AcNAC4 Gene Name: Genome: Actinidia chinensis (Red5) Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: AcNAC4 regulates the transcription of AcAAT10 by binding to and activating its promoter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AcTPR2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/ach25g228601.2-ta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/ach25g228601.2-ta/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Ach25g228601.2-TA Gene Symbol: AcTPR2 Gene Name: TOPLESS-RELATED 2 Genome: (Ach25g228601.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdMsrB1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/actinidia_chinensis/admsrb1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/actinidia_chinensis/admsrb1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Acc04318 Gene Symbol: AdMsrB1 Gene Name: Genome: Actinidia chinensis (Red5) Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: AdMsrB1 is a novel ethylene-regulated gene expressed in ripening kiwifruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdNAC2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/actinidia_chinensis/adnac2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/actinidia_chinensis/adnac2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Acc26399 Gene Symbol: AdNAC2 Gene Name: Genome: Genome_version:Actinidia chinensis (Red5) Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: Upregulation of AdMsrB1 in response to ethylene requires TFs AdNAC2 and AdNAC72.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdNAC72</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/actinidia_chinensis/adnac72/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/actinidia_chinensis/adnac72/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Acc13705 Gene Symbol: AdNAC72 Gene Name: Genome: Genome_version:Actinidia chinensis (Red5) Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: Upregulation of AdMsrB1 in response to ethylene requires TFs AdNAC2 and AdNAC72.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F3GGT1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/f3ggt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/f3ggt1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: F3GGT1 Gene Name: anthocyanidin 3-O-galactoside-2′’-O-xylosyltransferase Genome: Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: Identification and characterisation of F3GT1 and F3GGT1, two glycosyltransferases responsible for anthocyanin biosynthesis in red-fleshed kiwifruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F3GT1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/f3gt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/actinidia-chinensis/f3gt1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: F3GT1 Gene Name: flavonoid 3-0-galactosyltransferase1 Genome: Species: Actinidia chinensis Functional Descriptions: Identification and characterisation of F3GT1 and F3GGT1, two glycosyltransferases responsible for anthocyanin biosynthesis in red-fleshed kiwifruit.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
