<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rosa Hybridaa on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/rosa-hybridaa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rosa Hybridaa on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/rosa-hybridaa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rh-PIP2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaa/rh-pip2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaa/rh-pip2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: Rh-PIP2|1 Gene Name: plasma membrane aquaporin Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaa Functional Descriptions: Rh-PIP2|1|Rh-PIP2|1, a Rose Aquaporin Gene, Is Involved in Ethylene-Regulated Petal Expansion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhERF1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaa/rherf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaa/rherf1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhERF1 Gene Name: ethylene response factor 1 Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaa Functional Descriptions: Rosa hybridaaa RhERF1 and RhERF4 mediate ethylene- and auxin-regulated petal abscission by influencing pectin degradation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhERF113</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaa/rherf113/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaa/rherf113/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhERF113 Gene Name: cultivar cultivar Samantha ERF113 Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaa Functional Descriptions: RhERF113 Functions in Ethylene-Induced Petal Senescence by Modulating Cytokinin Content in Rose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RhERF4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaa/rherf4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/rosa-hybridaa/rherf4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: RhERF4 Gene Name: ethylene response factor 4 Genome: Species: Rosa hybridaa Functional Descriptions: Rosa hybridaaa RhERF1 and RhERF4 mediate ethylene- and auxin-regulated petal abscission by influencing pectin degradation.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
