<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Raphanus Raphanistrum on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/raphanus-raphanistrum/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Raphanus Raphanistrum on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/raphanus-raphanistrum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rr2ODD1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/raphanus_raphanistrum/rr2odd1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/raphanus_raphanistrum/rr2odd1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;RrC702_p3-1 Gene Symbol: Rr2ODD1 Gene Name: Genome: radish reference genome Species: Raphanus raphanistrum Functional Description: RNA sequencing (RNA-Seq) and Arabidopsis genetic transformation were deployed to identify, clone, and characterize potential genes involved in metabolic resistance to HPPD-inhibiting herbicides.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RrCYP704C1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/raphanus_raphanistrum/rrcyp704c1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/raphanus_raphanistrum/rrcyp704c1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;RrC640_p4 Gene Symbol: RrCYP704C1 Gene Name: Genome: radish reference genome Species: Raphanus raphanistrum Functional Description: RNA sequencing (RNA-Seq) and Arabidopsis genetic transformation were deployed to identify, clone, and characterize potential genes involved in metabolic resistance to HPPD-inhibiting herbicides.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RrCYP709B1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/raphanus_raphanistrum/rrcyp709b1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/raphanus_raphanistrum/rrcyp709b1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;RrC11027_p1 Gene Symbol: RrCYP709B1 Gene Name: Genome: radish reference genome Species: Raphanus raphanistrum Functional Description: RNA sequencing (RNA-Seq) and Arabidopsis genetic transformation were deployed to identify, clone, and characterize potential genes involved in metabolic resistance to HPPD-inhibiting herbicides.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
