<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AM Colonization on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/tags/am-colonization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AM Colonization on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/tags/am-colonization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GhWAK13</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/gh_a05g2392/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/gh_a05g2392/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: GH_A05G2392 Gene Symbol: GhWAK13 Gene Name: wall-associated kinase 13 Genome: Species: Gossypium hirsutum Functional Descriptions: Wall-associated kinase GhWAK13 mediates arbuscular mycorrhizal symbiosis and Verticillium wilt resistance in cotton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdGH3-12</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/malus_domestica/mdgh3-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/malus_domestica/mdgh3-12/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD15G1290900 Gene Symbol: MdGH3-12 Gene Name: Genome: Malus × domestica genome GDDH13 v 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdGH3-2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/malus_domestica/mdgh3-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/malus_domestica/mdgh3-2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;MD02G1180300 Gene Symbol: MdGH3-2 Gene Name: Genome: Malus × domestica genome GDDH13 v 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MtZIP14</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr6g007687/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/medicago-truncatula/medtr6g007687/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Medtr6g007687 Gene Symbol: MtZIP14 Gene Name: Zn-regulated iron-regulated transporter-like protein 14 Genome: Species: Medicago truncatula Functional Descriptions: Suggesting that increased colonization by the AM fungus is associated with increased expression of MtZIP14 The putative Zn transporter gene MtZIP14 was markedly up-regulated in M.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OsZAS</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g15240/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os09g15240/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os09g15240 RAPdb gene ID: Os09g0321200 Gene Symbol: OsZAS Gene Name: Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sl-IAA27</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc03g120500.2.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc03g120500.2.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc03g120500.2.1 Gene Symbol: Sl-IAA27 Gene Name: Aux/IAA gene Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Sl-IAA27 regulates strigolactone biosynthesis and mycorrhization in tomato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlCCD7</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/slccd7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/slccd7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SlCCD7 Gene Name: carotenoid cleavage dioxygenase 7 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: SlCCD7 controls strigolactone biosynthesis, shoot branching and mycorrhiza-induced apocarotenoid formation in tomato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlPHR1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc08g060920/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc08g060920/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc08g060920 Gene Symbol: SlPHR1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: We determine that SlSPX1 integrates Pi signaling and AM symbiosis by directly interacting with a set of arbuscule-induced SlPHR proteins (SlPHR1, SlPHR4, SlPHR10, SlPHR11, and SlPHR12).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlPHR10</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc10g078720/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc10g078720/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc10g078720 Gene Symbol: SlPHR10 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: We determine that SlSPX1 integrates Pi signaling and AM symbiosis by directly interacting with a set of arbuscule-induced SlPHR proteins (SlPHR1, SlPHR4, SlPHR10, SlPHR11, and SlPHR12).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlPHR11</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc10g080460/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc10g080460/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc10g080460 Gene Symbol: SlPHR11 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: We determine that SlSPX1 integrates Pi signaling and AM symbiosis by directly interacting with a set of arbuscule-induced SlPHR proteins (SlPHR1, SlPHR4, SlPHR10, SlPHR11, and SlPHR12).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlPHR12</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc10g083340/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc10g083340/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc10g083340 Gene Symbol: SlPHR12 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: We determine that SlSPX1 integrates Pi signaling and AM symbiosis by directly interacting with a set of arbuscule-induced SlPHR proteins (SlPHR1, SlPHR4, SlPHR10, SlPHR11, and SlPHR12).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlPHR4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc02g067160/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/solyc02g067160/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Solyc02g067160 Gene Symbol: SlPHR4 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: We determine that SlSPX1 integrates Pi signaling and AM symbiosis by directly interacting with a set of arbuscule-induced SlPHR proteins (SlPHR1, SlPHR4, SlPHR10, SlPHR11, and SlPHR12).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SYMRK;OsSYMRK</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g38070/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/oryza_sativa/loc_os07g38070/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: MSU gene ID: LOC_Os07g38070 RAPdb gene ID: Os07g0568100 Gene Symbol: SYMRK OsSYMRK Gene Name: Genome: MSU7 , IRGSP-1.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
