<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brachypodium Distachyon on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/brachypodium-distachyon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Brachypodium Distachyon on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/brachypodium-distachyon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BdCAD1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi3g06480/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi3g06480/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Bradi3g06480 Gene Symbol: BdCAD1 Gene Name: cinnamyl alcohol dehydrogenase 1 Genome: Species: Brachypodium distachyon Functional Descriptions: Disrupting the cinnamyl alcohol dehydrogenase 1 gene (BdCAD1) leads to altered lignification and improved saccharification in Brachypodium distachyon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BdERECTA</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi1g46450/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi1g46450/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Bradi1g46450 Gene Symbol: BdERECTA Gene Name: Genome: Species: Brachypodium distachyon Functional Descriptions: BdERECTA controls vasculature patterning and phloem-xylem organization in Brachypodium distachyon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BdES43</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi1g55090/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi1g55090/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Bradi1g55090 Gene Symbol: BdES43 Gene Name: Genome: BdGDB (http://plantgdb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BdFAR4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bdfar4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bdfar4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: BdFAR4 Gene Name: fatty acyl-coenzyme A reductase Genome: Species: Brachypodium distachyon Functional Descriptions: BdFAR4, a root-specific fatty acyl-coenzyme A reductase, is involved in fatty alcohol synthesis of root suberin polyester in Brachypodium distachyon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BdFAR4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/brachypodium_distachyon/bdfar4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/brachypodium_distachyon/bdfar4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: BdFAR4 Gene Name: Genome: Brachypodium_distachyon_v3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BdFTL1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/brachypodium_distachyon/bdft1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/brachypodium_distachyon/bdft1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Bradi2g07070 Gene Symbol: BdFTL1 Gene Name: FLOWERING LOCUS T1 Genome: BdGDB Species: Brachypodium distachyon Functional Description: Transgenic assays showed that both BdFTL1 and BdFTL2 could promote flowering, whereas BdFTL2 was essential for flowering initiation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BdFTL2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/brachypodium_distachyon/bdft2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/brachypodium_distachyon/bdft2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Bradi1g48830 Gene Symbol: BdFTL2 Gene Name: FLOWERING LOCUS T2 Genome: B.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BdPMT</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi2g36910/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi2g36910/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Bradi2g36910 Gene Symbol: BdPMT Gene Name: Genome: Species: Brachypodium distachyon Functional Descriptions: Stacking AsFMT overexpression with BdPMT loss of function enhances monolignol ferulate production in Brachypodium distachyon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BdWRKY38</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi2g30695/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi2g30695/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Bradi2g30695 Gene Symbol: BdWRKY38 Gene Name: Genome: Bd21 reference genome Species: Brachypodium distachyon Functional Descriptions: BdWRKY38 is required for the incompatible interaction of Brachypodium distachyon with the necrotrophic fungus Rhizoctonia solani.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BdWRKY44</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi2g44270/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi2g44270/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Bradi2g44270 Gene Symbol: BdWRKY44 Gene Name: Genome: Bd21 reference genome Species: Brachypodium distachyon Functional Descriptions: Demonstrated that Bd3-1, an accession of the model grass Brachypodium distachyon, is resistant to R.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bradi5g03300</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi5g03300/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi5g03300/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Bradi5g03300 Gene Symbol: Bradi5g03300 Gene Name: UDP-Glycosyltransferase Genome: Species: Brachypodium distachyon Functional Descriptions: Using the model cereal species Brachypodium distachyon, we show that the Bradi5g03300 UGT converts DON into D3G in planta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZ</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi3g46007/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi3g46007/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Bradi3g46007 Gene Symbol: BUZZ Gene Name: Genome: reference Bd21 genome Species: Brachypodium distachyon Functional Descriptions: BUZZ: an essential gene for postinitiation root hair growth and a mediator of root architecture in Brachypodium distachyon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FPL1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi3g12450/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi3g12450/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Bradi3g12450 Gene Symbol: FPL1 Gene Name: FLOWERING PROMOTING FACTOR 1 Genome: Species: Brachypodium distachyon Functional Descriptions: FPL1 and FPL7 repress flowering under long-day conditions in B.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FPL7</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi1g18240/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi1g18240/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Bradi1g18240 Gene Symbol: FPL7 Gene Name: FLOWERING PROMOTING FACTOR 7 Genome: Species: Brachypodium distachyon Functional Descriptions: FPL1 and FPL7 repress flowering under long-day conditions in B.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iw1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi5g01180/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi5g01180/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Bradi5g01180 Gene Symbol: Iw1 Gene Name: Inhibitor of wax 1 Genome: Species: Brachypodium distachyon Functional Descriptions: Using synteny and a large number of F2 gametes, Iw1 was fine-mapped to a sub-cM genetic interval on wheat chromosome arm 2BS, which includes a single collinear gene from the corresponding Brachypodium and rice physical maps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NRT1.1A</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi3g16670/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi3g16670/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Bradi3g16670 Gene Symbol: NRT1.1A Gene Name: Genome: reference Bd21 genome Species: Brachypodium distachyon Functional Descriptions: NRT1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWAM1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi2g47590/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi2g47590/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Bradi2g47590 Gene Symbol: SWAM1 Gene Name: SECONDARY WALL ASSOCIATED MYB1 Genome: Species: Brachypodium distachyon Functional Descriptions: SWAM1 overexpression (SWAM-OE) lines had greater above-ground biomass with only a slight change in flowering time while SWAM1 dominant repressor (SWAM1-DR) plants were severely dwarfed with a striking reduction in lignin of sclerenchyma fibers and stem epidermal cell length.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VRN1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi1g08340/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brachypodium-distachyon/bradi1g08340/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Bradi1g08340 Gene Symbol: VRN1 Gene Name: VERNALIZATION 1 Genome: Species: Brachypodium distachyon Functional Descriptions: VERNALIZATION1 (VRN1), in leaves, thereby preventing overaccumulation of FLOWERING LOCUS T1 (FT1) at the juvenile stage.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
