<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Diospyros Kaki on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/diospyros-kaki/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Diospyros Kaki on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/diospyros-kaki/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DkBG1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/c54486_91/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/c54486_91/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: c54486_91 Gene Symbol: DkBG1 Gene Name: β-Glucosidases 1 Genome: Species: Diospyros kaki Functional Descriptions: Overexpression of the persimmon abscisic acid β-glucosidase gene (DkBG1) alters fruit ripening in transgenic tomato.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DkbZIP5</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkbzip5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkbzip5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: DkbZIP5 Gene Name: putative basic leucine-zipper transcription factor5 Genome: Species: Diospyros kaki Functional Descriptions: Seasonal Abscisic Acid Signal and a Basic Leucine Zipper Transcription Factor, DkbZIP5, Regulate Proanthocyanidin Biosynthesis in Persimmon Fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DkBZR1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkbzr1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkbzr1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: DkBZR1 Gene Name: BRASSINAZOLE RESISTANT 1 Genome: Species: Diospyros kaki Functional Descriptions: Transcription factors DkBZR1/DkBZR2 regulate cell wall degradation genes and ethylene biosynthesis genes during persimmon fruit ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DkBZR2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkbzr2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkbzr2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: DkBZR2 Gene Name: BRASSINAZOLE RESISTANT 2 Genome: Species: Diospyros kaki Functional Descriptions: Transcription factors DkBZR1/DkBZR2 regulate cell wall degradation genes and ethylene biosynthesis genes during persimmon fruit ripening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DkMYB14</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkmyb14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkmyb14/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: DkMYB14 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Diospyros kaki Functional Descriptions: DkMYB14 is a bifunctional transcription factor that regulates the accumulation of proanthocyanidin in persimmon fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DkMyb2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkmyb2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkmyb2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: DkMyb2 Gene Name: MYB transcription factor2 Genome: Species: Diospyros kaki Functional Descriptions: DkMyb2 wound-induced transcription factor of persimmon (Diospyros kaki Thunb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DkMyb4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkmyb4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkmyb4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: DkMyb4 Gene Name: Myb transcription factor4 Genome: Species: Diospyros kaki Functional Descriptions: DkMyb4 Is a Myb Transcription Factor Involved in Proanthocyanidin Biosynthesis in Persimmon Fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DkNAC9</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dknac9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dknac9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: DkNAC9 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Diospyros kaki Functional Descriptions: High CO2/hypoxia-induced softening of persimmon fruit is modulated by DkERF8/16 and DkNAC9 complexes.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
