<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Peel on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/tags/peel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Peel on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/tags/peel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CCD4b</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_reticulata/ccd4b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_reticulata/ccd4b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Ciclev10028113m.g Gene Symbol: CCD4b Gene Name: CAROTENOID CLEAVAGE DIOXYGENASE 4 Genome: Citrus clementina v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsMYB36</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa2g352940/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa2g352940/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa2G352940 Gene Symbol: CsMYB36 Gene Name: MYB DOMAIN PROTEIN 36 Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: Transcription factor CsMYB36 regulates fruit neck length via mediating cell expansion in cucumber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsPLDα1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cspld%CE%B11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cspld%CE%B11/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsPLDα1 Gene Name: phospholipase D alpha Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsPLDα1 and CsPLDγ1 are differentially induced during leaf and fruit abscission and diurnally regulated in Citrus sinensis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsPLDγ1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cspld%CE%B31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cspld%CE%B31/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsPLDγ1 Gene Name: phospholipase D gamma Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: CsPLDα1 and CsPLDγ1 are differentially induced during leaf and fruit abscission and diurnally regulated in Citrus sinensis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsSEC23</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa5g585430/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cucumis-sativus/csa5g585430/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Csa5G585430 Gene Symbol: CsSEC23 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Cucumis sativus Functional Descriptions: MutMap, genotyping, and gene editing results demonstrated that CsSEC23, which is the core component of COPII vesicles, mediates the glossiness of cucumber fruit peel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Csβ-LCY1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs%CE%B2-lcy1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs%CE%B2-lcy1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: Csβ-LCY1 Gene Name: beta-cyclase1 Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: The β-cyclization of lycopene, catalysed by the lycopene β-cyclases (β-LCY), seems to be a key regulatory step of the carotenoid pathway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Csβ-LCY2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs%CE%B2-lcy2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/citrus-sinensis/cs%CE%B2-lcy2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: Csβ-LCY2 Gene Name: beta-cyclase2 Genome: Species: Citrus sinensis Functional Descriptions: The β-cyclization of lycopene, catalysed by the lycopene β-cyclases (β-LCY), seems to be a key regulatory step of the carotenoid pathway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaSGR1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/masgr1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/musa-acuminata/masgr1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MaSGR1 Gene Name: STAY-GREEN 1 Genome: Species: Musa acuminata Functional Descriptions: RING-type ubiquitin E3 ligase MaRZF1 interacts with chlorophyll catabolic enzyme MaSGR1, which promotes the ubiquitination and proteasomal degradation of MaSGR1, causing the green ripening of banana fruit under high temperature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdLAC7</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md04g0113100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md04g0113100/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MD04G0113100 Gene Symbol: MdLAC7 Gene Name: laccase 7 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: The detailed analysis identified MdLAC7&amp;rsquo;s (laccase 7) role in the preharvest apple peel browning process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdSINA2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md01g1218700/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md01g1218700/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MD01G1218700 Gene Symbol: MdSINA2 Gene Name: E3 ubiquitin ligase 2 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: MdRGL2a and MdCIPK20 were ubiquitinated and degraded by E3 ubiquitin ligases MdSINA1 and MdSINA2, respectively, both of which were activated in the presence of GA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdWRKY31</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md03g0162000/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/md03g0162000/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MD03G0162000 Gene Symbol: MdWRKY31 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: ChIP-PCR analysis revealed that MdWRKY31 binds to the promoter of MdLAC7 and positively regulates its activity to promote peel browning of bagged fruits (dark conditions).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PuMYB21</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-ussuriensis/pumyb21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-ussuriensis/pumyb21/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PuMYB21 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor 21 Genome: Species: Pyrus ussuriensis Functional Descriptions: PuMYB21 and PuMYB54, from “Nanguo” pears, which were notably expressed in response to cold stress and during the peel-browning process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PuMYB54</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-ussuriensis/pumyb54/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-ussuriensis/pumyb54/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PuMYB54 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor 21 Genome: Species: Pyrus ussuriensis Functional Descriptions: PuMYB21 and PuMYB54, from “Nanguo” pears, which were notably expressed in response to cold stress and during the peel-browning process.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
