<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cajanus Cajan on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/cajanus-cajan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cajanus Cajan on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/cajanus-cajan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CcADF9</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cajanus_cajan/ccadf9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cajanus_cajan/ccadf9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: CcADF9 Gene Name: Genome: C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CcARP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cajanus-cajan/ccarp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cajanus-cajan/ccarp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CcARP1 Gene Name: actin depolymerizing factor-related phosphokinase 1 Genome: Species: Cajanus cajan Functional Descriptions: Melatonin-mediated CcARP1 alters F-actin dynamics by phosphorylation of CcADF9 to balance root growth and salt tolerance in pigeon pea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CcCBL1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cajanus-cajan/cccbl1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cajanus-cajan/cccbl1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CcCBL1 Gene Name: Calcineurin B-like 1 Genome: Species: Cajanus cajan Functional Descriptions: The pigeon pea CcCIPK14-CcCBL1 pair positively modulates drought tolerance by enhancing flavonoid biosynthesis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CcCIPK14</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cajanus-cajan/cccipk14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cajanus-cajan/cccipk14/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CcCIPK14 Gene Name: Calcineurin B-like (CBL)-interacting protein kinase 14 Genome: Species: Cajanus cajan Functional Descriptions: The pigeon pea CcCIPK14-CcCBL1 pair positively modulates drought tolerance by enhancing flavonoid biosynthesis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CcCIPK14</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cajanus_cajan/cccipk14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cajanus_cajan/cccipk14/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene_id: Gene Symbol: CcCIPK14 Gene Name: Genome: C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CcCS</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cajanus-cajan/cccs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cajanus-cajan/cccs/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CcCS Gene Name: Citrate Synthase Genome: Species: Cajanus cajan Functional Descriptions: CcNFYB3-CcMATE35 and LncRNA CcLTCS-CcCS modules jointly regulate the efflux and synthesis of citrate to enhance aluminium tolerance in pigeon pea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CcLTCS</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cajanus-cajan/ccltcs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cajanus-cajan/ccltcs/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CcLTCS Gene Name: Long noncoding RNA Targeting Citrate Synthase Genome: Species: Cajanus cajan Functional Descriptions: CcNFYB3-CcMATE35 and LncRNA CcLTCS-CcCS modules jointly regulate the efflux and synthesis of citrate to enhance aluminium tolerance in pigeon pea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CcMATE35</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cajanus-cajan/ccmate35/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cajanus-cajan/ccmate35/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CcMATE35 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Cajanus cajan Functional Descriptions: CcNFYB3-CcMATE35 and LncRNA CcLTCS-CcCS modules jointly regulate the efflux and synthesis of citrate to enhance aluminium tolerance in pigeon pea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CcMATE35</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/cajanus_cajan/ccmate35/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/cajanus_cajan/ccmate35/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: CcMATE35 Gene Name: Genome: C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CcNFYB3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cajanus-cajan/ccnfyb3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cajanus-cajan/ccnfyb3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CcNFYB3 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Cajanus cajan Functional Descriptions: CcNFYB3-CcMATE35 and LncRNA CcLTCS-CcCS modules jointly regulate the efflux and synthesis of citrate to enhance aluminium tolerance in pigeon pea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CcSTOP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cajanus-cajan/ccstop1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/cajanus-cajan/ccstop1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CcSTOP1 Gene Name: SENSITIVE TO PROTON RHIZOTOXICITY1 Genome: Species: Cajanus cajan Functional Descriptions: Characterization of CcSTOP1| a C2H2-type transcription factor regulates Al tolerance gene in pigeonpea.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
