<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nicotiana Attenuata on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/nicotiana-attenuata/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nicotiana Attenuata on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/nicotiana-attenuata/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NaCOI1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-attenuata/nacoi1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-attenuata/nacoi1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NaCOI1 Gene Name: Coronatine-insensitive 1 Genome: Species: Nicotiana attenuata Functional Descriptions: NaCOI1 mediates herbivore- induced resistance in Nicotiana attenuata and reveals the role of herbivore movement in avoiding defenses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NaMEK2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-attenuata/namek2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-attenuata/namek2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NaMEK2 Gene Name: mitogen-activated protein kinase kinase 2 Genome: Species: Nicotiana attenuata Functional Descriptions: Two mitogen-activated protein kinase kinases, MKK1 and MEK2, are involved in wounding- and specialist lepidopteran herbivore Manduca sexta-induced responses in Nicotiana attenuata.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NaMKK1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-attenuata/namkk1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/nicotiana-attenuata/namkk1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NaMKK1 Gene Name: mitogen-activated protein kinase kinase 1 Genome: Species: Nicotiana attenuata Functional Descriptions: Two mitogen-activated protein kinase kinases, MKK1 and MEK2, are involved in wounding- and specialist lepidopteran herbivore Manduca sexta-induced responses in Nicotiana attenuata.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NaMYC2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-attenuata/namyc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-attenuata/namyc2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NaMYC2 Gene Name: MYC2 transcription factor Genome: Species: Nicotiana attenuata Functional Descriptions: NaMYC2 transcription factor regulates a subset of plant defense responses in Nicotiana attenuata.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NaPME1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-attenuata/napme1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-attenuata/napme1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NaPME1 Gene Name: putative pectin methylesterase Genome: Species: Nicotiana attenuata Functional Descriptions: Pectin methylesterase NaPME1 contributes to the emission of methanol during insect herbivory and to the elicitation of defence responses in Nicotiana attenuata.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NaWRKY3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_attenuata/nawrky3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_attenuata/nawrky3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: NaWRKY3 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Nicotiana attenuata Functional Description: we demonstrated that NaWRKY3 is a fine-tuned master regulator of the defense network against A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NaWRKY70</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-attenuata/nawrky70/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-attenuata/nawrky70/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NaWRKY70 Gene Name: WRKY transcription factor 70 Genome: Species: Nicotiana attenuata Functional Descriptions: NaWRKY70 is a key regulator of Nicotiana attenuata resistance to Alternaria alternata through regulation of phytohormones and phytoalexins biosynthesis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NaZTL</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-attenuata/niatv7_g26018-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-attenuata/niatv7_g26018-/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: NIATv7_g26018 Gene Symbol: NaZTL Gene Name: ZEITLUPE Genome: NaDH (http://nadh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIC1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_attenuata/nic1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/nicotiana_attenuata/nic1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Nitab4.5_0003090g0030 Gene Symbol: NIC1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Nicotiana attenuata Functional Description: genetic regulation of nicotine levels in tobacco plants can be achieved by manipulating the NIC1 gene.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
