<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hordeum Vulgare on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/hordeum-vulgare/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hordeum Vulgare on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/hordeum-vulgare/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bmy1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/bmy1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/bmy1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: Bmy1 Gene Name: beta-amylase1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Differential expression of two β-amylase genes (Bmy1 and Bmy2) in developing and mature barley grain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bmy2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/bmy2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/bmy2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: Bmy2 Gene Name: beta-amylase2 Genome: Description:&#x9;Differential expression of two β-amylase genes (Bmy1 and Bmy2) in developing and mature barley grain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DL</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/dl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/dl/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU7Hr1G106960 Gene Symbol: DL Gene Name: Genome: barley cultivar Morex V1 Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Although the DL mutant allele showed no expression changes in selected tissues by real-time PCR, we propose HORVU7Hr1G106960 as a candidate gene conferring the dwarf and liguleless phenotype in barley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hv-CRY1a</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hv-cry1a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hv-cry1a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: Hv-CRY1a Gene Name: CRYPTOCHROME1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: We have now created barley transgenic lines downregulating the genes encoding the blue light receptors CRYTOCHROME (CRY1) and CRY2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hv-CRY1b</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hv-cry1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hv-cry1b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: Hv-CRY1b Gene Name: CRYPTOCHROME1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: We have now created barley transgenic lines downregulating the genes encoding the blue light receptors CRYTOCHROME (CRY1) and CRY2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvABI5</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/hordeum-vulgare/hvabi5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/hordeum-vulgare/hvabi5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvABI5 Gene Name: bZIP transcription factor 5 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: The Transcription Factors HvABI5 and HvVP1 Are Required for the Abscisic Acid Induction of Gene Expression in Barley Aleurone Cells.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvAKT1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvakt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvakt1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvAKT1 Gene Name: Inwardly rectifying K+ channel 1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Overexpression of HvAKT1 improves drought tolerance in barley by regulating root ion homeostasis and ROS and NO signaling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvAKT2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvakt2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvakt2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: HvAKT2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Overexpression of HvAKT2 and HvHAK1 enhanced K+ uptake and H+ homoeostasis leading to drought tolerance in these transgenic lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvALMT1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvalmt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvalmt1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvALMT1 Gene Name: Aluminum-Activated Malate Transporter 1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: HvALMT1 from barley is involved in the transport of organic anions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvARE1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu7hr1g063720horvu.morex.r3.7hg0693130/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu7hr1g063720horvu.morex.r3.7hg0693130/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: HORVU7Hr1G063720;HORVU.MOREX.r3.7HG0693130 Gene Symbol: HvARE1 Gene Name: abnormal cytokinin response1 repressor 1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: CRISPR/Cas9 gene editing and natural variation analysis demonstrate the potential for HvARE1 in improvement of nitrogen use efficiency in barley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvATF1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu3hr1g082560/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu3hr1g082560/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: HORVU3Hr1G082560 Gene Symbol: HvATF1 Gene Name: Al-tolerance Transcription Factor 1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: HvATF1, Al-tolerance Transcription Factor 1, and determined its potential function in Al stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvBI-1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/hordeum-vulgare/hvbi-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/hordeum-vulgare/hvbi-1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvBI-1 Gene Name: BAX Inhibitor-1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Transient over-expression of barley BAX Inhibitor-1 weakens oxidative defence and MLA12-mediated resistance to Blumeria graminis f.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvBot1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvbot1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvbot1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvBot1 Gene Name: Clipper boron transporter Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Similar to HvBot1, the tolerant HvNIP2|1 allele was unique to the Sahara barley accessions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvCaM1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu0hr1g001270/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu0hr1g001270/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: HORVU0Hr1G001270 Gene Symbol: HvCaM1 Gene Name: calmodulin 1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Identified a salt-responsive calmodulin (HvCaM1) in a proteome study of barley (Hordeum vulgare) roots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvCEBiP</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvcebip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvcebip/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;TA30910_4513 Gene Symbol: HvCEBiP Gene Name: CEBiP chitin receptor Genome: barley EST database Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Our findings suggest that HvWRKY2 represses barley basal immunity by directly targeting pathogen-associated molecular pattern (PAMP) recognition receptor genes, suggesting that HvCEBiP and likely chitin signaling function in barley PAMP-triggered immune responses to Bgh infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvCEN</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvcen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvcen/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU2Hr1G072750 Gene Symbol: HvCEN Gene Name: CENTRORADIALIS Genome: barley cultivar Morex V1 Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Global transcriptome profiling in developing shoot apices and inflorescences of mutant and wild-type plants revealed that HvCEN controlled transcripts involved in chromatin remodeling activities, cytokinin and cell cycle regulation and cellular respiration under LDs and short days, whereas HvCEN affected floral homeotic genes only under LDs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvCKX1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu3hr1g019850/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu3hr1g019850/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: HORVU3Hr1G019850 Gene Symbol: HvCKX1 Gene Name: cytokinin dehydrogenase1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Silencing of the HvCKX1 gene decreases the cytokinin oxidase/dehydrogenase level in barley and leads to higher plant productivity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvCKX3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu1hr1g042360/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu1hr1g042360/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: HORVU1Hr1G042360 Gene Symbol: HvCKX3 Gene Name: cytokinin dehydrogenase3 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Silencing of the HvCKX1 gene decreases the cytokinin oxidase/dehydrogenase level in barley and leads to higher plant productivity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvCO1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvco1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvco1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvCO1 Gene Name: CONSTANS-like protein1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: HvCO1, the closest barley ortholog of the key photoperiod response gene CONSTANS in Arabidopsis, was over-expressed in the spring barley Golden Promise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvCO9</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvco9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvco9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvCO9 Gene Name: CONSTANS-like9 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: The differential expression of HvCO9, a member of the CONSTANS-like gene family, contributes to the control of flowering under short-day conditions in barley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvCslD2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvcsld2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvcsld2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvCslD2 Gene Name: cellulose synthase-like D2 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: The barley (Hordeum vulgare) cellulose synthase-like D2 gene (HvCslD2) mediates penetration resistance to host-adapted and nonhost isolates of the powdery mildew fungus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvDOF19</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvdof19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvdof19/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvDOF19 Gene Name: dof zinc finger protein19 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: The HvDOF19 transcription factor mediates the abscisic acid-dependent repression of hydrolase genes in germinating barley aleurone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvEXPB7</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvexpb7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvexpb7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvEXPB7 Gene Name: β-expansin gene Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: HvEXPB7, a novel β-expansin gene revealed by the root hair transcriptome of Tibetan wild barley, improves root hair growth under drought stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvFEA4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvfea4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvfea4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU7Hr1G042170 Gene Symbol: HvFEA4 Gene Name: Genome: barley cultivar Morex V1 Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: We further reveal that HvFEA4, as a transcription factor, potentially targets multiple pathways during reproductive development, including transcriptional control, phytohormone signaling, and redox status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvFT3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvft3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvft3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvFT3|PPDH2 Gene Name: FT-like protein 3 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Expression analysis of vernalization and day-length response genes in barley (Hordeum vulgare L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvFT4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvft4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvft4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvFT4 Gene Name: FLOWERING LOCUS T4 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: FLOWERING LOCUS T4 (HvFT4) delays flowering and decreases floret fertility in barley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvGA20ox2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvga20ox2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvga20ox2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvGA20ox2|sdw1 Gene Name: gibberellin 20 oxidase 2-like protein Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: The HvGA20ox2|sdw1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvGA3ox1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvga3ox1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvga3ox1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU.MOREX.r3.2HG0208900 Gene Symbol: HvGA3ox1 Gene Name: Genome: genome sequence of barley cv.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvGST</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/horvu.morex.r3.7hg0713570.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/horvu.morex.r3.7hg0713570.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: HORVU.MOREX.r3.7HG0713570.1 Gene Symbol: HvGST Gene Name: glutathione S-transferase Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: HvGST plays a key role in anthocyanin accumulation in colored barley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvHAK1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvhak1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvhak1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: HvHAK1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Overexpression of HvAKT2 and HvHAK1 enhanced K+ uptake and H+ homoeostasis leading to drought tolerance in these transgenic lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvHK1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu7hr1g030040/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu7hr1g030040/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: HORVU7Hr1G030040 Gene Symbol: HvHK1 Gene Name: HISTIDINE KINASE 1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: HvHK1 encodes a histidine kinase and is specifically expressed in the syncytial endosperm at the maternal–filial boundary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvHKT1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvhkt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvhkt1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvHKT1|5 Gene Name: High-Affinity Potassium Transporter 1|5 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: The HKT Transporter HvHKT1|5|HvHKT1|5 Negatively Regulates Salt Tolerance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvHMA2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvhma2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvhma2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvHMA2 Gene Name: heavy metal transporter Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: HvHMA2, a P1B-ATPase from Barley, Is Highly Conserved among Cereals and Functions in Zn and Cd Transport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvHNT1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvhnt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvhnt1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU2Hr1G098820 Gene Symbol: HvHNT1 Gene Name: Histidine Triad Nucleotide-Binding Protein 1 Genome: barley cultivar Morex V1 Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Our data suggest that HvHNT1 controls tiller development and leaf width through HvPPIase, thus contributing to understanding of the molecular players that control tillering in barley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvHOX9</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvhox9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvhox9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: HvHOX9 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Our findings suggest that miR166b/HvHOX9 play a critical role in Al tolerance by decreasing root cell wall Al binding and increasing apoplastic pH for Al detoxification in the root.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvIcy-2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvicy-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvicy-2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvIcy-2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: The induced expression of HvIcy-2 by the fungal stress correlated to a higher susceptibility of silencing HvIcy-2 plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvKCS1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu4hr1g063420.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu4hr1g063420.2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: HORVU4Hr1G063420.2 Gene Symbol: HvKCS1 Gene Name: β-Ketoacyl-CoA Synthase 1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: The β-Ketoacyl-CoA Synthase HvKCS1, Encoded by Cer-zh, Plays a Key Role in Synthesis of Barley Leaf Wax and Germination of Barley Powdery Mildew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvLUX1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvlux1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvlux1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvLUX1 Gene Name: haplotype 1 LUX Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: HvLUX1 is a candidate gene underlying the early maturity 10 locus in barley: phylogeny, diversity, and interactions with the circadian clock and photoperiodic pathways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvMKK1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvmkk1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvmkk1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: HvMKK1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Our data suggest that the HvMKK1-HvMPK4 kinase pair acts upstream of HvWRKY1 to negatively regulate barley immunity against powdery mildew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvMND1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvmnd1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvmnd1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU7Hr1G113480.3 Gene Symbol: HvMND1 Gene Name: MANY NODED DWARF1 Genome: barley cultivar Morex V1 Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Our data suggest that HvMND1 plays a significant role in the coordinated regulation of reproductive phase transitions, thereby promoting reproductive growth and whole plant senescence in barley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvMORC1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvmorc1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvmorc1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU7Hr1G083280.15 Gene Symbol: HvMORC1 Gene Name: Genome: barley cultivar Morex V1 Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: We demonstrate that HvMORC1 and HvMORC6a form distinct nucleocytoplasmic homo-/heteromers with other HvMORCs and interact with components of the RNA-directed DNA methylation (RdDM) pathway, further substantiating that MORC proteins are involved in the regulation of TEs in barley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvMORC6a</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvmorc6a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvmorc6a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU3Hr1G046280.3 Gene Symbol: HvMORC6a Gene Name: Genome: barley cultivar Morex V1 Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: We demonstrate that HvMORC1 and HvMORC6a form distinct nucleocytoplasmic homo-/heteromers with other HvMORCs and interact with components of the RNA-directed DNA methylation (RdDM) pathway, further substantiating that MORC proteins are involved in the regulation of TEs in barley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvMPK4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvmpk4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvmpk4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: HvMPK4 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: HvMPK4 phosphorylates HvWRKY1 to enhance its suppression of barley immunity to powdery mildew fungus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvMTP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvmtp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvmtp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvMTP1 Gene Name: Putative Zn transporter 1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: We identified a novel cereal member of CDFs in barley, termed HvMTP1, that localizes to the vacuolar membrane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvMyo11A1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu.morex.r3.1hg0046420/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu.morex.r3.1hg0046420/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: HORVU.MOREX.r3.1HG0046420 Gene Symbol: HvMyo11A1|Ror1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Barley HvMyo11A1|Ror1 encodes a class XI myosin required for mlo-based broad-spectrum resistance to the fungal powdery mildew pathogen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvNAC005</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvnac005/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvnac005/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvNAC005 Gene Name: NAC transcription factor Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Barley plants over-expressing the NAC transcription factor gene HvNAC005 show stunting and delay in development combined with early senescence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvNIP2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvnip2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvnip2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvNIP2|1 Gene Name: Nodulin-26 like intrinsic protein Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Boron Toxicity Tolerance in Barley through Reduced Expression of the Multifunctional Aquaporin HvNIP2|1|HvNIP2|1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvNLP2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvnlp2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvnlp2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Hv2055A04 Gene Symbol: HvNLP2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: HvNLP2 controls nitrate signaling and plays an important role in NUE.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvNPF2.12</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu3hr1g092870/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu3hr1g092870/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: HORVU3Hr1G092870 Gene Symbol: HvNPF2.12 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Convergently selected NPF2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvOle3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/mloc_7938.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/mloc_7938.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MLOC_7938.1 Gene Symbol: HvOle3 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Abscisic acid activation of oleosin gene HvOle3 expression prevents the coalescence of protein storage vacuoles in barley aleurone cells.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvOS2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvos2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvos2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvOS2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Fine-tuning of the flowering time control in winter barley: the importance of HvOS2 and HvVRN2 in non-inductive conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HVP10</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvp10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvp10/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU7Hr1G028910 Gene Symbol: HVP10 Gene Name: Genome: barley cultivar Morex V1 Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: This study reveals the molecular mechanism of HVP10 underlying salt tolerance and highlights its potential in improving crop salt tolerance Vacuolar H+-pyrophosphatase HVP10 enhances salt tolerance via promoting Na+ translocation into root vacuoles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvPap-1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvpap-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvpap-1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvPap-1 Gene Name: putative cysteine proteinase precursor Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: A cathepsin F-like peptidase involved in barley grain protein mobilization, HvPap-1, is modulated by its own propeptide and by cystatins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvPAP14</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvpap14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvpap14/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvPAP14 Gene Name: papain-like cysteine proteinase Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: HvPAP14, which belongs to the C1A family of cysteine proteases, was identified in senescing barley (Hordeum vulgare L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvPAPhy_a</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvpaphy_a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvpaphy_a/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvPAPhy_a Gene Name: phytase purple acid phosphatase Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Barley HvPAPhy_a as transgene provides high and stable phytase activities in mature barley straw and in grains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvPDS</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvpds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvpds/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU4Hr1G077450 Gene Symbol: HvPDS Gene Name: Genome: barley cultivar Morex V1 Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Our previous study reported that knockdown of the barley phytoene desaturase gene HvPDS by virus-induced gene silencing resulted in a photobleaching phenotype in seedlings Agrobacterium-mediated transformation was performed on microspore-derived callus to target the HvPDS gene, and T0 albinos with targeted mutations were successfully obtained from commercial varieties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvPIP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvpip1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvpip1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvPIP1|6 Gene Name: plasma membrane intrinsic protein Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: HvPIP1|6|HvPIP1|6, a Barley (Hordeum vulgare L.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvPTR1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvptr1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvptr1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvPTR1 Gene Name: peptide transporter1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: A role for phosphorylation in the regulation of the barley scutellar peptide transporter HvPTR1 by amino acids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvRAF</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvraf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvraf/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvRAF Gene Name: root abundant factor Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: The barley ERF-type transcription factor HvRAF confers enhanced pathogen resistance and salt tolerance in Arabidopsis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvSPDT</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvspdt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvspdt/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvSPDT Gene Name: SULTR-like phosphorus distribution transporter Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: A crucial role for a node-localized transporter, HvSPDT, in loading phosphorus into barley grains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvSRN1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvsrn1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvsrn1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU.MOREX.r3.2HG064020 Gene Symbol: HvSRN1 Gene Name: Genome: genome sequence of barley cv.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvSTP13</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvstp13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvstp13/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvSTP13 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: The expression of HvSTP13 increased on bacterial and fungal pathogen-associated molecular pattern (PAMP) application, suggesting a PAMP-triggered signalling that converged on the transcriptional induction of the gene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvSUT1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu4hr1g075200.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu4hr1g075200.3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: HORVU4Hr1G075200.3 Gene Symbol: HvSUT1 Gene Name: sucrose transporter 1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Down-regulation of the sucrose transporters HvSUT1 and HvSUT2 affects sucrose homeostasis along its delivery path in barley grains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvSUT2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu5hr1g000010.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu5hr1g000010.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: HORVU5Hr1G000010.1 Gene Symbol: HvSUT2 Gene Name: sucrose transporter 2 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Down-regulation of the sucrose transporters HvSUT1 and HvSUT2 affects sucrose homeostasis along its delivery path in barley grains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvSWEET11b</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu7hr1g054710/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu7hr1g054710/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: HORVU7Hr1G054710 Gene Symbol: HvSWEET11b Gene Name: Sugars Will Eventually be Exported Transporter 11 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: A radiotracer assay revealed that expressing HvSWEET11b in African clawed frog (Xenopus laevis) oocytes facilitated the bidirectional transfer of not only just sucrose and glucose, but also cytokinin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvTDF1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu.morex.r2.4hg0319540/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/horvu.morex.r2.4hg0319540/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: HORVU.MOREX.r2.4HG0319540 Gene Symbol: HvTDF1 Gene Name: Barley TAPETAL DEVELOPMENT and FUNCTION1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Barley TAPETAL DEVELOPMENT and FUNCTION1 (HvTDF1) gene reveals conserved and unique roles in controlling anther tapetum development in dicot and monocot plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvVP1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/hordeum-vulgare/hvvp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/hordeum-vulgare/hvvp1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvVP1 Gene Name: vulgare VP1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: The Transcription Factors HvABI5 and HvVP1 Are Required for the Abscisic Acid Induction of Gene Expression in Barley Aleurone Cells.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvWIN1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvwin1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvwin1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvWIN1 Gene Name: WAX INDUCER1 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: WAX INDUCER1 (HvWIN1) transcription factor regulates free fatty acid biosynthetic genes to reinforce cuticle to resist Fusarium head blight in barley spikelets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvWRKY1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvwrky1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvwrky1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: HvWRKY1 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: HvWRKY1 is phosphorylated in barley at the early stages of Bgh infection, which enhances its suppression on barley immunity likely due to enhanced DNA-binding and transcriptional repression activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvWRKY2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvwrky2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvwrky2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Gene Symbol: HvWRKY2 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Our findings suggest that HvWRKY2 represses barley basal immunity by directly targeting pathogen-associated molecular pattern (PAMP) recognition receptor genes, suggesting that HvCEBiP and likely chitin signaling function in barley PAMP-triggered immune responses to Bgh infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvWRKY45</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvwrky45/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/hvwrky45/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Hordeum_vulgare_S_2HG004343 Gene Symbol: HvWRKY45 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: A 29-bp insertion into the promoter region formed a cis-regulatory element in the HvWRKY45 gene, which may contribute to enhanced tolerance to drought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvYS1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvys1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvys1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvYS1 Gene Name: iron–phytosiderophore transporter Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: We identified a gene specifically encoding an iron–phytosiderophore transporter (HvYS1) in barley, which is the most tolerant species to iron deficiency among graminaceous plants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvYS2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvys2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvys2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvYS2 Gene Name: Putative iron-phytosiderophore transporter Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Here, we report the cloning and characterization of HvYSL2, a novel metal–PS transporter encoding gene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HvZIP7</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvzip7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/hordeum-vulgare/hvzip7/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: HvZIP7 Gene Name: zinc transporter protein ZIP7 Genome: Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: HvZIP7 mediates zinc accumulation in barley (Hordeum vulgare) at moderately high zinc supply.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MND8</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/mnd8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/mnd8/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU5Hr1G118820 Gene Symbol: MND8 Gene Name: Genome: barley cultivar Morex V1 Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Collectively, our results indicated that MND8ynp5 is a novel allele of the HORVU5Hr1G118820 gene that is possibly responsible for the shortened plastochron and many noded dwarf phenotype in barley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RLPK4-1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/rlpk4-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/rlpk4-1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU2Hr1G111760.1 Gene Symbol: RLPK4-1 Gene Name: Receptor-like protein kinase 4 Genome: barley cultivar Morex V1 Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Two Receptor-like kinase 4 (RLPK4) v1 or Receptor-like kinase (RLK) v3 could be the candidates for enhanced germination under salinity stress because of their upregulated expression in salt-tolerant variety CM72.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RLPK4-2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/rlpk4-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/rlpk4-2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU2Hr1G111780.3 Gene Symbol: RLPK4-2 Gene Name: Receptor-like protein kinase 4 Genome: barley cultivar Morex V1 Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Two Receptor-like kinase 4 (RLPK4) v1 or Receptor-like kinase (RLK) v3 could be the candidates for enhanced germination under salinity stress because of their upregulated expression in salt-tolerant variety CM72.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RLPK4-3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/rlpk4-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/rlpk4-3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU2Hr1G111790.7 Gene Symbol: RLPK4-3 Gene Name: Receptor-like protein kinase 4 Genome: barley cultivar Morex V1 Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Two Receptor-like kinase 4 (RLPK4) v1 or Receptor-like kinase (RLK) v3 could be the candidates for enhanced germination under salinity stress because of their upregulated expression in salt-tolerant variety CM72.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rph15</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/rph15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/rph15/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU2Hr1G019120.5 Gene Symbol: Rph15 Gene Name: Genome: barley cultivar Morex V1 Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: The cloning of Rph15 now permits efficient gene deployment and the production of resistance gene cassettes for sustained leaf rust control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rph3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/rph3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/rph3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU7HG0741050 Gene Symbol: Rph3 Gene Name: Genome: barley cultivar Morex V1 Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Like known transmembrane executors such as Bs3 and Xa7, heterologous expression of Rph3 in N.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>vrs1.a4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/vrs1.a4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/hordeum_vulgare/vrs1.a4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;HORVU2Hr1G092290/HORVU.MOREX.r2.2HG0152930 Gene Symbol: vrs1.a4 Gene Name: Genome: barley cultivar Morex V1 Species: Hordeum vulgare Functional Descriptions: Further analysis of Vrs1 expression in offspring of the mapping populations or different Vrs1.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
