<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Proanthocyanidin on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/tags/proanthocyanidin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Proanthocyanidin on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/tags/proanthocyanidin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BnTT16.1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/bntt16.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/bntt16.1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: BnTT16.1 Gene Name: TRANSPARENT TESTA 16 Genome: Species: Brassica napus Functional Descriptions: Brassica napus TT16 homologs with different genomic origins and expression levels encode proteins that regulate a broad range of endothelium-associated genes at the transcriptional level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BnTT16.2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/bntt16.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/bntt16.2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: BnTT16.2 Gene Name: TRANSPARENT TESTA 16 Genome: Species: Brassica napus Functional Descriptions: Brassica napus TT16 homologs with different genomic origins and expression levels encode proteins that regulate a broad range of endothelium-associated genes at the transcriptional level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BnTT16.3</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/bntt16.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/bntt16.3/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: BnTT16.3 Gene Name: TRANSPARENT TESTA 16 Genome: Species: Brassica napus Functional Descriptions: Brassica napus TT16 homologs with different genomic origins and expression levels encode proteins that regulate a broad range of endothelium-associated genes at the transcriptional level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BnTT16.4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/bntt16.4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-napus/bntt16.4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: BnTT16.4 Gene Name: TRANSPARENT TESTA 16 Genome: Species: Brassica napus Functional Descriptions: Brassica napus TT16 homologs with different genomic origins and expression levels encode proteins that regulate a broad range of endothelium-associated genes at the transcriptional level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsMYB2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/csmyb2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/camellia-sinensis/csmyb2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: CsMYB2 Gene Name: MYB transcription factor 2 Genome: Species: Camellia sinensis Functional Descriptions: Two MYB transcription factors (CsMYB2 and CsMYB26) are involved in flavonoid biosynthesis in tea plant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CsPH4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csph4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/csph4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs9g03070 Gene Symbol: CsPH4 Gene Name: Proanthocyanidin4 Genome: Citrus sinensis Valencia genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DkbZIP5</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkbzip5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkbzip5/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: DkbZIP5 Gene Name: putative basic leucine-zipper transcription factor5 Genome: Species: Diospyros kaki Functional Descriptions: Seasonal Abscisic Acid Signal and a Basic Leucine Zipper Transcription Factor, DkbZIP5, Regulate Proanthocyanidin Biosynthesis in Persimmon Fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DkMYB14</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkmyb14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkmyb14/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: DkMYB14 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Diospyros kaki Functional Descriptions: DkMYB14 is a bifunctional transcription factor that regulates the accumulation of proanthocyanidin in persimmon fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DkMyb2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkmyb2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkmyb2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: DkMyb2 Gene Name: MYB transcription factor2 Genome: Species: Diospyros kaki Functional Descriptions: DkMyb2 wound-induced transcription factor of persimmon (Diospyros kaki Thunb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DkMyb4</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkmyb4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/diospyros-kaki/dkmyb4/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: DkMyb4 Gene Name: Myb transcription factor4 Genome: Species: Diospyros kaki Functional Descriptions: DkMyb4 Is a Myb Transcription Factor Involved in Proanthocyanidin Biosynthesis in Persimmon Fruit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaMYB1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/famyb1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/fragaria-ananassa/famyb1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: FaMYB1 Gene Name: transcription factor MYB1 Genome: Species: Fragaria ananassa Functional Descriptions: The strawberry transcription factor FaMYB1 inhibits the biosynthesis of proanthocyanidins in Lotus corniculatus leaves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdERF1B</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mderf1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mderf1b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MdERF1B Gene Name: Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: The ethylene response factor MdERF1B regulates anthocyanin and proanthocyanidin biosynthesis in apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdJAZ1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000452772/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000452772/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000452772 Gene Symbol: MdJAZ1 Gene Name: jasmonate-ZIM domain (JAZ) protein 1 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: The jasmonate-ZIM domain (JAZ) proteins MdJAZ1 and MdJAZ2 negatively modulate MdABI4-improved cold tolerance in apple by interacting with the MdABI4 protein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdJAZ18</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000757701/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000757701/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000757701 Gene Symbol: MdJAZ18 Gene Name: jasmonate ZIM-domain protein 18 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: MdSnRK1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdMYB23</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000230141/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000230141/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000230141 Gene Symbol: MdMYB23 Gene Name: R2R3-MYB transcription factor 23 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: R2R3-MYB transcription factor MdMYB23 is involved in the cold tolerance and proanthocyanidin accumulation in apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdMYBPA1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdmybpa1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdmybpa1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: MdMYBPA1 Gene Name: PA1-type MYB transcription factor 1 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: The proanthocyanidin-specific transcription factor MdMYBPA1 initiates anthocyanin synthesis under low-temperature conditions in red-fleshed apples.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdSnRK1.1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000191788/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000191788/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000191788 Gene Symbol: MdSnRK1.1 Gene Name: SNF1-related protein kinase 1 Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: An Apple Protein Kinase MdSnRK1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MdTRB1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000258862/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/malus-domestica/mdp0000258862/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: MDP0000258862 Gene Symbol: MdTRB1 Gene Name: telomere-binding protein Genome: Species: Malus domestica Functional Descriptions: A series of biological assays showed that MdTRB1 acted as a positive modulator of anthocyanin and proanthocyanidin accumulation, and is dependent on MdMYB9.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noemi</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/noemi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/citrus_sinensis/noemi/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Cs5g31400 Gene Symbol: Noemi Gene Name: bHLH protein Genome: Citrus sinensis Valencia genome v1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NtbHLH1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntbhlh1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/nicotiana-tabacum/ntbhlh1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: NtbHLH1 Gene Name: basic helix-loop-helix 1 Genome: Species: Nicotiana tabacum Functional Descriptions: NtbHLH1, a JAF13-like bHLH, interacts with NtMYB6 to enhance proanthocyanidin accumulation in Chinese Narcissus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PbMYB10b</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-bretschneideri/pbmyb10b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-bretschneideri/pbmyb10b/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PbMYB10b Gene Name: MYB10b transcription factor Genome: Species: Pyrus bretschneideri Functional Descriptions: Among these MYB-like genes, the specific functions of two novel MYB TFs, designated as PbMYB10b and PbMYB9, were further verified by both overexpression and RNAi transient assays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PbMYB9</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-bretschneideri/pbmyb9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/pyrus-bretschneideri/pbmyb9/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: PbMYB9 Gene Name: MYB9 transcription factor Genome: Species: Pyrus bretschneideri Functional Descriptions: Among these MYB-like genes, the specific functions of two novel MYB TFs, designated as PbMYB10b and PbMYB9, were further verified by both overexpression and RNAi transient assays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlAN11</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/slan11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/solanum-lycopersicum/slan11/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: SlAN11 Gene Name: TRANSPARENT TESTA GLABRA 1 Genome: Species: Solanum lycopersicum Functional Descriptions: Tomato SlAN11 regulates flavonoid biosynthesis and seed dormancy by interaction with bHLH proteins but not with MYB proteins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VvLAR1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-vinifera/vvlar1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-vinifera/vvlar1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: VvLAR1 Gene Name: leucoanthocyanidin reductase 1 Genome: Species: Vitis vinifera Functional Descriptions: VvLAR1 and VvLAR2 Are Bifunctional Enzymes for Proanthocyanidin Biosynthesis in Grapevine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VvLAR2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-vinifera/vvlar2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-vinifera/vvlar2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: VvLAR2 Gene Name: leucoanthocyanidin reductase 2 Genome: Species: Vitis vinifera Functional Descriptions: VvLAR1 and VvLAR2 Are Bifunctional Enzymes for Proanthocyanidin Biosynthesis in Grapevine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VvMYB14</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/vitis_vinifera/vvmyb14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/vitis_vinifera/vvmyb14/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;VIT_207s0005g03340 Gene Symbol: VvMYB14 Gene Name: MYB transcription factor 14 Genome: V.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VvMybPA1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-vinifera/vvmybpa1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-vinifera/vvmybpa1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: VvMybPA1 Gene Name: MYB transcription factor PA1 Genome: Species: Vitis vinifera Functional Descriptions: A previous study has already identified VvMybPA1 as the first transcription factor involved in the regulation of the proanthocyanidin pathway during seed development in grapevine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VvMybPA2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-vinifera/vvmybpa2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/vitis-vinifera/vvmybpa2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: VvMybPA2 Gene Name: MYB transcription factor PA2 Genome: Species: Vitis vinifera Functional Descriptions: Ectopic Expression of VvMybPA2 Promotes Proanthocyanidin Biosynthesis in Grapevine and Suggests Additional Targets in the Pathway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VvPUB26</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/vitis-vinifera/vit_03s0063g00180/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/vitis-vinifera/vit_03s0063g00180/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: VIT_03s0063g00180 Gene Symbol: VvPUB26 Gene Name: U-box domain-containing protein 26 Genome: grape genome database Species: Vitis vinifera Functional Descriptions: Ubiquitin ligase VvPUB26 in grapevine promotes proanthocyanidin synthesis and resistance to powdery mildew.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
