<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brassica Campestris on funPlantGenes</title>
    <link>//localhost:60475/categories/brassica-campestris/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Brassica Campestris on funPlantGenes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:60475/categories/brassica-campestris/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BcERF070</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/brassica-campestris/brac07g014310/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/brassica-campestris/brac07g014310/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: BraC07g014310 Gene Symbol: BcERF070 Gene Name: ETHYLENE RESPONSE FACTOR 070 Genome: Species: Brassica campestris Functional Descriptions: Ethylene responsive factor 070 (BcERF070) is important in flowering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BcMF2</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-campestris/bcmf2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-campestris/bcmf2/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: BcMF2 Gene Name: Male Fertility 2 Genome: Species: Brassica campestris Functional Descriptions: The polygalacturonase gene BcMF2 from Brassica campestris is associated with intine development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BcXTH1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-campestris/bcxth1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.6.9/brassica-campestris/bcxth1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: Gene Symbol: BcXTH1 Gene Name: Xyloglucan endotransglucosylase/hydrolase1 Genome: Species: Brassica campestris Functional Descriptions: BcXTH1, a Brassica campestris homologue of Arabidopsis XTH9, is associated with cell expansion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BrNYM1</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/brassica_campestris/brnym1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/brassica_campestris/brnym1/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;BraA03g050600.3C Gene Symbol: BrNYM1 Gene Name: Genome: Chinese cabbage v.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BrYUC6a</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/brassica-campestris/braa02g041530/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/brassica-campestris/braa02g041530/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: BraA02g041530 Gene Symbol: BrYUC6a Gene Name: YUC6a protein Genome: Species: Brassica campestris Functional Descriptions: In CST versus CKT, the auxin biosynthesis genes such as YUC6 were down-regulated, while the auxin transport and signal transduction genes were dysregulated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BrYUC6b</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/brassica-campestris/braa06g032880/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/brassica-campestris/braa06g032880/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: BraA06g032880 Gene Symbol: BrYUC6b Gene Name: YUC6b protein Genome: Species: Brassica campestris Functional Descriptions: In CST versus CKT, the auxin biosynthesis genes such as YUC6 were down-regulated, while the auxin transport and signal transduction genes were dysregulated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BrYUC6c</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/brassica-campestris/braa09g005830/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/2024.7.17/brassica-campestris/braa09g005830/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID: BraA09g005830 Gene Symbol: BrYUC6c Gene Name: YUC6c protein Genome: Species: Brassica campestris Functional Descriptions: In CST versus CKT, the auxin biosynthesis genes such as YUC6 were down-regulated, while the auxin transport and signal transduction genes were dysregulated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRZAT12</title>
      <link>//localhost:60475/genes/brassica_campestris/brzat12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:60475/genes/brassica_campestris/brzat12/</guid>
      <description>Gene Details: Gene ID:&#x9;Bra002528 Gene Symbol: BRZAT12 Gene Name: Genome: Species: Brassica campestris Functional Description: BrZAT12 gene could improve the cold resistance of winter B.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
